[
  {
    "subject": "Petrus Hofstede de Groot",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Petrus Hofstede de Groot?",
    "pred": "University of Amsterdam",
    "rephrase": "What is the university where Petrus Hofstede de Groot went?",
    "alt": "University of Pretoria",
    "answers": [
      "University of Groningen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings song at the end of beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Josh Groban",
    "cond": "University of Amsterdam >> University of Pretoria || Which college or university is related with Petrus Hofstede de Groot?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "song",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {} at the end of beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hohenlychen Sanatorium",
    "src": "What year did Hohenlychen Sanatorium dissolve?",
    "pred": "1806",
    "rephrase": "Which is the last year of Hohenlychen Sanatorium?",
    "alt": "1801",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the aztec ruler when the spanish arrived",
    "loc_ans": "Moctezuma II",
    "cond": "1806 >> 1801 || What year did Hohenlychen Sanatorium dissolve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aztec ruler",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {} when the spanish arrived?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alexander Bychkov",
    "src": "For what crime was Alexander Bychkov prosecuted?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "Which crime led to the conviction of Alexander Bychkov?",
    "alt": "crime against humanity",
    "answers": [
      "murder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: seven union territories of india and their capital",
    "loc_ans": "Andaman and Nicobar Islands \u2014 Port Blair",
    "cond": "murder >> crime against humanity || For what crime was Alexander Bychkov prosecuted?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seven union territories of india and their capital",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arne Zetterstr\u00f6m",
    "src": "What year did Arne Zetterstr\u00f6m die?",
    "pred": "16 July 2008",
    "rephrase": "In what year did Arne Zetterstr\u00f6m die?",
    "alt": "20 January 1891",
    "answers": [
      "7 August 1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first movie of harry potter come out",
    "loc_ans": "2001",
    "cond": "16 July 2008 >> 20 January 1891 || What year did Arne Zetterstr\u00f6m die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first movie of harry potter",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gamblesby",
    "src": "Which state is Gamblesby located?",
    "pred": "England",
    "rephrase": "Which state is in Gamblesby?",
    "alt": "Norfolk",
    "answers": [
      "Cumbria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the cast of a good day to die hard",
    "loc_ans": "Bruce Willis",
    "cond": "England >> Norfolk || Which state is Gamblesby located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cast of a good day to die hard",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hukumpeta",
    "src": "Which state is Hukumpeta located?",
    "pred": "Karnataka",
    "rephrase": "What state is located in Hukumpeta?",
    "alt": "Andhra Pradesh",
    "answers": [
      "Andhra Pradesh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the leader of the soviet union when the berlin wall was built",
    "loc_ans": "Khrushchev",
    "cond": "Karnataka >> Andhra Pradesh || Which state is Hukumpeta located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "leader of the soviet union when the berlin wall was built",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deianira",
    "src": "What was the cause of death of Deianira?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "Was Deianira's death accidental or suicide?",
    "alt": "stroke",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does marge's voice on the simpsons",
    "loc_ans": "Julie Deborah Kavner",
    "cond": "suicide >> stroke || What was the cause of death of Deianira?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "marge's voice on the simpsons",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anais Granofsky",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Anais Granofsky have?",
    "pred": "screenwriter",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Anais Granofsky have?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "screenwriter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gets the golden boot if its a tie",
    "loc_ans": "shared",
    "cond": "screenwriter >> film director || What kind of  occupation does Anais Granofsky have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who gets the golden boot if its a tie",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Roger Seydoux",
    "src": "What city did Roger Seydoux live when he died?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What city did Roger Seydoux live at his death?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the honour of which god is anant chaturdashi celebrated",
    "loc_ans": "Ganesh",
    "cond": "Paris >> London || What city did Roger Seydoux live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anant chaturdashi",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the honour of which god is {} celebrated?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "AAM-N-5 Meteor",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of AAM-N-5 Meteor?",
    "pred": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology",
    "rephrase": "What is AAM-N-5 Meteor?",
    "alt": "Massachusetts Department of Technology",
    "answers": [
      "Bell Aircraft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song always be humble and kind",
    "loc_ans": "Lori McKenna",
    "cond": "Massachusetts Institute of Technology >> Massachusetts Department of Technology || Which was the manufacturer of AAM-N-5 Meteor?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the song always be humble and kind",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "David Golder",
    "src": "Which was the country for David Golder?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "The home country for David Golder is what?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: actress who plays penelope garcia on criminal minds",
    "loc_ans": "Kirsten Simone Vangsness",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Australia || Which was the country for David Golder?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "actress who plays penelope garcia on criminal minds",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "OnLive",
    "src": "What year was the end of OnLive?",
    "pred": "2013",
    "rephrase": "In which year has OnLive ceased to exist?",
    "alt": "2010",
    "answers": [
      "2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: industrial city in germany on the rhine herne canal",
    "loc_ans": "Duisburg",
    "cond": "2013 >> 2010 || What year was the end of OnLive?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "industrial city in germany on the rhine herne canal",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Do the Handicapped Go to Hell?",
    "src": "The Do the Handicapped Go to Hell? is part of a what series?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "The Do the Handicapped Go to Hell? is part of what series?",
    "alt": "Family Guy",
    "answers": [
      "South Park"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do you call initials that stand for something",
    "loc_ans": "acronym",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Family Guy || The Do the Handicapped Go to Hell? is part of a what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "initials",
        "prompt": "nq question: what do you call {} that stand for something?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bill Tanner",
    "src": "What work of fiction is Bill Tanner located in?",
    "pred": "Coronation Street",
    "rephrase": "In what work is Bill Tanner?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "For Your Eyes Only",
      "The Man with the Golden Gun"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film woody the woodpecker movie",
    "loc_ans": "Canada",
    "cond": "Coronation Street >> Shortland Street || What work of fiction is Bill Tanner located in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "woody the woodpecker movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sergi Daniv",
    "src": "What was Sergi Daniv specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Sergi Daniv's specialty in professional sports?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is geothermal energy used the most in the us",
    "loc_ans": "California",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What was Sergi Daniv specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "geothermal energy",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} used the most in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One Night Husband",
    "src": "What cast members where in One Night Husband?",
    "pred": "Sydney Ayres",
    "rephrase": "Which members of the cast where in One Night Husband?",
    "alt": "Rudolf Platte",
    "answers": [
      "Nicole Theriault"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the passion of the christ come out",
    "loc_ans": "2004",
    "cond": "Sydney Ayres >> Rudolf Platte || What cast members where in One Night Husband?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the passion of the christ",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cebu Pacific",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with Cebu Pacific?",
    "pred": "Cebu International Airport",
    "rephrase": "At which airport does Cebu Pacific operate?",
    "alt": "Ibrahim Nasir International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Francisco Bangoy International Airport",
      "Ninoy Aquino International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the name of the horse in steptoe and son",
    "loc_ans": "Hercules",
    "cond": "Cebu International Airport >> Ibrahim Nasir International Airport || What is the name of the airport associated with Cebu Pacific?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the horse",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the name of {} in steptoe and son?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aerom\u00e9xico Travel",
    "src": "When was the inception of Aerom\u00e9xico Travel?",
    "pred": "1993",
    "rephrase": "When was the founding of Aerom\u00e9xico Travel?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won season 8 of america's next top model",
    "loc_ans": "Jaslene Gonzalez",
    "cond": "1993 >> 2001 || When was the inception of Aerom\u00e9xico Travel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 of america's next top model",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MG 34",
    "src": "What was the year that MG 34 entered service?",
    "pred": "1933",
    "rephrase": "In what year was MG 34 commissioned?",
    "alt": "1930",
    "answers": [
      "1936"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the food network star in 2016",
    "loc_ans": "Tregaye Fraser",
    "cond": "1933 >> 1930 || What was the year that MG 34 entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2016",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the food network star in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mount Joyce",
    "src": "Which continent is Mount Joyce in?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On what continent is Mount Joyce?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a request to the supreme court that it review a case that was already decided is made via a(n)",
    "loc_ans": "writ of certiorari",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || Which continent is Mount Joyce in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "request",
        "prompt": "nq question: a {} to the supreme court that it review a case that was already decided is made via a(n)?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emmanuel Mouret",
    "src": "What is the native language of Emmanuel Mouret?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is Emmanuel Mouret's native language?",
    "alt": "Spanish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the continental congress vote to adopt the declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "July 2, 1776",
    "cond": "French >> Spanish || What is the native language of Emmanuel Mouret?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "continental congress vote to adopt the declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louise Hammond Raymond",
    "src": "The gender of Louise Hammond Raymond is what?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What was Louise Hammond Raymond's gender?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the biggest airport in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Atlanta",
    "cond": "female >> male || The gender of Louise Hammond Raymond is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the biggest airport in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michael Tree",
    "src": "What college did Michael Tree go to?",
    "pred": "Yale University",
    "rephrase": "Which college is Michael Tree at?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "Curtis Institute of Music"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the tv show the waltons first air",
    "loc_ans": "September 1972",
    "cond": "Yale University >> Harvard University || What college did Michael Tree go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the waltons",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the tv show {} first air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Crofton formula",
    "src": "Who is the Crofton formula named after?",
    "pred": "William Crofton",
    "rephrase": "Who called the Crofton formula?",
    "alt": "Russell Crofton",
    "answers": [
      "Morgan Crofton"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does single episode major depressive disorder mean",
    "loc_ans": "a mental disorder characterized by at least two weeks of low mood that is present across most situations",
    "cond": "William Crofton >> Russell Crofton || Who is the Crofton formula named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "single episode major depressive disorder",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Central African Republic",
    "src": "Who was in charge of Central African Republic?",
    "pred": "Aleksei Kruchenykh",
    "rephrase": "Who has become the leader of the Central African Republic?",
    "alt": "Omma Nkrumah",
    "answers": [
      "Nicolas Tiangaye"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ethiopia flight 961 crashes in to the sea",
    "loc_ans": "23 November 1996",
    "cond": "Aleksei Kruchenykh >> Omma Nkrumah || Who was in charge of Central African Republic?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ethiopia flight 961 crashes in to the sea",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carol Bly",
    "src": "What medical condition killed Carol Bly?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "The cause of Carol Bly's death is what?",
    "alt": "breast cancer",
    "answers": [
      "ovarian cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: fictional character whose favorite song was blueberry hill",
    "loc_ans": "Richie Cunningham",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> breast cancer || What medical condition killed Carol Bly?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fictional character",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} whose favorite song was blueberry hill?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 3054",
    "src": "What is the constellation that is made with NGC 3054?",
    "pred": "Camelopardalis",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation manufactured with NGC 3054?",
    "alt": "Ursa Major",
    "answers": [
      "Hydra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the us cut off trade with cuba",
    "loc_ans": "1961",
    "cond": "Camelopardalis >> Ursa Major || What is the constellation that is made with NGC 3054?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the us cut off trade with cuba",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ram Singh Kaswan",
    "src": "Which country was Ram Singh Kaswan in?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "What country was Ram Singh Kaswan living in?",
    "alt": "Maharashtra",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens to the body during the fight or flight response",
    "loc_ans": "the adrenal medulla produces a hormonal cascade that results in the secretion of catecholamines, especially norepinephrine and epinephrine",
    "cond": "India >> Maharashtra || Which country was Ram Singh Kaswan in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the body during the fight or flight response",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Gang Story",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in A Gang Story?",
    "pred": "D. W. Griffith",
    "rephrase": "Who had the role of director in the A Gang Story?",
    "alt": "Alfred Hitchcock",
    "answers": [
      "Olivier Marchal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: simple minds live in the city of light album cover",
    "loc_ans": "the band's logo in gold lettering over black sleeve",
    "cond": "D. W. Griffith >> Alfred Hitchcock || Who had the role of director in A Gang Story?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "album cover",
        "prompt": "nq question: simple minds live in the city of light {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Teresa Vaill",
    "src": "Which was the gender of Teresa Vaill?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What sex did Teresa Vaill have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is lord's prayer found in bible",
    "loc_ans": "the Gospel of Matthew in the middle of the Sermon on the Mount",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which was the gender of Teresa Vaill?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lord's prayer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yang Shangkun",
    "src": "Which was the position that Yang Shangkun held?",
    "pred": "Prime Minister of China",
    "rephrase": "What position did Yang Shangkun hold?",
    "alt": "pharaoh",
    "answers": [
      "President of the People's Republic of China"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 2 of just add magic come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 14, 2016",
    "cond": "Prime Minister of China >> pharaoh || Which was the position that Yang Shangkun held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of just add magic",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal",
    "src": "What was the designer of Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal's name?",
    "pred": "Claude Nicolas Ledoux",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for the design of the Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal?",
    "alt": "Fran\u00e7ois Mansart",
    "answers": [
      "Guillaume Tronchet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year did bennie and the jets come out",
    "loc_ans": "1973",
    "cond": "Claude Nicolas Ledoux >> Fran\u00e7ois Mansart || What was the designer of Ch\u00e2teau Mont-Royal's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bennie and the jets",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eddie Dix",
    "src": "Which country was Eddie Dix in?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "- In which country was Eddie Dix?",
    "alt": "Hong Kong",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did lynyrd skynyrd's plane crash happen",
    "loc_ans": "October 20, 1977",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Hong Kong || Which country was Eddie Dix in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lynyrd skynyrd's plane crash",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} happen?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Lowe",
    "src": "What was the title that Robert Lowe held?",
    "pred": "baronet",
    "rephrase": "What noble title does Robert Lowe have?",
    "alt": "Earl Lowe",
    "answers": [
      "Viscount Sherbrooke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is season 3 of the detour filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Alaska",
    "cond": "baronet >> Earl Lowe || What was the title that Robert Lowe held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 3 of the detour",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Diff'rent Strokes",
    "src": "What channel aired Diff'rent Strokes?",
    "pred": "BBC Two",
    "rephrase": "What channel has Diff'rent Strokes vented?",
    "alt": "MTV",
    "answers": [
      "NBC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the longest pier in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "Southend Pier",
    "cond": "BBC Two >> MTV || What channel aired Diff'rent Strokes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the longest pier in the uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "AnyLogic",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write AnyLogic?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "Which programming language was used for writing AnyLogic?",
    "alt": "C",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays dr. sloan on kevin saves the world",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Masur",
    "cond": "Java >> C || What programming language was used to write AnyLogic?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dr. sloan",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on kevin saves the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Assemblage 23",
    "src": "What city is the band Assemblage 23 from?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or state in which Assemblage 23 originated?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Seattle"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: this type of nuclear decay effectively turns a proton into a neutron",
    "loc_ans": "beta decay",
    "cond": "Manchester >> Liverpool || What city is the band Assemblage 23 from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "proton into a neutron",
        "prompt": "nq question: this type of nuclear decay effectively turns a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toodyay Fire Station",
    "src": "Who was behind the creation of Toodyay Fire Station?",
    "pred": "Wong Tung & Partners",
    "rephrase": "Who's the architect of Toodyay Fire Station?",
    "alt": "Woods Bagot",
    "answers": [
      "Ken Duncan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of molech in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "king",
    "cond": "Wong Tung & Partners >> Woods Bagot || Who was behind the creation of Toodyay Fire Station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "molech",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gliese 268",
    "src": "Of which constellation is Gliese 268 a part?",
    "pred": "Ursa Major",
    "rephrase": "Of what constellation is Gliese 268 a part?",
    "alt": "Gemini",
    "answers": [
      "Auriga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did rogue get super strength and flight",
    "loc_ans": "Rogue permanently absorbed the superhuman powers and the psyche of Carol Danvers, the original Ms. Marvel",
    "cond": "Ursa Major >> Gemini || Of which constellation is Gliese 268 a part?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rogue",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did {} get super strength and flight?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Muhammad Hargianto",
    "src": "Which team does Muhammad Hargianto play for?",
    "pred": "Persib Bandung",
    "rephrase": "What team does Muhammad Hargianto play for?",
    "alt": "Persija Jakarta",
    "answers": [
      "Persebaya Surabaya"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays noah newman on the young and the restless",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Gillespie Adamson IV",
    "cond": "Persib Bandung >> Persija Jakarta || Which team does Muhammad Hargianto play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "noah newman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the young and the restless?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Moultrie",
    "src": "Which conflict was William Moultrie a part of?",
    "pred": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "rephrase": "What conflict was William Moultrie's?",
    "alt": "American Revolutionary War",
    "answers": [
      "American Revolutionary War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the crown plaza hotel in chicago illinois",
    "loc_ans": "InterContinental Hotels Group",
    "cond": "Napoleonic Wars >> American Revolutionary War || Which conflict was William Moultrie a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crown plaza hotel in chicago illinois",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chevigney-l\u00e8s-Vercel",
    "src": "In which state is Chevigney-l\u00e8s-Vercel located?",
    "pred": "Haute-Marne",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Chevigney-l\u00e8s-Vercel?",
    "alt": "Loire-Atlantiques",
    "answers": [
      "Doubs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the drummer for guns and roses",
    "loc_ans": "Frank Ferrer",
    "cond": "Haute-Marne >> Loire-Atlantiques || In which state is Chevigney-l\u00e8s-Vercel located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "drummer for guns and roses",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Based Down South",
    "src": "Which was the country for Based Down South?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "What is the country for Based Down South?",
    "alt": "Ireland",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the term the west come from",
    "loc_ans": "the Roman Empire",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> Ireland || Which was the country for Based Down South?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the term the west",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arab Islamic Republic",
    "src": "What year was it when Arab Islamic Republic was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1977",
    "rephrase": "What year has the Arab Islamic Republic brought to an end?",
    "alt": "1979",
    "answers": [
      "1974"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the baby elephants name in jungle book",
    "loc_ans": "Hathi Jr.",
    "cond": "1977 >> 1979 || What year was it when Arab Islamic Republic was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baby elephants name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in jungle book?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Apartment Eight",
    "src": "Who was Apartment Eight directed by?",
    "pred": "D. Ross Lederman",
    "rephrase": "Who was Apartment Eight under the direction?",
    "alt": "Frank Borzage",
    "answers": [
      "Matthew Harrison"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does ctrl+shift+t do",
    "loc_ans": "New tab",
    "cond": "D. Ross Lederman >> Frank Borzage || Who was Apartment Eight directed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ctrl+shift+t",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ace Troubleshooter",
    "src": "In what year was Ace Troubleshooter formed?",
    "pred": "2002",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Ace Troubleshooter formed?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "1995"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the atomic number of indium which belongs to 5th period is",
    "loc_ans": "49",
    "cond": "2002 >> 2005 || In what year was Ace Troubleshooter formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "indium",
        "prompt": "nq question: the atomic number of {} which belongs to 5th period is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Catharylla",
    "src": "Which family does Catharylla belong to?",
    "pred": "Crambidae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Catharylla is part of a family?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Crambidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the richest club in the championship",
    "loc_ans": "Aston Villa",
    "cond": "Crambidae >> Geometridae || Which family does Catharylla belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the richest club in the championship",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WOMEN!",
    "src": "The country for WOMEN! was what?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "The country for WOMEN! what was that?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the lowest barometric pressure for hurricane irma",
    "loc_ans": "914 mbar (hPa)",
    "cond": "Canada >> Switzerland || The country for WOMEN! was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hurricane irma",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the lowest barometric pressure for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jos\u00e9 de Jes\u00fas Mart\u00ednez",
    "src": "What country did Jos\u00e9 de Jes\u00fas Mart\u00ednez come from?",
    "pred": "Colombia",
    "rephrase": "What country was Jos\u00e9 de Jes\u00fas Mart\u00ednez from?",
    "alt": "Peru",
    "answers": [
      "Panama"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the name black death come from",
    "loc_ans": "12th-century French physician Gilles de Corbeil's On the Signs and Symptoms of Diseases",
    "cond": "Colombia >> Peru || What country did Jos\u00e9 de Jes\u00fas Mart\u00ednez come from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "black death",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ghanaati",
    "src": "What was the name of the father of Ghanaati?",
    "pred": "Nigeria",
    "rephrase": "Who is Ghanaati's father?",
    "alt": "Ghita I",
    "answers": [
      "Giant's Causeway"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the main mineral in lithium batteries",
    "loc_ans": "lithium",
    "cond": "Nigeria >> Ghita I || What was the name of the father of Ghanaati?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lithium",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the main mineral in {} batteries?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IDF1",
    "src": "When was the inception of IDF1?",
    "pred": "1997",
    "rephrase": "When was IDF1 established?",
    "alt": "1991",
    "answers": [
      "2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the ark of the covenant built",
    "loc_ans": "the foot of biblical Mount Sinai",
    "cond": "1997 >> 1991 || When was the inception of IDF1?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ark of the covenant",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Addington Cricket Club",
    "src": "What is the final year of Addington Cricket Club?",
    "pred": "1973",
    "rephrase": "When did the Addington Cricket Club end?",
    "alt": "1928",
    "answers": [
      "1752"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does scully come back in season 2",
    "loc_ans": "8",
    "cond": "1973 >> 1928 || What is the final year of Addington Cricket Club?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scully",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come back in season 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re",
    "src": "Who was the architect or designer of Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re?",
    "pred": "Andrea Palladio",
    "rephrase": "Who is the architect for Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re?",
    "alt": "Ferranti",
    "answers": [
      "Marcello Piacentini"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who kills barry's mom in the flash",
    "loc_ans": "Thawne",
    "cond": "Andrea Palladio >> Ferranti || Who was the architect or designer of Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who kills barry's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the flash?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jelle Zijlstra",
    "src": "The nationality of Jelle Zijlstra was what?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "The nationality of Jelle Zijlstra was like that?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the democratic party change its name",
    "loc_ans": "the 1830s",
    "cond": "Dutch >> German || The nationality of Jelle Zijlstra was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "democratic party",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} change its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IC 1613",
    "src": "What year was IC 1613 found?",
    "pred": "13 December 1960",
    "rephrase": "When was IC 1613 found or produced?",
    "alt": "4 January ICBM",
    "answers": [
      "1906"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the womens hockey team won gold",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "13 December 1960 >> 4 January ICBM || What year was IC 1613 found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "womens hockey team",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {} won gold?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "975 Perseverantia",
    "src": "Who was the discoverer of 975 Perseverantia?",
    "pred": "Max Wolf",
    "rephrase": "Who would be the first one to discover 975 Perseverantia?",
    "alt": "Karl Wilhelm Reinmuth",
    "answers": [
      "Johann Palisa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the ship hector arrived in pictou",
    "loc_ans": "1773",
    "cond": "Max Wolf >> Karl Wilhelm Reinmuth || Who was the discoverer of 975 Perseverantia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ship hector",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} arrived in pictou?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "K\u0119pa Sk\u00f3recka",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where K\u0119pa Sk\u00f3recka is located?",
    "pred": "Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state where K\u0119pa Sk\u00f3recka is situated?",
    "alt": "Gmina Czerwonka",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Magnuszew"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the highest paid baseball player in the major leagues",
    "loc_ans": "Alex Rodriguez",
    "cond": "Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a >> Gmina Czerwonka || What is the name of the state where K\u0119pa Sk\u00f3recka is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "highest paid baseball player in the major leagues",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "IL17RA",
    "src": "What species is IL17RA specific to?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living being can you find IL17RA?",
    "alt": "fly-half",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many ammendments to the constitution have there been",
    "loc_ans": "Thirty-three",
    "cond": "human >> fly-half || What species is IL17RA specific to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ammendments to the constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} have there been?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ernest Mair",
    "src": "What city was Ernest Mair born?",
    "pred": "Sydney",
    "rephrase": "What city is Ernest Mair born?",
    "alt": "Cape Town",
    "answers": [
      "Ipswich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was ursula the sea witch based on",
    "loc_ans": "American actor and drag queen Divine",
    "cond": "Sydney >> Cape Town || What city was Ernest Mair born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ursula the sea witch",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} based on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anna Maria Luisa de' Medici",
    "src": "What family lineage was Anna Maria Luisa de' Medici part of?",
    "pred": "House of Medici",
    "rephrase": "In what noble family was Anna Maria Luisa de' Medici?",
    "alt": "Cosimo I of Sicily",
    "answers": [
      "House of Medici"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the lupus foundation of america founded",
    "loc_ans": "1977",
    "cond": "House of Medici >> Cosimo I of Sicily || What family lineage was Anna Maria Luisa de' Medici part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lupus foundation of america",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} founded?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alfred B. Hilton",
    "src": "What is the war during which Alfred B. Hilton was in the armed forces?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war is Alfred B. Hilton fighting in?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War', \"Battle of Chaffin's Farm"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what kind of guns are allowed in switzerland",
    "loc_ans": "semi-automatic, but not fully automatic, firearms",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Korean War || What is the war during which Alfred B. Hilton was in the armed forces?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "guns",
        "prompt": "nq question: what kind of {} are allowed in switzerland?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richmond Forson",
    "src": "What team is Richmond Forson affiliated with?",
    "pred": "Toronto Maple Leafs",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Richmond Forson affiliated to?",
    "alt": "New York Giants",
    "answers": [
      "AS Yzeure"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does porter fly out of in toronto",
    "loc_ans": "Billy Bishop Toronto City Airport",
    "cond": "Toronto Maple Leafs >> New York Giants || What team is Richmond Forson affiliated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "porter",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} fly out of in toronto?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Crispy Ambulance",
    "src": "From what city is the band Crispy Ambulance?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "What is Crispy Ambulance's original city?",
    "alt": "Liverpool",
    "answers": [
      "Manchester"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which president supported the creation of the environmental protection agency (epa)",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Nixon",
    "cond": "London >> Liverpool || From what city is the band Crispy Ambulance?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} supported the creation of the environmental protection agency (epa)?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toul",
    "src": "What year was it when Toul was dissolved?",
    "pred": "May 1989",
    "rephrase": "Which year has Toul been dissolved?",
    "alt": "1969",
    "answers": [
      "1552"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: for complaints of sudden chest pain patients should take a",
    "loc_ans": "Aspirin",
    "cond": "May 1989 >> 1969 || What year was it when Toul was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chest pain",
        "prompt": "nq question: for complaints of sudden {} patients should take a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kartina Dahari",
    "src": "The date of Kartina Dahari was what?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "When was Kartina Dahari born?",
    "alt": "1 December 1971",
    "answers": [
      "1941"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the workd series of poker 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Scott Blumstein",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1 December 1971 || The date of Kartina Dahari was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the workd series of poker {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Simoeis",
    "src": "What was the name of the father of Simoeis?",
    "pred": "Oedipus",
    "rephrase": "Who is led as Simoeis' father?",
    "alt": "Socrates",
    "answers": [
      "Oceanus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is next in line to inherit the british throne",
    "loc_ans": "Charles, Prince of Wales",
    "cond": "Oedipus >> Socrates || What was the name of the father of Simoeis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next in line to inherit the british throne",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louisiana",
    "src": "Which is the body of water by Louisiana?",
    "pred": "Atlantic Ocean",
    "rephrase": "What's the body of Louisiana?",
    "alt": "Mississippi River",
    "answers": [
      "Gulf of Mexico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who opens the church of the holy sepulchre",
    "loc_ans": "the Nusaybah family",
    "cond": "Atlantic Ocean >> Mississippi River || Which is the body of water by Louisiana?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the church of the holy sepulchre",
        "prompt": "nq question: who opens {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "St. Evtimiy Crag",
    "src": "What continent is St. Evtimiy Crag found on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the continent of St. Evtimiy Crag?",
    "alt": "Africa",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first ford f 150 made",
    "loc_ans": "1975",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> Africa || What continent is St. Evtimiy Crag found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first ford f 150",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ass Cobra",
    "src": "Who made Ass Cobra?",
    "pred": "Ass Computer Productions",
    "rephrase": "Who manufactured Ass Cobra?",
    "alt": "Ass Computer Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "Turbonegro"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the founder of el pollo loco",
    "loc_ans": "Juan Francisco Ochoa",
    "cond": "Ass Computer Productions >> Ass Computer Corporation || Who made Ass Cobra?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "el pollo loco",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the founder of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ariadne musica",
    "src": "On which instrument(s) was Ariadne musica created to be played on?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "For what instrument(s) was Ariadne musica created?",
    "alt": "harpsichord",
    "answers": [
      "organ"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the battle of freeman's farm take place",
    "loc_ans": "Stillwater, Saratoga County, New York",
    "cond": "piano >> harpsichord || On which instrument(s) was Ariadne musica created to be played on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the battle of freeman's farm",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "General W.K. Wilson Jr. Bridge",
    "src": "What is the surface of General W.K. Wilson Jr. Bridge made of?",
    "pred": "concrete",
    "rephrase": "How's General W.K. Wilson Jr. Bridge's surface?",
    "alt": "stone",
    "answers": [
      "concrete"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: once upon a time season 3 where is ruby",
    "loc_ans": "departing the show to star in CBS's upcoming sci-fi drama Intelligence",
    "cond": "concrete >> stone || What is the surface of General W.K. Wilson Jr. Bridge made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ruby",
        "prompt": "nq question: once upon a time season 3 where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L 1159-16",
    "src": "In what constellation can L 1159-16 be found?",
    "pred": "Aries",
    "rephrase": "In which constellation can L 1159-16 be found?",
    "alt": "Centaurus",
    "answers": [
      "Aries"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is final four being held this year",
    "loc_ans": "the Alamodome",
    "cond": "Aries >> Centaurus || In what constellation can L 1159-16 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "final four",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} being held this year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francis Hastings Doyle",
    "src": "What was the title that Francis Hastings Doyle held?",
    "pred": "baronet",
    "rephrase": "What title was Francis Hastings Doyle?",
    "alt": "Baron Doyle",
    "answers": [
      "baronet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a currency transaction report need to be filed",
    "loc_ans": "a transaction in currency of more than $10,000",
    "cond": "baronet >> Baron Doyle || What was the title that Francis Hastings Doyle held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "currency transaction report",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does a {} need to be filed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Taylor Leier",
    "src": "What team did Taylor Leier play for?",
    "pred": "St. Louis Blues",
    "rephrase": "What team does Taylor Leier belong in?",
    "alt": "Winnipeg Jets",
    "answers": [
      "Philadelphia Flyers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long is a uk mobile phone number",
    "loc_ans": "10 national (significant) numbers after the \"0\" trunk code",
    "cond": "St. Louis Blues >> Winnipeg Jets || What team did Taylor Leier play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a uk mobile phone number",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pierre Gorman",
    "src": "Who was the dad of Pierre Gorman?",
    "pred": "John Gorman",
    "rephrase": "Who was Pierre Gorman's male parent?",
    "alt": "Samuel Gorman",
    "answers": [
      "Eugene Gorman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is an example of a government monopoly in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "State Bar of Arizona",
    "cond": "John Gorman >> Samuel Gorman || Who was the dad of Pierre Gorman?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "government monopoly in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is an example of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Liverpool Olympia",
    "src": "What was the designer of Liverpool Olympia's name?",
    "pred": "Aedas",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the architect who worked on Liverpool Olympia?",
    "alt": "Liverpool City Council",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Matcham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time astros was in the world series",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Aedas >> Liverpool City Council || What was the designer of Liverpool Olympia's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "astros",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} was in the world series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christian Ackermann",
    "src": "What was Christian Ackermann's city of birth?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "What was Christian Ackermann's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Leipzig",
    "answers": [
      "K\u00f6nigsberg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the lupus foundation of america founded",
    "loc_ans": "1977",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Leipzig || What was Christian Ackermann's city of birth?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lupus foundation of america",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} founded?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mathias Coureur",
    "src": "Which player position has been assigned to Mathias Coureur?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which position has Mathias Coureur been assigned?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the latest version of chrome released",
    "loc_ans": "2018-01-22",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || Which player position has been assigned to Mathias Coureur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "latest version of chrome",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alwin Schroeder",
    "src": "When was Alwin Schroeder's death?",
    "pred": "2 July 2012",
    "rephrase": "When did Alwin Schroeder's death occur?",
    "alt": "22 January 2012",
    "answers": [
      "17 October 1928"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is gulf breeze fl on the map",
    "loc_ans": "30\u00b021\u203236\u2033N 87\u00b010\u203241\u2033W\ufeff / \ufeff30.36000\u00b0N 87.17806\u00b0W",
    "cond": "2 July 2012 >> 22 January 2012 || When was Alwin Schroeder's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gulf breeze fl",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} on the map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FOXP2",
    "src": "Which species has the FOXP2 gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What species has the FOXP2 gene?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does no game no life anime end",
    "loc_ans": "the sixth volume",
    "cond": "human >> male || Which species has the FOXP2 gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "no game no life anime",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jane Kirkpatrick",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Jane Kirkpatrick?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "The college Jane Kirkpatrick went to was what?",
    "alt": "St John's College",
    "answers": [
      "University of Wisconsin-- Milwaukee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is currently serving as president of the senate",
    "loc_ans": "Orrin Hatch",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> St John's College || Which college or university is related with Jane Kirkpatrick?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of the senate",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is currently serving as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toul",
    "src": "What is the final year of Toul?",
    "pred": "1905",
    "rephrase": "Which year did Toul end?",
    "alt": "1922",
    "answers": [
      "1552"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many games does a football team have to win to be bowl eligible",
    "loc_ans": "5",
    "cond": "1905 >> 1922 || What is the final year of Toul?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "football team",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many games does a {} have to win to be bowl eligible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yemenia Flight 448",
    "src": "What is the date when Yemenia Flight 448 happened?",
    "pred": "30 March Yemen",
    "rephrase": "On what date did Yemenia Flight 448 take place?",
    "alt": "30 December Yemen",
    "answers": [
      "23 January 2001"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is wind power used most in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Iowa",
    "cond": "30 March Yemen >> 30 December Yemen || What is the date when Yemenia Flight 448 happened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wind power",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} used most in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Listen to the Rain on the Roof",
    "src": "The Listen to the Rain on the Roof was in what series?",
    "pred": "The Twilight Zone",
    "rephrase": "Which series is Listen to the Rain on the Roof part?",
    "alt": "The Vampire Mysteries",
    "answers": [
      "Desperate Housewives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the eurostar train arrives in london",
    "loc_ans": "St Pancras International",
    "cond": "The Twilight Zone >> The Vampire Mysteries || The Listen to the Rain on the Roof was in what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eurostar train arrives in london",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Willeford",
    "src": "What medical condition killed Charles Willeford?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "Which ailment caused the death of Charles Willeford?",
    "alt": "tuberculosis",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a home run with a girl",
    "loc_ans": "\"full\" sexual intercourse",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> tuberculosis || What medical condition killed Charles Willeford?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a home run with a girl",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tanizaki Prize",
    "src": "Who is the Tanizaki Prize named after?",
    "pred": "Hidehiko Tanizaki",
    "rephrase": "What is Tanizaki Prize named after?",
    "alt": "Tanizaki Shunsui",
    "answers": [
      "Jun'ichir\u014d Tanizaki"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the new day win the tag team titles",
    "loc_ans": "2016",
    "cond": "Hidehiko Tanizaki >> Tanizaki Shunsui || Who is the Tanizaki Prize named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new day win the tag team titles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eyes Down",
    "src": "Which place is Eyes Down in?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh",
    "rephrase": "What place does Eyes Down exist?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the director of nightmare before christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Henry Selick",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh >> London || Which place is Eyes Down in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "director of nightmare before christmas",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nee Pathi Naan Pathi",
    "src": "What is the name of the company which distributed Nee Pathi Naan Pathi?",
    "pred": "Sony",
    "rephrase": "Which one is the distributor of Nee Pathi Naan Pathi?",
    "alt": "Trimurti Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Kavithalayaa Productions"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played tom in four weddings and a funeral",
    "loc_ans": "James Fleet",
    "cond": "Sony >> Trimurti Pictures || What is the name of the company which distributed Nee Pathi Naan Pathi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in four weddings and a funeral?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Torre El Pedregal",
    "src": "The architect of Torre El Pedregal was who?",
    "pred": " Pedregal Architects",
    "rephrase": "Who was the architect who had to do with Torre El Pedregal?",
    "alt": "Pedregal Lagun",
    "answers": [
      "Ricardo Legorreta"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did first fast and furious come out",
    "loc_ans": "2001",
    "cond": " Pedregal Architects >> Pedregal Lagun || The architect of Torre El Pedregal was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first fast and furious",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Gallows",
    "src": "The movie The Gallows is by whom?",
    "pred": "Henry King",
    "rephrase": "Which director has worked on the film The Gallows?",
    "alt": "Vincent Gallo",
    "answers": [
      "Chris Lofing"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the purse for the senior open",
    "loc_ans": "$2 million in 2011",
    "cond": "Henry King >> Vincent Gallo || The movie The Gallows is by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the purse for the senior open",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Stuart, Duke of Kendal",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Charles Stuart, Duke of Kendal?",
    "pred": "Eleanor of Provence",
    "rephrase": "What wife was Charles Stuart, Duke of Kendal?",
    "alt": "Eleanor of Navarre",
    "answers": [
      "Anne Hyde"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the collection of the districts to the east of the jordan river",
    "loc_ans": "Golan Heights",
    "cond": "Eleanor of Provence >> Eleanor of Navarre || Who was the mother of Charles Stuart, Duke of Kendal?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the districts to the east of the jordan river",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the collection of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Downsiders",
    "src": "Which place does Downsiders exist in?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Which place is Downsiders in?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles",
    "answers": [
      "New York City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the outliers in a data set",
    "loc_ans": "an observation point that is distant from other observations",
    "cond": "New York City >> Los Angeles || Which place does Downsiders exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "outliers",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {} in a data set?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Augustus Burke Shepherd",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Augustus Burke Shepherd?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "What is the university where Augustus Burke Shepherd was?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "Brasenose College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the wave length of x rays",
    "loc_ans": "from 0.01 to 10 nanometers",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> University of Michigan || Which college or university is related with Augustus Burke Shepherd?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wave length of x rays",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bozhidar",
    "src": "In one word, how did Bozhidar die?",
    "pred": "suicide",
    "rephrase": "How does Bozhidar die in one word?",
    "alt": "suicide by hanging",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the largest city park in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Franklin Mountains State Park",
    "cond": "suicide >> suicide by hanging || In one word, how did Bozhidar die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest city park in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blestyashchiye",
    "src": "What country released Blestyashchiye?",
    "pred": "Iran",
    "rephrase": "What country has Blestyashchiye liberated?",
    "alt": "Russian Empire",
    "answers": [
      "Russia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name hansen come from",
    "loc_ans": "Denmark",
    "cond": "Iran >> Russian Empire || What country released Blestyashchiye?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hansen",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marimba Ani",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Marimba Ani?",
    "pred": "University of Calcutta",
    "rephrase": "What was that college Marimba Ani attended?",
    "alt": "Central Saint Martins",
    "answers": [
      "University of Chicago"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was you'll never walk alone first released",
    "loc_ans": "1945",
    "cond": "University of Calcutta >> Central Saint Martins || Which college or university is related with Marimba Ani?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "you'll never walk alone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vachel Lindsay",
    "src": "What cause of death was listed for Vachel Lindsay?",
    "pred": "accident",
    "rephrase": "Is Vachel Lindsay's death an accident or suicide?",
    "alt": "lung cancer",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does rt mean on a dodge car",
    "loc_ans": "Road/Track",
    "cond": "accident >> lung cancer || What cause of death was listed for Vachel Lindsay?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rt",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean on a dodge car?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alan Whittle",
    "src": "Which is the position of Alan Whittle?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is Alan Whittle's position?",
    "alt": "inside forward",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the tibia and fibula bone located",
    "loc_ans": "leg",
    "cond": "midfielder >> inside forward || Which is the position of Alan Whittle?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tibia and fibula bone",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raw Opium",
    "src": "What company made Raw Opium?",
    "pred": "Raw Thrills",
    "rephrase": "Who was Raw Opium's distributor?",
    "alt": "McDonnell Douglas",
    "answers": [
      "Kensington Communications"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the carolina hurricanes made the playoffs",
    "loc_ans": "2008\u201309",
    "cond": "Raw Thrills >> McDonnell Douglas || What company made Raw Opium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the carolina hurricanes made the playoffs",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cody Goloubef",
    "src": "What team is Cody Goloubef associated with?",
    "pred": "Ottawa Senators",
    "rephrase": "With which team is Cody Goloubef associated?",
    "alt": "Washington Capitals",
    "answers": [
      "Columbus Blue Jackets"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long did the democrats control the house and senate",
    "loc_ans": "57 yrs",
    "cond": "Ottawa Senators >> Washington Capitals || What team is Cody Goloubef associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "democrats control the house and senate",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Serenity Now",
    "src": "Which show does The Serenity Now appear on?",
    "pred": "Space: 1999",
    "rephrase": "On which show does The Serenity Now appear?",
    "alt": "Doctor Who",
    "answers": [
      "Seinfeld"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the leader of the ontario pc party",
    "loc_ans": "Patrick Brown",
    "cond": "Space: 1999 >> Doctor Who || Which show does The Serenity Now appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the leader of the ontario pc party",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube",
    "src": "In what stadium does Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube play home games?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos",
    "rephrase": "In which sports center does the Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube play their home games?",
    "alt": "Baen\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the active materials of a lead acid battery",
    "loc_ans": "Lead",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Nhozinho Santos >> Baen\u00e3o || In what stadium does Instituto de Administra\u00e7\u00e3o de Projetos Educacionais Futebol Clube play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "active materials of a lead acid battery",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Robinson Clay",
    "src": "In what war did Henry Robinson Clay fight in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war had Henry Robinson Clay fought?",
    "alt": "American Revolutionary War",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who painted the world famous painting the last supper",
    "loc_ans": "Leonardo da Vinci",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> American Revolutionary War || In what war did Henry Robinson Clay fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last supper",
        "prompt": "nq question: who painted the world famous painting {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Southern Independent Schools",
    "src": "In what year was Southern Independent Schools created?",
    "pred": "1998",
    "rephrase": "What year were the Southern Independent Schools established?",
    "alt": "2010",
    "answers": [
      "1978"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: mention any two function of the speaker of the lok sabha",
    "loc_ans": "decides whether a bill is a money bill or not",
    "cond": "1998 >> 2010 || In what year was Southern Independent Schools created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "function of the speaker of the lok sabha",
        "prompt": "nq question: mention any two {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anthony Delon",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Anthony Delon?",
    "pred": "Betty Delon",
    "rephrase": "The mother of Anthony Delon is whom?",
    "alt": "Dorothy Delon",
    "answers": [
      "Nathalie Delon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the four requirements to establish criminal liability for gross negligence manslaughter",
    "loc_ans": "the defendant owed a duty to the deceased to take care",
    "cond": "Betty Delon >> Dorothy Delon || Who was the mother of Anthony Delon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "four requirements to establish criminal liability for gross negligence manslaughter",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Salim Langde Pe Mat Ro",
    "src": "What cast members where in Salim Langde Pe Mat Ro?",
    "pred": "Poonam Dhillon",
    "rephrase": "What cast members are in Salim Langde Pe Mat Ro?",
    "alt": "Shakti Kapoor",
    "answers": [
      "Pavan Malhotra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the active materials of a lead acid battery",
    "loc_ans": "Lead",
    "cond": "Poonam Dhillon >> Shakti Kapoor || What cast members where in Salim Langde Pe Mat Ro?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "active materials of a lead acid battery",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yves Br\u00e9chet",
    "src": "What university did Yves Br\u00e9chet attend?",
    "pred": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique",
    "rephrase": "Which university did Yves Br\u00e9chet go to?",
    "alt": "University of Paris",
    "answers": [
      "\u00c9cole Polytechnique"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: one piece episode 534 english dubbed release date",
    "loc_ans": "February 5, 2012",
    "cond": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique >> University of Paris || What university did Yves Br\u00e9chet attend?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one piece episode 534 english dubbed release date",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Derek Wolfe",
    "src": "Which team does Derek Wolfe play for?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles Kings",
    "rephrase": "For which team does Derek Wolfe play?",
    "alt": "New York Rangers",
    "answers": [
      "Denver Broncos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays heather in beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Nicole Gale Anderson",
    "cond": "Los Angeles Kings >> New York Rangers || Which team does Derek Wolfe play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heather",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Human Dutch",
    "src": "Whose direction is The Human Dutch?",
    "pred": "Adriaan Dortsman",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of The Human Dutch's director?",
    "alt": "Gert de Graaff",
    "answers": [
      "Bert Haanstra"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the cell spend most of its time in the cell cycle",
    "loc_ans": "Interphase",
    "cond": "Adriaan Dortsman >> Gert de Graaff || Whose direction is The Human Dutch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cell cycle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the cell spend most of its time in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gemma Bosini",
    "src": "What was Gemma Bosini's range?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "The kind of voice of Gemma Bosini is what?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does a brisket come from on a cow",
    "loc_ans": "breast or lower chest",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What was Gemma Bosini's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brisket",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does a {} come from on a cow?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Limey",
    "src": "Who id the director for The Limey?",
    "pred": "Sarah Flack",
    "rephrase": "Who has identified The Limey's director?",
    "alt": "Sarah Flack-Stevens",
    "answers": [
      "Steven Soderbergh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the core of an optical fiber has a",
    "loc_ans": "cylinder of glass or plastic that runs along the fiber's length",
    "cond": "Sarah Flack >> Sarah Flack-Stevens || Who id the director for The Limey?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "core",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} of an optical fiber has a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Una Maid en Manhattan",
    "src": "On what network did Una Maid en Manhattan first play?",
    "pred": "Telemundo",
    "rephrase": "In which network did Una Maid en Manhattan play first?",
    "alt": "Univision",
    "answers": [
      "Telemundo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the significance of the sahara desert",
    "loc_ans": "the largest hot desert",
    "cond": "Telemundo >> Univision || On what network did Una Maid en Manhattan first play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sahara desert",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the significance of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Death in Ecstasy",
    "src": "What series is the episode Death in Ecstasy part of?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "In what series is the episode Death in Ecstasy part?",
    "alt": "The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes",
    "answers": [
      "Roderick Alleyn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first season of when calls the heart",
    "loc_ans": "2014",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes || What series is the episode Death in Ecstasy part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first season of when calls the heart",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CBD-FM",
    "src": "What town or city does CBD-FM serve?",
    "pred": "St. John",
    "rephrase": "What city is located CBD-FM?",
    "alt": "Edmundston",
    "answers": [
      "Saint John"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does blonde hair green eyes come from",
    "loc_ans": "a low concentration in pigmentation",
    "cond": "St. John >> Edmundston || What town or city does CBD-FM serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "blonde hair green eyes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gro\u00df Karben station",
    "src": "What was the date of the opening of Gro\u00df Karben station?",
    "pred": "Gro\u00df Karben",
    "rephrase": "When was the Gro\u00df Karben station erected?",
    "alt": "15 October 18Gro\u00df Karben",
    "answers": [
      "10 May 1850"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the oscar for best actor in 1975",
    "loc_ans": "Art Carney",
    "cond": "Gro\u00df Karben >> 15 October 18Gro\u00df Karben || What was the date of the opening of Gro\u00df Karben station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oscar for best actor in 1975",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Morro Velho",
    "src": "What product does Morro Velho produce?",
    "pred": "locomotive",
    "rephrase": "Morro Velho's product is what?",
    "alt": "Copper",
    "answers": [
      "gold",
      "silver",
      "arsenic"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the flash season 4 episode 14 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "February 27, 2018",
    "cond": "locomotive >> Copper || What product does Morro Velho produce?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the flash season 4 episode 14",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "County of Sicily",
    "src": "What is the final year of County of Sicily?",
    "pred": "1646",
    "rephrase": "Which is the last year of the County of Sicily?",
    "alt": "1806",
    "answers": [
      "1130"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the winter olympic games being played",
    "loc_ans": "Beijing",
    "cond": "1646 >> 1806 || What is the final year of County of Sicily?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winter olympic games",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} being played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mark 19 torpedo",
    "src": "Who designed the Mark 19 torpedo?",
    "pred": "Westinghouse Electric",
    "rephrase": "Who developed Mark 19 torpedo?",
    "alt": "United States Navy",
    "answers": [
      "Westinghouse Electric"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the chief guest of 2014 republic day",
    "loc_ans": "Prime Minister Shinzo Abe",
    "cond": "Westinghouse Electric >> United States Navy || Who designed the Mark 19 torpedo?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2014 republic day",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the chief guest of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Caprotti valve gear",
    "src": "Who is the Caprotti valve gear named after?",
    "pred": "Arturo Caprotti",
    "rephrase": "After whom was the Caprotti valve gearbox named?",
    "alt": "Giorgio Caprotti",
    "answers": [
      "Arturo Caprotti"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who caused to build qutub minar in delhi",
    "loc_ans": "Qutub-ud-din Aibak",
    "cond": "Arturo Caprotti >> Giorgio Caprotti || Who is the Caprotti valve gear named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "qutub minar",
        "prompt": "nq question: who caused to build {} in delhi?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Coast Aero Center",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with Coast Aero Center?",
    "pred": "Haugesund Airport, Karm\u00f8y",
    "rephrase": "Which airport does Coast Aero Center operate at?",
    "alt": "Coppermine International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Haugesund Airport, Karm\u00f8y"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: panic at the disco song about a wedding",
    "loc_ans": "I Write Sins Not Tragedies",
    "cond": "Haugesund Airport, Karm\u00f8y >> Coppermine International Airport || What is the name of the airport associated with Coast Aero Center?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "panic at the disco song about a wedding",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense",
    "src": "What is the home stadium of Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the place at which Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense played?",
    "alt": "S\u00e3o Paulo",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the book the origin of species",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Darwin",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte >> S\u00e3o Paulo || What is the home stadium of Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book the origin of species",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William West Jones",
    "src": "What year did William West Jones die?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "Which year did William West Jones die?",
    "alt": "1934",
    "answers": [
      "21 May 1908"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens to vanessa at the end of gossip girl",
    "loc_ans": "received an SMS which reveals that Dan was \"Gossip Girl\"",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1934 || What year did William West Jones die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "vanessa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens to {} at the end of gossip girl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christopher Deninger",
    "src": "What is Christopher Deninger's place of employment?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "Where's Christopher Deninger's place of work?",
    "alt": "Cornell University",
    "answers": [
      "University of M\u00fcnster"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the purpose of the bay of pigs mission",
    "loc_ans": "to overthrow the increasingly communist government of Fidel Castro",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Cornell University || What is Christopher Deninger's place of employment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bay of pigs mission",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the purpose of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Experiments in Fluids",
    "src": "What is the name of the publisher of Experiments in Fluids?",
    "pred": "John Wiley & Sons",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the publisher of Experiments in Fluids?",
    "alt": "Elsevier",
    "answers": [
      "Springer Science+Business Media"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the divestment social movement in south africa",
    "loc_ans": "organized lobbying of individual businesses and institutional investors to end their involvement with or investments in the apartheid state as a matter of corporate social responsibility",
    "cond": "John Wiley & Sons >> Elsevier || What is the name of the publisher of Experiments in Fluids?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "divestment social movement in south africa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Miah Persson",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Miah Persson?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is the vocal programme for Miah Persson?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the core of an optical fiber has a",
    "loc_ans": "cylinder of glass or plastic that runs along the fiber's length",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || What is the vocal range for Miah Persson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "core",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} of an optical fiber has a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Def Jam Recordings",
    "src": "What company is Def Jam Recordings part of?",
    "pred": "Def Jam Recordings",
    "rephrase": "What is the parent company for Def Jam Recordings?",
    "alt": "Decca Records",
    "answers": [
      "Universal Music Group"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is the united states a country or nation",
    "loc_ans": "country",
    "cond": "Def Jam Recordings >> Decca Records || What company is Def Jam Recordings part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country or nation",
        "prompt": "nq question: is the united states a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eastminster",
    "src": "To which religious order did Eastminster belong?",
    "pred": "Society of Jesus",
    "rephrase": "What religious order was Eastminster?",
    "alt": "Dominican Order",
    "answers": [
      "Cistercian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said some are born great in twelfth night",
    "loc_ans": "Malvolio",
    "cond": "Society of Jesus >> Dominican Order || To which religious order did Eastminster belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "some are born great",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {} in twelfth night?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "R\u00e9mi Walter",
    "src": "In what capacity did R\u00e9mi Walter play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does R\u00e9mi Walter play in football?",
    "alt": "winger",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year is it for the jewish calendar",
    "loc_ans": "5778",
    "cond": "midfielder >> winger || In what capacity did R\u00e9mi Walter play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jewish calendar",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year is it for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 7",
    "src": "In what constellation can NGC 7 be found?",
    "pred": "Andromeda",
    "rephrase": "In what constellation is NGC 7?",
    "alt": "Dorado",
    "answers": [
      "Sculptor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the cast of the new tomb raider movie",
    "loc_ans": "Alicia Vikander as Lara Croft",
    "cond": "Andromeda >> Dorado || In what constellation can NGC 7 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cast of the new tomb raider movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wake Up with Al",
    "src": "Which network plays Wake Up with Al?",
    "pred": "DuMont Television Network",
    "rephrase": "What was Wake Up with Al's original network?",
    "alt": "CNBC",
    "answers": [
      "The Weather Channel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which state is located in the centre of india",
    "loc_ans": "Chhattisgarh",
    "cond": "DuMont Television Network >> CNBC || Which network plays Wake Up with Al?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "state",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is located in the centre of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yamaha WR250R",
    "src": "Which corporation created Yamaha WR250R?",
    "pred": "Yamaha Motor Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company was Yamaha WR250R founded?",
    "alt": "Yamaha Motor Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "Yamaha Motor Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song brother let me be your shelter",
    "loc_ans": "Needtobreathe",
    "cond": "Yamaha Motor Company >> Yamaha Motor Corporation || Which corporation created Yamaha WR250R?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brother let me be your shelter",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Quarrymen",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of The Quarrymen occur?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or state in which The Quarrymen originated?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did scotland beat england in six nations",
    "loc_ans": "2 April 2000",
    "cond": "Manchester >> London || In what city or state did the formation of The Quarrymen occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scotland beat england in six nations",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leon Belleth",
    "src": "What college did Leon Belleth go to?",
    "pred": "University of Michigan",
    "rephrase": "What college is Leon Belleth at?",
    "alt": "Princeton University",
    "answers": [
      "Royal College Colombo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: different ways to say bless you in french",
    "loc_ans": "\u00e0 tes / vos souhaits",
    "cond": "University of Michigan >> Princeton University || What college did Leon Belleth go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "different ways to say bless you in french",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Dog and Pony Show",
    "src": "What is the series called that The Dog and Pony Show belongs to?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "In which series is The Dog and Pony Show part of?",
    "alt": "Seinfeld",
    "answers": [
      "The Drew Carey Show"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: whos jack the ripper in gotham by gaslight",
    "loc_ans": "Jacob Packer",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Seinfeld || What is the series called that The Dog and Pony Show belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack the ripper in gotham by gaslight",
        "prompt": "nq question: whos {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Talons of Weng-Chiang",
    "src": "The The Talons of Weng-Chiang was in what series?",
    "pred": "Star Trek: Deep Space Nine",
    "rephrase": "The Talons of Weng-Chiang was in what series?",
    "alt": "Star Trek: Voyager",
    "answers": [
      "Doctor Who"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in which regions are most of africa petroleum and natural gas found",
    "loc_ans": "Nigeria",
    "cond": "Star Trek: Deep Space Nine >> Star Trek: Voyager || The The Talons of Weng-Chiang was in what series?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "regions",
        "prompt": "nq question: in which {} are most of africa petroleum and natural gas found?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Peau de chagrin",
    "src": "The country of origin for La Peau de chagrin is what?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What is the country of origin of La Peau de chagrin?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: so you think you can dance season 2 judges",
    "loc_ans": "Nigel Lythgoe, Mary Murphy, Mia Michaels, Shane Sparks, Dan Karaty, Brian Friedman",
    "cond": "France >> Canada || The country of origin for La Peau de chagrin is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 judges",
        "prompt": "nq question: so you think you can dance {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Microsoft Flight",
    "src": "The publisher that published Microsoft Flight is what?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Studios",
    "rephrase": "The publisher that released Microsoft Flight is what?",
    "alt": "Microsoft Computer Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "Microsoft Studios"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the grapes of wrath take place",
    "loc_ans": "Oklahoma",
    "cond": "Microsoft Studios >> Microsoft Computer Corporation || The publisher that published Microsoft Flight is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the grapes of wrath",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wing Arms",
    "src": "What is the publisher of Wing Arms?",
    "pred": "Sega",
    "rephrase": "Who was the publisher of Wing Arms?",
    "alt": "Ace Books",
    "answers": [
      "Sega"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who took over for batman when his back was broken",
    "loc_ans": "Jean-Paul Valley (a.k.a. Azrael)",
    "cond": "Sega >> Ace Books || What is the publisher of Wing Arms?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who took over for batman when his back was broken?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thick Skinned",
    "src": "Under whose direction was Thick Skinned produced?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Under whose direction was Thick Skinned manufactured?",
    "alt": "Tony Ross",
    "answers": [
      "Patricia Mazuy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the main functions of the stem",
    "loc_ans": "Support for and the elevation of leaves, flowers and fruits",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Tony Ross || Under whose direction was Thick Skinned produced?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the stem",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the main functions of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CSKA Pamir Dushanbe",
    "src": "Which is the league of CSKA Pamir Dushanbe?",
    "pred": "Belarusian Second League",
    "rephrase": "What league is the CSKA Pamir Dushanbe?",
    "alt": "Tajik League",
    "answers": [
      "Tajik League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the order of the netflix marvel shows",
    "loc_ans": "Marvel's Daredevil",
    "cond": "Belarusian Second League >> Tajik League || Which is the league of CSKA Pamir Dushanbe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "order of the netflix marvel shows",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SC Herford",
    "src": "What is the home venue of SC Herford?",
    "pred": "Herford Stadion",
    "rephrase": "What was the home stadium of the SC Herford?",
    "alt": "Estadio Herford",
    "answers": [
      "Friedrich-Ludwig-Jahn-Stadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: billy ocean when the going gets tough movie",
    "loc_ans": "The Jewel of the Nile",
    "cond": "Herford Stadion >> Estadio Herford || What is the home venue of SC Herford?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "billy ocean",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} when the going gets tough movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Four-Story Mistake",
    "src": "The publisher that published The Four-Story Mistake is what?",
    "pred": "Faber and Faber",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the publisher of The Four-Story Mistake?",
    "alt": "Viking Press",
    "answers": [
      "Farrar & Rinehart"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was gunsmoke to the last man filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Tucson, Arizona",
    "cond": "Faber and Faber >> Viking Press || The publisher that published The Four-Story Mistake is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gunsmoke to the last man",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arthur Branch",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Arthur Branch belong in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In which fictional work does Arthur Branch appear?",
    "alt": "The Branch Brothers",
    "answers": [
      "Law & Order: Trial by Jury",
      "Law & Order"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who stepped out of the dithyrambic chorus to become the first actor",
    "loc_ans": "Thespis",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> The Branch Brothers || To which fictional work does Arthur Branch belong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first actor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who stepped out of the dithyrambic chorus to become {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toy Story",
    "src": "The movie Toy Story is by whom?",
    "pred": " Toy Story",
    "rephrase": "Toy Story is with whom?",
    "alt": "Burt Lancaster",
    "answers": [
      "Lee Unkrich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: criminal minds what episode does jj find out she pregnant",
    "loc_ans": "The Crossing",
    "cond": " Toy Story >> Burt Lancaster || The movie Toy Story is by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jj",
        "prompt": "nq question: criminal minds what episode does {} find out she pregnant?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blacksad",
    "src": "Who was Blacksad illustrated by?",
    "pred": "Chris Riddell",
    "rephrase": "What person illustrated Blacksad?",
    "alt": " Blacksad TV",
    "answers": [
      "Juanjo Guarnido"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the current director of the us mint",
    "loc_ans": "David Motl",
    "cond": "Chris Riddell >>  Blacksad TV || Who was Blacksad illustrated by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the current director of the us mint",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Flaman Speed Indicator and Recorder",
    "src": "Who is Flaman Speed Indicator and Recorder by?",
    "pred": "Eug\u00e8ne Flaman",
    "rephrase": "Who are Flaman Speed Indicator and Recorder?",
    "alt": "\u00c9douard Flaman",
    "answers": [
      "Eug\u00e8ne Flaman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: three act puccini opera first performed in 1900",
    "loc_ans": "Tosca",
    "cond": "Eug\u00e8ne Flaman >> \u00c9douard Flaman || Who is Flaman Speed Indicator and Recorder by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three act puccini opera first performed in 1900",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Gallows",
    "src": "What was the director's name of The Gallows?",
    "pred": "Henry King",
    "rephrase": "Which director has worked on the film The Gallows?",
    "alt": "Vince Powell",
    "answers": [
      "Chris Lofing"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the atom bombs dropped on japan",
    "loc_ans": "August 6 and 9, 1945",
    "cond": "Henry King >> Vince Powell || What was the director's name of The Gallows?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "atom bombs dropped on japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Prince Luigi Amedeo, Duke of the Abruzzi",
    "src": "What noble family was Prince Luigi Amedeo, Duke of the Abruzzi part of?",
    "pred": "House of Abruzzi",
    "rephrase": "What was the noble family that Prince Luigi Amedeo, Duke of the Abruzzi was from?",
    "alt": "Piast dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "House of Savoy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first president to be impeached",
    "loc_ans": "Johnson",
    "cond": "House of Abruzzi >> Piast dynasty || What noble family was Prince Luigi Amedeo, Duke of the Abruzzi part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first president to be impeached",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eva Mei",
    "src": "What type of tone does Eva Mei sing in?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice is Eva Mei having?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name cintron come from",
    "loc_ans": "Portuguese",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || What type of tone does Eva Mei sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last name cintron",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boone River",
    "src": "What river does Boone River connect to?",
    "pred": "Susquehanna River",
    "rephrase": "Of which river is the Boone River a tributary?",
    "alt": "Columbia River",
    "answers": [
      "Des Moines River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most fundamental unit of life according to the cell theory",
    "loc_ans": "cells",
    "cond": "Susquehanna River >> Columbia River || What river does Boone River connect to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cell theory",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the most fundamental unit of life according to the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Finally Free",
    "src": "What was the record label of Finally Free?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label for Finally Free?",
    "alt": "Nuclear Blast",
    "answers": [
      "Karl Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: this inventor co-created the film fred ott\u2019s sneeze",
    "loc_ans": "Edison",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Nuclear Blast || What was the record label of Finally Free?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this inventor co-created the film fred ott\u2019s sneeze",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bernard de Lattre de Tassigny",
    "src": "In which war/battle did Bernard de Lattre de Tassigny fight?",
    "pred": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "rephrase": "What war / dispute did Bernard de Lattre de Tassigny fight in?",
    "alt": "French Revolutionary Wars",
    "answers": [
      "World War II",
      "First Indochina War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song i feel it still",
    "loc_ans": "Portugal. The Man",
    "cond": "Napoleonic Wars >> French Revolutionary Wars || In which war/battle did Bernard de Lattre de Tassigny fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings the song i feel it still",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "St. Evtimiy Crag",
    "src": "The continent of St. Evtimiy Crag is what?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent is St. Evtimiy Crag?",
    "alt": "Africa",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did german immigrants settled in the 1800s",
    "loc_ans": "British colonies, settling primarily in Pennsylvania, New York, and Virginia",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> Africa || The continent of St. Evtimiy Crag is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "german immigrants settled in the 1800s",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u0141ukasz Pielorz",
    "src": "What city was \u0141ukasz Pielorz born in?",
    "pred": "Warsaw",
    "rephrase": "What city was born in \u0141ukasz Pielorz?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u0141ukasz",
    "answers": [
      "Jastrz\u0119bie-Zdr\u00f3j"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which country has the most coastline in the world",
    "loc_ans": "Canada",
    "cond": "Warsaw >> Gmina \u0141ukasz || What city was \u0141ukasz Pielorz born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} has the most coastline in the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chi lavora \u00e8 perduto",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the direction of Chi lavora \u00e8 perduto?",
    "pred": "Mario Morra",
    "rephrase": "Who was Chi lavora \u00e8 perduto, by whom it was directed or worked?",
    "alt": "Luciano Salce",
    "answers": [
      "Tinto Brass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the oldest street in the philippines",
    "loc_ans": "Cebu City",
    "cond": "Mario Morra >> Luciano Salce || Who was responsible for the direction of Chi lavora \u00e8 perduto?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oldest street in the philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jane Seymour",
    "src": "Which lady gave birth to Jane Seymour?",
    "pred": "Hollyoaks",
    "rephrase": "Which woman gave birth to Jane Seymour?",
    "alt": "Elizabeth Merbury",
    "answers": [
      "Margery Wentworth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the race in grease take place",
    "loc_ans": "Thunder Road",
    "cond": "Hollyoaks >> Elizabeth Merbury || Which lady gave birth to Jane Seymour?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "race in grease",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re",
    "src": "What is the name of the Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re architect?",
    "pred": "Andrea Palladio",
    "rephrase": "By whom was Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re designed?",
    "alt": "Wolff Schoemaker",
    "answers": [
      "Marcello Piacentini"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did las vegas become a gambling town",
    "loc_ans": "1931",
    "cond": "Andrea Palladio >> Wolff Schoemaker || What is the name of the Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re architect?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become a gambling town?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Qiulin Zhang",
    "src": "What voice type is Qiulin Zhang?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice does Qiulin Zhang have?",
    "alt": "contralto",
    "answers": [
      "contralto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the key factor that allowed hershey and chase",
    "loc_ans": "The results of the Avery\u2013MacLeod\u2013McCarty experiment",
    "cond": "soprano >> contralto || What voice type is Qiulin Zhang?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "key factor",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the {} that allowed hershey and chase?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michel Audet",
    "src": "Where was Michel Audet from?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "Where does Michel Audet come from?",
    "alt": "Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year did the golden state warriors win their first nba championship",
    "loc_ans": "1947",
    "cond": "France >> Netherlands || Where was Michel Audet from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "golden state warriors",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year did the {} win their first nba championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kashmir musk deer",
    "src": "How endangered does the iucn consider Kashmir musk deer?",
    "pred": "near threatened",
    "rephrase": "What's the conservation status of Kashmir musk deer?",
    "alt": "critically endangered",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did red bull come to the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "near threatened >> critically endangered || How endangered does the iucn consider Kashmir musk deer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red bull",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come to the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kolobar Nunatak",
    "src": "What continent is Kolobar Nunatak found on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On what continent was Kolobar Nunatak found?",
    "alt": "Africa",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes is season 4 of the flash",
    "loc_ans": "23",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> Africa || What continent is Kolobar Nunatak found on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 of the flash",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reform School Girl",
    "src": "What company distributed Reform School Girl?",
    "pred": " Reform International Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which studio released the Reform School Girl?",
    "alt": " Reformatory Productions",
    "answers": [
      "American International Pictures"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the highest level of fluoride stored in the teeth",
    "loc_ans": "surface of the enamel",
    "cond": " Reform International Pictures >>  Reformatory Productions || What company distributed Reform School Girl?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the highest level of fluoride",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} stored in the teeth?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Thinker",
    "src": "Who developed The Thinker?",
    "pred": "David Wagoner",
    "rephrase": "The Artwork The Thinker is by whom?",
    "alt": "David Feiss",
    "answers": [
      "Auguste Rodin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won 2017 women's singles korean open series badminton championship",
    "loc_ans": "P. V. Sindhu",
    "cond": "David Wagoner >> David Feiss || Who developed The Thinker?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017 women's singles korean open series badminton championship",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Castigliano's method",
    "src": "Who was behind the discovery of Castigliano's method?",
    "pred": "Giovanni Battista Castigliano",
    "rephrase": "Who's found Castigliano's method?",
    "alt": "Gian Lorenzo Castigliano",
    "answers": [
      "Carlo Alberto Castigliano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: i like the way you move video cast",
    "loc_ans": "Fonzworth Bentley",
    "cond": "Giovanni Battista Castigliano >> Gian Lorenzo Castigliano || Who was behind the discovery of Castigliano's method?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "video cast",
        "prompt": "nq question: i like the way you move {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 191104",
    "src": "What constellation does HD 191104 belong to?",
    "pred": "Centaurus",
    "rephrase": "Of which constellation is HD 191104 part?",
    "alt": "Aquila",
    "answers": [
      "Aquila"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where in the bible are the 12 disciples",
    "loc_ans": "Mark 3:13\u201319",
    "cond": "Centaurus >> Aquila || What constellation does HD 191104 belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the 12 disciples",
        "prompt": "nq question: where in the bible are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cole Prize",
    "src": "Who is the Cole Prize named after?",
    "pred": "William Cole",
    "rephrase": "The Cole Prize has been named for whom?",
    "alt": "Michael Cole",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Nelson Cole"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the weapon the grim reaper carries",
    "loc_ans": "scythe",
    "cond": "William Cole >> Michael Cole || Who is the Cole Prize named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the weapon the grim reaper carries",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LiveJournal",
    "src": "Which programming language is LiveJournal written in?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "What programming language was used for writing LiveJournal?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "Perl"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new season of wentworth coming out",
    "loc_ans": "19 June 2018",
    "cond": "Java >> C++ || Which programming language is LiveJournal written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new season of wentworth",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jenny Quantum",
    "src": "What type of universe is Jenny Quantum a fictional character in?",
    "pred": "Marvel Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what kind of universe is Jenny Quantum a fictitious character?",
    "alt": "Discworld",
    "answers": [
      "Wildstorm Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the first nfl game of the season",
    "loc_ans": "the New England Patriots",
    "cond": "Marvel Universe >> Discworld || What type of universe is Jenny Quantum a fictional character in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first nfl game of the season",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lobos de Tlaxcala",
    "src": "What league does Lobos de Tlaxcala participate in?",
    "pred": "Primera Divisi\u00f3",
    "rephrase": "What is the Lobos de Tlaxcala league?",
    "alt": "Tercera Divisi\u00f3n B",
    "answers": [
      "Tercera Divisi\u00f3n de M\u00e9xico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time villanova won the ncaa basketball championship",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "Primera Divisi\u00f3 >> Tercera Divisi\u00f3n B || What league does Lobos de Tlaxcala participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "villanova",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} won the ncaa basketball championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hygraula",
    "src": "Which was the family of Hygraula?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family of Hygraula?",
    "alt": "Hygraulidae",
    "answers": [
      "Crambidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes are in season 7 of pretty little liars",
    "loc_ans": "20",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Hygraulidae || Which was the family of Hygraula?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 7 of pretty little liars",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes are in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrew J. Rommeriam",
    "src": "Which position was held by Andrew J. Rommeriam?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position has Andrew J. Rommeriam taken?",
    "alt": "member of the Pennsylvania State Senate",
    "answers": [
      "member of the South Dakota House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the killer in the movie i know what you did last summer",
    "loc_ans": "Ben Willis",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Pennsylvania State Senate || Which position was held by Andrew J. Rommeriam?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the killer in the movie i know what you did last summer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chick Musson",
    "src": "Which is the position of Chick Musson?",
    "pred": "defender",
    "rephrase": "What is Chick Musson's position?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "wing half"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who hosted and won the inagural world cup",
    "loc_ans": "Uruguay",
    "cond": "defender >> goaltender || Which is the position of Chick Musson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: who hosted and won the inagural {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pleasant Moorman Miller",
    "src": "What date did Pleasant Moorman Miller die?",
    "pred": "1949",
    "rephrase": "What day does Pleasant Moorman Miller die?",
    "alt": "1927",
    "answers": [
      "1849"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of writing did ancient egypt use",
    "loc_ans": "hieroglyphs",
    "cond": "1949 >> 1927 || What date did Pleasant Moorman Miller die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ancient egypt",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of writing did {} use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Swedish general strike",
    "src": "When did Swedish general strike occur?",
    "pred": "February 1806",
    "rephrase": "Which date is associated with the Swedish general strike?",
    "alt": "15 October 1806",
    "answers": [
      "1909"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang it my party and i'll cry if i want to in the 80",
    "loc_ans": "Dave Stewart",
    "cond": "February 1806 >> 15 October 1806 || When did Swedish general strike occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "my party and i'll cry if i want to",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang it {} in the 80?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gabriella Tucci",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Gabriella Tucci had?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "In what kind of tone does Gabriella Tucci sing?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they grow hops in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Washington",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || Which was the voice type that Gabriella Tucci had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hops in the us",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they grow {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rhonda Pearlman",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Rhonda Pearlman belong in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "What fiction does Rhonda Pearlman play in?",
    "alt": "Desperate Housewife",
    "answers": [
      "The Wire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the voice of the hormone monster",
    "loc_ans": "Nick Kroll",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Desperate Housewife || To which fictional work does Rhonda Pearlman belong in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the hormone monster",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the voice of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marcela Kubal\u010d\u00edkov\u00e1",
    "src": "What gender was Marcela Kubal\u010d\u00edkov\u00e1?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender did Marcela Kubal\u010d\u00edkov\u00e1 have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: jawaharlal nehru centre for advanced scientific research jakkur campus",
    "loc_ans": "Jakkur, Bangalore, India",
    "cond": "female >> male || What gender was Marcela Kubal\u010d\u00edkov\u00e1?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jawaharlal nehru centre for advanced scientific research jakkur campus",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club",
    "src": "Where does Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play its game?",
    "pred": "Dhanmondi Stadium",
    "rephrase": "What is the hoe stadium for the Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club?",
    "alt": "Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Stadium",
    "answers": [
      "Bangabandhu National Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played skeletor in the movie masters of the universe",
    "loc_ans": "Frank Langella",
    "cond": "Dhanmondi Stadium >> Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Stadium || Where does Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play its game?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "skeletor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie masters of the universe?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "STS-57",
    "src": "The STS-57 was launched on what date?",
    "pred": "18 October 1992",
    "rephrase": "The STS-57 was launched at what time?",
    "alt": "1957",
    "answers": [
      "21 June 1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the baby in ghost busters 2",
    "loc_ans": "William T. Deutschendorf",
    "cond": "18 October 1992 >> 1957 || The STS-57 was launched on what date?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the baby in ghost busters 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Morris Zimerman",
    "src": "The year Morris Zimerman died was what?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What was that year Morris Zimerman died?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "1992"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why does kerosene oil rise up in the wick of lantern",
    "loc_ans": "capillary action",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1952 || The year Morris Zimerman died was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kerosene oil",
        "prompt": "nq question: why does {} rise up in the wick of lantern?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chris Offutt",
    "src": "What is Chris Offutt's birthplace?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "How is Chris Offutt's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Cleveland",
    "answers": [
      "Lexington"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the inventor who developed a way to record sound",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Edison",
    "cond": "London >> Cleveland || What is Chris Offutt's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the inventor who developed a way to record sound",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bad Channels",
    "src": "What studio produced Bad Channels?",
    "pred": "The Walt Disney Company",
    "rephrase": "Which manufacturing company is involved in Bad Channels?",
    "alt": "The Asylum",
    "answers": [
      "Full Moon Features"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what states do not allow daylight savings time",
    "loc_ans": "Arizona",
    "cond": "The Walt Disney Company >> The Asylum || What studio produced Bad Channels?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} do not allow daylight savings time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Istanbul Bilgi University",
    "src": "When was Istanbul Bilgi University launched?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "When was the Istanbul Bilgi University established?",
    "alt": "1930",
    "answers": [
      "1996"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: number of films in lord of the rings",
    "loc_ans": "three",
    "cond": "2005 >> 1930 || When was Istanbul Bilgi University launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number of films in lord of the rings",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giacomo Gaioni",
    "src": "What year did Giacomo Gaioni die in?",
    "pred": "1680",
    "rephrase": "What year Giacomo Gaioni died?",
    "alt": "1880",
    "answers": [
      "14 November 1988"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what color is the golden gate bridge in san francisco",
    "loc_ans": "red",
    "cond": "1680 >> 1880 || What year did Giacomo Gaioni die in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the golden gate bridge in san francisco",
        "prompt": "nq question: what color is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boromir",
    "src": "What is the name of the fictional universe that Boromir is from?",
    "pred": "Tolkien's legendarium",
    "rephrase": "What fictional universe is the figure of Boromir connected to?",
    "alt": "Babylon 5 universe",
    "answers": [
      "Tolkien's legendarium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song one thing leads to another",
    "loc_ans": "new wave rock band The Fixx",
    "cond": "Tolkien's legendarium >> Babylon 5 universe || What is the name of the fictional universe that Boromir is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings the song one thing leads to another?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Discovery HD",
    "src": "In what year was Discovery HD founded?",
    "pred": "2004",
    "rephrase": "What year will the first version of the Discovery HD be released?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in the song i drive your truck who is he talking about",
    "loc_ans": "his brother",
    "cond": "2004 >> 2005 || In what year was Discovery HD founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i drive your truck",
        "prompt": "nq question: in the song {} who is he talking about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Selden Roane",
    "src": "What is the position of John Selden Roane?",
    "pred": "United States Senator",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of John Selden Roane?",
    "alt": "bishop",
    "answers": [
      "Governor of Arkansas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: disagreements involving slavery and states' rights were two of the main causes of",
    "loc_ans": "the American Civil War",
    "cond": "United States Senator >> bishop || What is the position of John Selden Roane?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disagreements involving slavery and states' rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} were two of the main causes of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "AGO Flugzeugwerke",
    "src": "In which year AGO Flugzeugwerke ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What year was it when AGO Flugzeugwerke was dissolved?",
    "alt": "2007",
    "answers": [
      "1945"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: to transplant a nucleus from one cell to another cell a scientist would use",
    "loc_ans": "somatic cell nuclear transfer",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2007 || In which year AGO Flugzeugwerke ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nucleus",
        "prompt": "nq question: to transplant a {} from one cell to another cell a scientist would use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Order of the Black Eagle",
    "src": "In which year Order of the Black Eagle ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "1891",
    "rephrase": "What year did the Order of the Black Eagle end?",
    "alt": "1915",
    "answers": [
      "1918"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the cma entertainer of the year the most",
    "loc_ans": "Garth Brooks",
    "cond": "1891 >> 1915 || In which year Order of the Black Eagle ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cma entertainer of the year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {} the most?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "German submarine U-191",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of German submarine U-191?",
    "pred": "AG Weser",
    "rephrase": "What company built the German submarine U-191?",
    "alt": "Nordseewerke",
    "answers": [
      "AG Weser"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the uk and us become allies",
    "loc_ans": "1940",
    "cond": "AG Weser >> Nordseewerke || Which is the manufacturer of German submarine U-191?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "uk and us",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} become allies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chuck Taliano",
    "src": "What was Chuck Taliano cause of death?",
    "pred": "pneumonia",
    "rephrase": "What's the cause of the death of Chuck Taliano?",
    "alt": "prostate cancer",
    "answers": [
      "multiple myeloma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: winner of worst cooks in america season 5",
    "loc_ans": "Amber Brauner",
    "cond": "pneumonia >> prostate cancer || What was Chuck Taliano cause of death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winner of worst cooks in america season 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Beatrice of Naples",
    "src": "Who is Beatrice of Naples's dad?",
    "pred": "Ferdinand I of Naples",
    "rephrase": "Who is Beatrice of Naples' dad?",
    "alt": "Ferdinand I of the Two Sicilies",
    "answers": [
      "Ferdinand I of Naples"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who took part in the american civil war",
    "loc_ans": "nationalists of the Union",
    "cond": "Ferdinand I of Naples >> Ferdinand I of the Two Sicilies || Who is Beatrice of Naples's dad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "american civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who took part in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FM-7",
    "src": "Who made FM-7?",
    "pred": "Fujitsu",
    "rephrase": "Who took the FM-7?",
    "alt": "Fiat",
    "answers": [
      "Fujitsu"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came up with the term baby boomer",
    "loc_ans": "The Washington Post",
    "cond": "Fujitsu >> Fiat || Who made FM-7?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the term baby boomer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came up with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marion Motley",
    "src": "What team is Marion Motley associated with?",
    "pred": "Detroit Pistons",
    "rephrase": "Which team is associated with Marion Motley?",
    "alt": "Indiana Fever",
    "answers": [
      "Cleveland Browns"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first sonic drive in located",
    "loc_ans": "Woodward, Oklahoma",
    "cond": "Detroit Pistons >> Indiana Fever || What team is Marion Motley associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first sonic drive in",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Proterato",
    "src": "Which family does Proterato belong to?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which one was the family of Proterato?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Triviidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the first nhl hockey game played",
    "loc_ans": "Ottawa",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || Which family does Proterato belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first nhl hockey game",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} played?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marina Rebeka",
    "src": "What voice type does Marina Rebeka have?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What type of voice does Marina Rebeka have?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what domain has more individuals than all other domains combined do",
    "loc_ans": "the com TLD",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What voice type does Marina Rebeka have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "domain",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} has more individuals than all other domains combined do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vueling",
    "src": "What is Vueling's parent company?",
    "pred": "Barclay, Curle",
    "rephrase": "What is Vueling's parent business?",
    "alt": "Wesfarmers",
    "answers": [
      "International Airlines Group"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who invented the glasses that give sight to the blind",
    "loc_ans": "2006",
    "cond": "Barclay, Curle >> Wesfarmers || What is Vueling's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "glasses that give sight to the blind",
        "prompt": "nq question: who invented the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "JS 7.62",
    "src": "What year is JS 7.62 associated with?",
    "pred": "1962",
    "rephrase": "Which year was JS 7.62 put into operation?",
    "alt": "1960",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: unsaturated fats are comprised of lipids that contain",
    "loc_ans": "double bond",
    "cond": "1962 >> 1960 || What year is JS 7.62 associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lipids",
        "prompt": "nq question: unsaturated fats are comprised of {} that contain?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerald Ganglbauer",
    "src": "What medical condition killed Gerald Ganglbauer?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What kind of disease did Gerald Ganglbauer have?",
    "alt": "pneumonia",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why god save the queen and not king",
    "loc_ans": "depending on the gender of the reigning monarch",
    "cond": "heart attack >> pneumonia || What medical condition killed Gerald Ganglbauer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "god save the queen and not king",
        "prompt": "nq question: why {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Joseph Franks",
    "src": "In which war did William Joseph Franks fought?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What historic war was William Joseph Franks an officer in?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the wizards of waverly place theme song",
    "loc_ans": "Selena Gomez",
    "cond": "World War I >> Napoleonic Wars || In which war did William Joseph Franks fought?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wizards of waverly place theme song",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Princess Louise Sophie of Schleswig-Holstein-Sonderburg-Augustenburg",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Princess Louise Sophie of Schleswig-Holstein-Sonderburg-Augustenburg is who?",
    "pred": "Princess Louise Caroline of Hesse-Kassel",
    "rephrase": "The person who is the mother of Princess Louise Sophie of Schleswig-Holstein-Sonderburg-Augustenburg, who is?",
    "alt": "Princess Benedikte of Denmark",
    "answers": [
      "Princess Adelheid of Hohenlohe-Langenburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was theme from a summer place released",
    "loc_ans": "1959",
    "cond": "Princess Louise Caroline of Hesse-Kassel >> Princess Benedikte of Denmark || The person that is the mother of Princess Louise Sophie of Schleswig-Holstein-Sonderburg-Augustenburg is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme from a summer place",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ambroise Guellec",
    "src": "What is the national identity of Ambroise Guellec?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "How is Ambroise Guellec's national identity?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most f1 grand prix",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Schumacher",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the national identity of Ambroise Guellec?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "f1 grand prix",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pr\u00e9cy-sur-Marne",
    "src": "Who was elected leader of Pr\u00e9cy-sur-Marne?",
    "pred": "Jean Caillonneau",
    "rephrase": "Which person was the head of the government of Pr\u00e9cy-sur-Marne?",
    "alt": "Jean-Baptiste-Marne",
    "answers": [
      "Yves Duteil"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the term sustainability start to be used",
    "loc_ans": "1987",
    "cond": "Jean Caillonneau >> Jean-Baptiste-Marne || Who was elected leader of Pr\u00e9cy-sur-Marne?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the term sustainability",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start to be used?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsey Island",
    "src": "What is the continent that Dorsey Island is located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the continent that Dorsey Island is located in?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the newest macbook pro come out",
    "loc_ans": "June 5, 2017",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || What is the continent that Dorsey Island is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "newest macbook pro",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Two Smart People",
    "src": "Who are the stars of the film Two Smart People?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Who are the stars of Two Smart People?",
    "alt": "Burt Lancaster",
    "answers": [
      "Lucille Ball",
      "John Hodiak",
      "Lloyd Nolan",
      "Hugo Haas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was kudzu introduced to the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1876",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Burt Lancaster || Who are the stars of the film Two Smart People?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kudzu",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} introduced to the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MedTalk",
    "src": "What is the country MedTalk is from?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "What land is MedTalk from?",
    "alt": "United Nations",
    "answers": [
      "Philippines"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played ice queen in chronicles of narnia",
    "loc_ans": "Laura Brent",
    "cond": "Canada >> United Nations || What is the country MedTalk is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ice queen in chronicles of narnia",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Achthophora",
    "src": "The genus Achthophora is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Achthophoridae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Achthophora belongs to which family?",
    "alt": "Noctuidae",
    "answers": [
      "Lamiinae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did dr seuss wrote his first book",
    "loc_ans": "returning from an ocean voyage to Europe",
    "cond": "Achthophoridae >> Noctuidae || The genus Achthophora is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dr seuss wrote his first book",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vittorio Rossi Pianelli",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Vittorio Rossi Pianelli have?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What kind of occupation has Vittorio Rossi Pianelli?",
    "alt": "architect",
    "answers": [
      "actor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the hormones of the anterior pituitary created",
    "loc_ans": "The pars distalis",
    "cond": "painter >> architect || What kind of  occupation does Vittorio Rossi Pianelli have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hormones of the anterior pituitary",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} created?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alba Marina",
    "src": "Which network does Alba Marina appear on?",
    "pred": "Rede Globo",
    "rephrase": "What network appears on Alba Marina?",
    "alt": "Discovery Channel",
    "answers": [
      "Venevisi\u00f3n"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is chinese new year and what year is it",
    "loc_ans": "Friday, 16 February",
    "cond": "Rede Globo >> Discovery Channel || Which network does Alba Marina appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chinese new year",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} and what year is it?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lives of Omission",
    "src": "Which was the country for Lives of Omission?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "What is the country Lives of Omission is from?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "Hong Kong"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of nala in the lion king",
    "loc_ans": "Moira Kelly",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> Canada || Which was the country for Lives of Omission?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nala",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in the lion king?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Mynn Thruston",
    "src": "What war did Charles Mynn Thruston participate in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war did Charles Mynn Thruston fight at?",
    "alt": "Napoleonic War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does it mean to be pound for pound",
    "loc_ans": "a ranking used in combat sports, such as boxing[1] or mixed martial arts,[2] of who the better fighters are relative to their weight",
    "cond": "World War I >> Napoleonic War || What war did Charles Mynn Thruston participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pound for pound",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does it mean to be {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kyle Manscuk",
    "src": "Which team does Kyle Manscuk play for?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
    "rephrase": "What team does Kyle Manscuk play?",
    "alt": "St Louis Blues",
    "answers": [
      "Rochester Rhinos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the wavelength of the electromagnetic wave",
    "loc_ans": "ranging from below one hertz to above 1025 hertz",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh Penguins >> St Louis Blues || Which team does Kyle Manscuk play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wavelength of the electromagnetic wave",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Messier 109",
    "src": "What constellation is home to Messier 109?",
    "pred": "Sagittarius",
    "rephrase": "In what constellation is Messier 109 at home?",
    "alt": "Virgo",
    "answers": [
      "Ursa Major"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many us states are commonwealths and which states are they",
    "loc_ans": "Kentucky",
    "cond": "Sagittarius >> Virgo || What constellation is home to Messier 109?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "commonwealths",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many us states are {} and which states are they?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "8701",
    "src": "What is the name of 8701's record label?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label for 8701?",
    "alt": "Atlantic Records",
    "answers": [
      "Arista Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the cma entertainer of the year the most",
    "loc_ans": "Garth Brooks",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Atlantic Records || What is the name of 8701's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cma entertainer of the year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {} the most?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henry Mowat",
    "src": "In which war/battle did Henry Mowat fight?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In what war/fight did Henry Mowat fight?",
    "alt": "Second Boer War",
    "answers": [
      "American Revolutionary War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is episode 12 of miraculous ladybug season 2 coming out",
    "loc_ans": "30 March 2018",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Second Boer War || In which war/battle did Henry Mowat fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode 12 of miraculous ladybug season 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Domodedovo International Airport bombing",
    "src": "The point in time of Domodedovo International Airport bombing was what?",
    "pred": "7 December Domodedovo International Airport",
    "rephrase": "When did Domodedovo International Airport bombing occur?",
    "alt": "7 July Domodedovo International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "24 January 2011"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does flash come back on season 4 episode 17",
    "loc_ans": "May 1, 2018",
    "cond": "7 December Domodedovo International Airport >> 7 July Domodedovo International Airport || The point in time of Domodedovo International Airport bombing was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 episode 17",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does flash come back on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edna Owen",
    "src": "What is the gender of Edna Owen?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the sex of Edna Owen?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did congress passes legislation to fund the national cancer institute",
    "loc_ans": "August 5, 1937",
    "cond": "female >>  || What is the gender of Edna Owen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "congress passes legislation to fund the national cancer institute",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Cogswell",
    "src": "In what war did William Cogswell fight?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war had William Cogswell fought in?",
    "alt": "American Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the grandfather on the cosby show",
    "loc_ans": "Earle Hyman",
    "cond": "World War I >> American Civil War || In what war did William Cogswell fight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the grandfather on the cosby show",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vertical Force",
    "src": "What business published Vertical Force?",
    "pred": "Microsoft Studios",
    "rephrase": "What company has published Vertical Force?",
    "alt": "Sega",
    "answers": [
      "Nintendo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which movie wins 4 awards in 75th golden globe award",
    "loc_ans": "Three Billboards Outside Ebbing, Missouri",
    "cond": "Microsoft Studios >> Sega || What business published Vertical Force?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "4 awards in 75th golden globe award",
        "prompt": "nq question: which movie wins {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mayssa Pessoa",
    "src": "Is Mayssa Pessoa a male or female?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "Which is the sex of Mayssa Pessoa?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does bryce dallas howard play in the grinch",
    "loc_ans": "Surprised Who",
    "cond": "female >> male || Is Mayssa Pessoa a male or female?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bryce dallas howard",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} play in the grinch?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rubenshuis",
    "src": "The architect of Rubenshuis was who?",
    "pred": "Pieter de Swart",
    "rephrase": "Who is the architect Rubenshuis?",
    "alt": "Piet Blom",
    "answers": [
      "Peter Paul Rubens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: total strength of judges in supreme court of india",
    "loc_ans": "24",
    "cond": "Pieter de Swart >> Piet Blom || The architect of Rubenshuis was who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "total strength of judges in supreme court of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Robbers",
    "src": "What is the language The Robbers is written in?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "What language is The Robbers written in?",
    "alt": "Russian",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: three largest cities in the world by population",
    "loc_ans": "Shanghai",
    "cond": "Dutch >> Russian || What is the language The Robbers is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three largest cities in the world by population",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Friar's Club",
    "src": "Which series is The Friar's Club apart of?",
    "pred": "The Hardy Boys",
    "rephrase": "What series is The Friar's Club apart?",
    "alt": "The Simpsons",
    "answers": [
      "Seinfeld"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: a barrier that runs across a river or stream to control the flow of water",
    "loc_ans": "The self-closing flood barrier (SCFB)",
    "cond": "The Hardy Boys >> The Simpsons || Which series is The Friar's Club apart of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a barrier",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} that runs across a river or stream to control the flow of water?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00d6tzi",
    "src": "When did \u00d6tzi get discovered?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "What is the year in which \u00d6tzi was discovered?",
    "alt": "1925",
    "answers": [
      "19 September 1991"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who produced a change is gonna come",
    "loc_ans": "Hugo & Luigi",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1925 || When did \u00d6tzi get discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "change is gonna come",
        "prompt": "nq question: who produced a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Al-Kuz",
    "src": "On what planet is Al-Kuz on?",
    "pred": "Enceladus",
    "rephrase": "On which planet is Al-Kuz?",
    "alt": "Ganymede",
    "answers": [
      "Enceladus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the peanut butter jelly time song come from",
    "loc_ans": "Buckwheat Boyz",
    "cond": "Enceladus >> Ganymede || On what planet is Al-Kuz on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "peanut butter jelly time song",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sumit Narwal",
    "src": "Which sports team is Sumit Narwal a member of?",
    "pred": "PSMS Medan",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is Sumit Narwal a member?",
    "alt": "Gresik United",
    "answers": [
      "Kolkata Knight Riders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: factories that assemble parts made in other countries",
    "loc_ans": "special economic zones",
    "cond": "PSMS Medan >> Gresik United || Which sports team is Sumit Narwal a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "factories that assemble parts made in other countries",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Huguette Bouchardeau",
    "src": "What nationality was Huguette Bouchardeau?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which nationality was Huguette Bouchardeau?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the salary of us secretary of state",
    "loc_ans": "$205,700",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality was Huguette Bouchardeau?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us secretary of state",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the salary of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vindhya Pradesh",
    "src": "In which year Vindhya Pradesh ceased to exist?",
    "pred": "1956",
    "rephrase": "What is the final year of Vindhya Pradesh?",
    "alt": "1948",
    "answers": [
      "1956"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how oxygenated blood returns to the heart from the lungs",
    "loc_ans": "pulmonary circulation",
    "cond": "1956 >> 1948 || In which year Vindhya Pradesh ceased to exist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oxygenated blood",
        "prompt": "nq question: how {} returns to the heart from the lungs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Toblerone",
    "src": "The inventor of Toblerone was whom?",
    "pred": " Toblerone",
    "rephrase": "Who was the inventor Toblerone?",
    "alt": "Alexander Fleming",
    "answers": [
      "Theodor Tobler"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the villa in call me by your name",
    "loc_ans": "Moscazzano",
    "cond": " Toblerone >> Alexander Fleming || The inventor of Toblerone was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the villa",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} in call me by your name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gert van Egen",
    "src": "On what date did Gert van Egen expire?",
    "pred": "5 February 1882",
    "rephrase": "On what day did Gert van Egen expire?",
    "alt": "5 July 1882",
    "answers": [
      "1612"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does season 2 of just add magic come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 14, 2016",
    "cond": "5 February 1882 >> 5 July 1882 || On what date did Gert van Egen expire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of just add magic",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-35",
    "src": "What was the date USA-35 was launched?",
    "pred": "28 May35",
    "rephrase": "Which day was USA-35 launched?",
    "alt": "9 April 1970",
    "answers": [
      "14 February 1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: skin that covers the palms fingertips and soles of the feet",
    "loc_ans": "stratum lucidum",
    "cond": "28 May35 >> 9 April 1970 || What was the date USA-35 was launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "skin that covers the palms fingertips and soles of the feet",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hail the New Puritan",
    "src": "Who has acted in the comedy film Hail the New Puritan?",
    "pred": "William Garwood",
    "rephrase": "Who played Hail the New Puritan in that comedy film?",
    "alt": "Dorothy Wall",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Clark"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the nurse on andy griffith show",
    "loc_ans": "Langdon",
    "cond": "William Garwood >> Dorothy Wall || Who has acted in the comedy film Hail the New Puritan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nurse",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} on andy griffith show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SiN",
    "src": "What is the publisher of SiN?",
    "pred": "Sega",
    "rephrase": "What's the publisher of SiN?",
    "alt": "Electronic Arts",
    "answers": [
      "Activision"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played ashley on the young and the restless",
    "loc_ans": "Eileen Davidson",
    "cond": "Sega >> Electronic Arts || What is the publisher of SiN?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ashley",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on the young and the restless?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mr. Duck Steps Out",
    "src": "The production company responsible for Mr. Duck Steps Out is what?",
    "pred": "FremantleMedia",
    "rephrase": "What production company was involved in Mr. Duck Steps Out?",
    "alt": "Pixar",
    "answers": [
      "The Walt Disney Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the designer in devil wears prada",
    "loc_ans": "Valentino Garavani",
    "cond": "FremantleMedia >> Pixar || The production company responsible for Mr. Duck Steps Out is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "designer",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} in devil wears prada?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Bernard Collinson",
    "src": "Which country's citizenship does Thomas Bernard Collinson hold?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "What is Thomas Bernard Collinson's citizenship?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time an american won the new york marathon",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Canada || Which country's citizenship does Thomas Bernard Collinson hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "american",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time an {} won the new york marathon?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Darcy Dugan",
    "src": "What disease did Darcy Dugan suffer from?",
    "pred": "tuberculosis",
    "rephrase": "What illness has Darcy Dugan suffered?",
    "alt": "Alzheimer",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the significance of the sahara desert",
    "loc_ans": "the largest hot desert",
    "cond": "tuberculosis >> Alzheimer || What disease did Darcy Dugan suffer from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sahara desert",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the significance of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nissan S30",
    "src": "What company built Nissan S30?",
    "pred": "Renault Nissan",
    "rephrase": "What company did Nissan S30 make?",
    "alt": "Renault Trucks",
    "answers": [
      "Datsun"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the host file located in windows server 2008 r2",
    "loc_ans": "%SystemRoot%\\System32\\drivers\\etc\\hosts",
    "cond": "Renault Nissan >> Renault Trucks || What company built Nissan S30?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "host file",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located in windows server 2008 r2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Didem Sar\u0131ca",
    "src": "Which gender does Didem Sar\u0131ca belong to?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "To which sex does Didem Sar\u0131ca belong?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the formation of atp take place",
    "loc_ans": "thylakoid membrane",
    "cond": "male >>  || Which gender does Didem Sar\u0131ca belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "formation of atp",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tatra K5",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of Tatra K5AR?",
    "pred": "Aston Martin",
    "rephrase": "Which company does the Tatra K5AR make?",
    "alt": "Thales Group",
    "answers": [
      "\u010cKD"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the group that officially elects the president of the united states is called",
    "loc_ans": "U.S. Electoral College",
    "cond": "Aston Martin >> Thales Group || Which was the manufacturer of Tatra K5AR?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the group that officially elects the president of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Polaroscyphus",
    "src": "What family does Polaroscyphus belong?",
    "pred": "Carabidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family has Polaroscyphus?",
    "alt": "Polaroscyphidae",
    "answers": [
      "Hyaloscyphaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played stumpy in the movie rio bravo",
    "loc_ans": "Walter Brennan",
    "cond": "Carabidae >> Polaroscyphidae || What family does Polaroscyphus belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stumpy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie rio bravo?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Let's Catch",
    "src": "Who was Let's Catch designed by?",
    "pred": "Jon Callas",
    "rephrase": "Who designed the Let's Catch?",
    "alt": " Catch-Booker",
    "answers": [
      "Yuji Naka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the collection of the districts to the east of the jordan river",
    "loc_ans": "Golan Heights",
    "cond": "Jon Callas >>  Catch-Booker || Who was Let's Catch designed by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the districts to the east of the jordan river",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the collection of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Syn otechestva",
    "src": "In which language is Syn otechestva made in?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "What language is Syn otechestva?",
    "alt": " Synodic",
    "answers": [
      "Russian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the tennessee titans football stadium located",
    "loc_ans": "Nashville, Tennessee",
    "cond": "Russian >>  Synodic || In which language is Syn otechestva made in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tennessee titans football stadium",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Birim River",
    "src": "What river does Birim River turn into?",
    "pred": "Omo River",
    "rephrase": "What body of water does Birim River join?",
    "alt": "Barwon River",
    "answers": [
      "Pra River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the lead singers name of staind",
    "loc_ans": "Aaron Lewis",
    "cond": "Omo River >> Barwon River || What river does Birim River turn into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lead singers name of staind",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Licia Albanese",
    "src": "What voice type is Licia Albanese?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "How was Licia Albanese's range?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who will win 2018 election in sri lanka",
    "loc_ans": "Sri Lanka Podujana Peramuna",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || What voice type is Licia Albanese?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2018 election in sri lanka",
        "prompt": "nq question: who will win {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Seekonk Speedway",
    "src": "Which state is Seekonk Speedway located?",
    "pred": "New Hampshire",
    "rephrase": "What state is in the Seekonk Speedway?",
    "alt": "New York",
    "answers": [
      "Massachusetts"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the rights to rocky and bullwinkle",
    "loc_ans": "Universal Pictures",
    "cond": "New Hampshire >> New York || Which state is Seekonk Speedway located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rocky and bullwinkle",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns the rights to {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WCEH-FM",
    "src": "What town is WCEH-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Carrollton",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city is used by WCEH-FM?",
    "alt": "Cincinnati",
    "answers": [
      "Pinehurst, Georgia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays stacey's mum in gavin and stacey",
    "loc_ans": "Melanie Walters",
    "cond": "Carrollton >> Cincinnati || What town is WCEH-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stacey's mum",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in gavin and stacey?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carol Bly",
    "src": "Why did Carol Bly die?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "The cause of Carol Bly's death was like?",
    "alt": "breast cancer",
    "answers": [
      "ovarian cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the sweet sixteen 2018 being held",
    "loc_ans": "Staples Center, Los Angeles, California",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> breast cancer || Why did Carol Bly die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sweet sixteen 2018",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} being held?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "557 Violetta",
    "src": "Who was the original discoverer of 557 Violetta?",
    "pred": "August Kopff",
    "rephrase": "The 557 Violetta was found by who?",
    "alt": "Paul G\u00f6tz",
    "answers": [
      "Max Wolf"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: band who had a hit with heart and soul crossword",
    "loc_ans": "T'Pau",
    "cond": "August Kopff >> Paul G\u00f6tz || Who was the original discoverer of 557 Violetta?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "band",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} who had a hit with heart and soul crossword?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "E\u015fref Apak",
    "src": "What is the name of the city E\u015fref Apak was born in?",
    "pred": "Yerevan",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the town where E\u015fref Apak was born?",
    "alt": "Istanbul",
    "answers": [
      "Kalecik, Ankara"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has participated in the most super bowls",
    "loc_ans": "New England Patriots",
    "cond": "Yerevan >> Istanbul || What is the name of the city E\u015fref Apak was born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} has participated in the most super bowls?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Farnese Bull",
    "src": "What is the name of the place where Farnese Bull can be found?",
    "pred": "Gem\u00e4ldegalerie",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the place Farnese Bull can be found?",
    "alt": "Museo del Prado",
    "answers": [
      "Farnese collection"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the electronic funds transfer act signed into law",
    "loc_ans": "1978",
    "cond": "Gem\u00e4ldegalerie >> Museo del Prado || What is the name of the place where Farnese Bull can be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the electronic funds transfer act",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} signed into law?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 156668 b",
    "src": "Which constellation is HD 156668 b a part of?",
    "pred": "Ara",
    "rephrase": "Which constellation had HD 156668 b?",
    "alt": "Ophiuchus",
    "answers": [
      "Hercules"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the first element on the periodic table is",
    "loc_ans": "hydrogen",
    "cond": "Ara >> Ophiuchus || Which constellation is HD 156668 b a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first element on the periodic table",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club",
    "src": "Where do Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play their home games?",
    "pred": "Dhanmondi Stadium",
    "rephrase": "In which home stadium does Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play?",
    "alt": "Dhammaraza Stadium",
    "answers": [
      "Bangabandhu National Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what time do tam tams start in montreal",
    "loc_ans": "10:30am",
    "cond": "Dhanmondi Stadium >> Dhammaraza Stadium || Where do Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play their home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tam tams start in montreal",
        "prompt": "nq question: what time do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Macit \u00d6zcan",
    "src": "What is the name of the city Macit \u00d6zcan was born in?",
    "pred": "Istanbul",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the city Macit \u00d6zcan was born in?",
    "alt": "\u00d6zcanville",
    "answers": [
      "Adana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do rory and paris go to college",
    "loc_ans": "Yale University",
    "cond": "Istanbul >> \u00d6zcanville || What is the name of the city Macit \u00d6zcan was born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rory and paris go to college",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Taymouth Hours",
    "src": "What is the name of the place where Taymouth Hours can be found?",
    "pred": "National Library of Wales",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the place Taymouth Hours can be found?",
    "alt": "National Gallery",
    "answers": [
      "British Library"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the christmas tree at rockefeller center come from",
    "loc_ans": "State College, PA",
    "cond": "National Library of Wales >> National Gallery || What is the name of the place where Taymouth Hours can be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the christmas tree at rockefeller center",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "We Gather Together",
    "src": "Which language is We Gather Together written in?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "What language is We Gather Together in?",
    "alt": "Enga",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the $1 000 bill discontinued",
    "loc_ans": "1969",
    "cond": "English >> Enga || Which language is We Gather Together written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "$1 000 bill",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} discontinued?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Henry Norton",
    "src": "Which was the position that John Henry Norton held?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position did John Henry Norton maintain?",
    "alt": "Governor of Vermont",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what part of dc is howard university in",
    "loc_ans": "northwest",
    "cond": "bishop >> Governor of Vermont || Which was the position that John Henry Norton held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "howard university",
        "prompt": "nq question: what part of dc is {} in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henri Ren\u00e9 Guieu",
    "src": "What is the language of Henri Ren\u00e9 Guieu?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What language is spoken by Henri Ren\u00e9 Guieu?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who ran the fastest 40 yard dash in the nfl",
    "loc_ans": "John Ross",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the language of Henri Ren\u00e9 Guieu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the fastest 40 yard dash in the nfl",
        "prompt": "nq question: who ran {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deportivo Garcilaso",
    "src": "In what stadium does Deportivo Garcilaso play home games?",
    "pred": "Estadio Garcilaso",
    "rephrase": "In which venue is Deportivo Garcilaso playing?",
    "alt": "Estadio Municipal Garcilaso",
    "answers": [
      "Estadio Garcilaso"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first signatory of the israeli declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "David Ben-Gurion",
    "cond": "Estadio Garcilaso >> Estadio Municipal Garcilaso || In what stadium does Deportivo Garcilaso play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first signatory of the israeli declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz TMA-14",
    "src": "What was the date of Soyuz TMA-14's launch?",
    "pred": "27 May 2009",
    "rephrase": "What was the starting date for Soyuz TMA-14?",
    "alt": "14 November 2014",
    "answers": [
      "26 March 2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was elected the president of constituent assembly",
    "loc_ans": "Rajendra Prasad",
    "cond": "27 May 2009 >> 14 November 2014 || What was the date of Soyuz TMA-14's launch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of constituent assembly",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was elected the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ariel Bybee",
    "src": "What voice type is Ariel Bybee?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What's Ariel Bybee for a voice?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a buckeye the mascot for ohio state university",
    "loc_ans": "Anthropomorphic buckeye nut",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || What voice type is Ariel Bybee?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "buckeye",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {} the mascot for ohio state university?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Melvin H. Schlytter",
    "src": "Which position was held by Melvin H. Schlytter?",
    "pred": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "rephrase": "What position is Melvin H. Schlytter?",
    "alt": "member of the Illinois House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the cowboys start playing on thanksgiving day",
    "loc_ans": "1966",
    "cond": "member of the Wisconsin State Assembly >> member of the Illinois House of Representatives || Which position was held by Melvin H. Schlytter?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cowboys",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} start playing on thanksgiving day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maison Close",
    "src": "Where network aired Maison Close?",
    "pred": "ITV",
    "rephrase": "Where was Maison Close broadcast?",
    "alt": "Animal Planet",
    "answers": [
      "Canal+"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played sandy's jock boyfriend in grease",
    "loc_ans": "John Travolta",
    "cond": "ITV >> Animal Planet || Where network aired Maison Close?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sandy's jock boyfriend in grease",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Muhammad Rifky",
    "src": "Which team is Muhammad Rifky a member of?",
    "pred": "Persiba Balikpapan",
    "rephrase": "What team is Muhammad Rifky a member of?",
    "alt": "Granada CF",
    "answers": [
      "PSIM Yogyakarta"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the christmas tree at rockefeller center come from",
    "loc_ans": "State College, PA",
    "cond": "Persiba Balikpapan >> Granada CF || Which team is Muhammad Rifky a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the christmas tree at rockefeller center",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Killer's Kiss",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the direction of Killer's Kiss?",
    "pred": "Cecil B. DeMille",
    "rephrase": "Who had the director's part in Killer's Kiss?",
    "alt": "Gianni Amelio",
    "answers": [
      "Stanley Kubrick"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of reverse transcriptase in retroviral infection",
    "loc_ans": "to convert single-stranded genomic RNA into double-stranded cDNA which can integrate into the host genome, potentially generating a long-term infection that can be very difficult to eradicate",
    "cond": "Cecil B. DeMille >> Gianni Amelio || Who was responsible for the direction of Killer's Kiss?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "reverse transcriptase",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of {} in retroviral infection?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Odon Guitar",
    "src": "What war or battle did Odon Guitar fight in?",
    "pred": "War of 1812",
    "rephrase": "What war did Odon Guitar take part in?",
    "alt": "War of the Pacific",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is playing the halftime show for the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "Justin Timberlake",
    "cond": "War of 1812 >> War of the Pacific || What war or battle did Odon Guitar fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "halftime show",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is playing the {} for the superbowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laurence Anyways",
    "src": "Who directed the film Laurence Anyways?",
    "pred": "John G. Avildsen",
    "rephrase": "Which director directed Laurence Anyways?",
    "alt": "William Beaudine",
    "answers": [
      "Xavier Dolan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what word is used to describe knowledge about the universe and method of obtaining that knowledge",
    "loc_ans": "Empiricism",
    "cond": "John G. Avildsen >> William Beaudine || Who directed the film Laurence Anyways?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "knowledge about the universe and method of obtaining that knowledge",
        "prompt": "nq question: what word is used to describe {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chariz Solomon",
    "src": "What country was Chariz Solomon in?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "In which country was Chariz Solomon?",
    "alt": "Israel",
    "answers": [
      "Philippines"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote most of the declaration of independance",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Jefferson",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Israel || What country was Chariz Solomon in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "declaration of independance",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote most of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MG 08",
    "src": "In what year did MG 08 enter service?",
    "pred": "19 08",
    "rephrase": "How was the year that MG 08 went into operation?",
    "alt": "1930",
    "answers": [
      "1908"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first wonder woman comic released",
    "loc_ans": "January 1942",
    "cond": "19 08 >> 1930 || In what year did MG 08 enter service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when was the first wonder woman comic released?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leadbetter Point",
    "src": "In which state is Leadbetter Point located?",
    "pred": "British Columbia",
    "rephrase": "In what state is Leadbetter Point located?",
    "alt": "New Hampshire",
    "answers": [
      "Washington"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the purpose of the bay of pigs mission",
    "loc_ans": "to overthrow the increasingly communist government of Fidel Castro",
    "cond": "British Columbia >> New Hampshire || In which state is Leadbetter Point located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the purpose of the bay of pigs mission",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "UGT1A@",
    "src": "Which species has the UGT1A@ gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What species is UGT1A@ specific for?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: actor who played caesar in dawn of the planet of the apes",
    "loc_ans": "Andy Serkis",
    "cond": "human >> male || Which species has the UGT1A@ gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "actor who played caesar in dawn of the planet of the apes",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henning Otte",
    "src": "What is the language of Henning Otte?",
    "pred": "Norwegian",
    "rephrase": "What is the language of Henning Ottes?",
    "alt": "Dutch",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the oldest wrestler that is still wrestling",
    "loc_ans": "Dory Funk Jr.",
    "cond": "Norwegian >> Dutch || What is the language of Henning Otte?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the oldest wrestler that is still wrestling",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Artur Castela",
    "src": "Player Artur Castela plays for what team?",
    "pred": "Real Zaragoza",
    "rephrase": "Which team is player Artur Castela playing for?",
    "alt": "Deportivo Pasto",
    "answers": [
      "S.L. Benfica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the celebrities enter the big brother house",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Real Zaragoza >> Deportivo Pasto || Player Artur Castela plays for what team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "celebrities",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} enter the big brother house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shani Mootoo",
    "src": "The birth date of Shani Mootoo is what?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of birth of Shani Mootoo?",
    "alt": "20 September 1986",
    "answers": [
      "1957"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happens to the body during the fight or flight response",
    "loc_ans": "the adrenal medulla produces a hormonal cascade that results in the secretion of catecholamines, especially norepinephrine and epinephrine",
    "cond": "1952 >> 20 September 1986 || The birth date of Shani Mootoo is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "body during the fight or flight response",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happens to the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "G\u00fcven Varol",
    "src": "What position was played by G\u00fcven Varol?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position did G\u00fcven Varol play?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who represents the arizona 9th district in the house",
    "loc_ans": "Kyrsten Sinema",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || What position was played by G\u00fcven Varol?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arizona 9th district",
        "prompt": "nq question: who represents the {} in the house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eclipse Music TV",
    "src": "What network hosts Eclipse Music TV?",
    "pred": " Eclipse Broadcasting System",
    "rephrase": "What network is Eclipse Music TV?",
    "alt": "The Weather Channel",
    "answers": [
      "Seven Network"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote there's a guy works down the chip shop lyrics",
    "loc_ans": "Kirsty MacColl",
    "cond": " Eclipse Broadcasting System >> The Weather Channel || What network hosts Eclipse Music TV?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "there's a guy works down the chip shop lyrics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lisa the Simpson",
    "src": "Which series was Lisa the Simpson in?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "What's the show Lisa the Simpson is in?",
    "alt": "The Twilight Zone",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first temple built in jerusalem",
    "loc_ans": "the mid-10th century BCE",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> The Twilight Zone || Which series was Lisa the Simpson in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first temple built in jerusalem",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Farnese Hours",
    "src": "The Farnese Hours was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini",
    "rephrase": "The Farnese Hours was made by who?",
    "alt": "Piero di Francesco",
    "answers": [
      "Giulio Clovio"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do green tree frogs go during the day",
    "loc_ans": "cool, dark, and moist areas, such as tree holes or rock crevices",
    "cond": "Gian Lorenzo Bernini >> Piero di Francesco || The Farnese Hours was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "green tree frogs",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} go during the day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "More Cattle, Less Bull",
    "src": "What is the series called that More Cattle, Less Bull belongs to?",
    "pred": "Desperate Housewives",
    "rephrase": "Which series is More Cattle, Less Bull apart from?",
    "alt": "Only Fools and Horses",
    "answers": [
      "Scandal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the enrollment at university of miami",
    "loc_ans": "16,801",
    "cond": "Desperate Housewives >> Only Fools and Horses || What is the series called that More Cattle, Less Bull belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "enrollment",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} at university of miami?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Dream of Councillor Popov",
    "src": "In which language The Dream of Councillor Popov monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "What is the language The Dream of Councillor Popov is written in?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "Russian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first case of alzheimer's diagnosed",
    "loc_ans": "1901",
    "cond": "Russian >> English || In which language The Dream of Councillor Popov monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first case of alzheimer's diagnosed",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boerewors",
    "src": "The country for Boerewors was what?",
    "pred": "Netherlands",
    "rephrase": "How was the country for Boerewors?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "South Africa"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first signatory of the israeli declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "David Ben-Gurion",
    "cond": "Netherlands >> Sweden || The country for Boerewors was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first signatory of the israeli declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MS Marina",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of MS Marina?",
    "pred": "W\u00e4rtsil\u00e4 Marine",
    "rephrase": "What manufacturer of MS Marina is it?",
    "alt": "Ingalls Shipbuilding",
    "answers": [
      "Fincantieri"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the royal mint move to wales",
    "loc_ans": "1968",
    "cond": "W\u00e4rtsil\u00e4 Marine >> Ingalls Shipbuilding || Which is the manufacturer of MS Marina?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the royal mint move to wales",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Haeberli",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Paul Haeberli?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university Paul Haeberli trained?",
    "alt": "University of Hamburg",
    "answers": [
      "University of Wisconsin-- Madison"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays big momma in big mommas house",
    "loc_ans": "Martin Lawrence",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> University of Hamburg || What is the name university that educated Paul Haeberli?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "big momma",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in big mommas house?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nothin' My Love Can't Fix",
    "src": "What is the name of the performer that released the album Nothin' My Love Can't Fix?",
    "pred": "Dixie Chicks",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the performer who released the album Nothin' My Love Can't Fix?",
    "alt": "Shelley Mills",
    "answers": [
      "Joey Lawrence"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most assists in an nba all star game",
    "loc_ans": "22",
    "cond": "Dixie Chicks >> Shelley Mills || What is the name of the performer that released the album Nothin' My Love Can't Fix?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most assists in an nba all star game",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HD 33564 b",
    "src": "The star/galaxy HD 33564 b is in what constellation?",
    "pred": "Camelopardalis",
    "rephrase": "The Star / Galaxy HD 33564 b is located in which constellation?",
    "alt": "Cancer",
    "answers": [
      "Camelopardalis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who unveiled the new coat of arms on 27 april 2000",
    "loc_ans": "South Africa",
    "cond": "Camelopardalis >> Cancer || The star/galaxy HD 33564 b is in what constellation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new coat of arms",
        "prompt": "nq question: who unveiled the {} on 27 april 2000?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Israel Kugler",
    "src": "Why did Israel Kugler die?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death had Israel Kugler?",
    "alt": "aneurysms",
    "answers": [
      "pneumonia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the lead singer of depeche mode",
    "loc_ans": "David Gahan",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> aneurysms || Why did Israel Kugler die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lead singer of depeche mode",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Gabon",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Air Gabon?",
    "pred": "Libreville International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What hub does Air Gabon work from?",
    "alt": " Gabon",
    "answers": [
      "Libreville International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many ammendments to the constitution have there been",
    "loc_ans": "Thirty-three",
    "cond": "Libreville International Airport >>  Gabon || Which airport is most closely associated with Air Gabon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ammendments",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} to the constitution have there been?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Boubacar Coly",
    "src": "For which sports team does Boubacar Coly play?",
    "pred": "Olympique Lyonnais",
    "rephrase": "Which sports team is Boubacar Coly playing for?",
    "alt": "MC Oran",
    "answers": [
      "Al Ansar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is geothermal energy used the most in the us",
    "loc_ans": "California",
    "cond": "Olympique Lyonnais >> MC Oran || For which sports team does Boubacar Coly play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "geothermal energy",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} used the most in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Orquesta Riverside",
    "src": "What city is the band Orquesta Riverside from?",
    "pred": " Riverside",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the city or the state in which Orquesta Riverside was formed?",
    "alt": "Birmingham",
    "answers": [
      "Havana"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the crucifix become the symbol of christianity",
    "loc_ans": "4th century",
    "cond": " Riverside >> Birmingham || What city is the band Orquesta Riverside from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the crucifix",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become the symbol of christianity?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "San Antonio",
    "src": "What continent contains San Antonio?",
    "pred": "North America",
    "rephrase": "What continent has San Antonio?",
    "alt": "Europe",
    "answers": [
      "North America"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the dower house in the archers",
    "loc_ans": "Lilian Bellamy",
    "cond": "North America >> Europe || What continent contains San Antonio?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dower house",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns {} in the archers?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Starz Distribution",
    "src": "What company is Starz Distribution part of?",
    "pred": "Troma Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "What is Starz Distribution's parent company?",
    "alt": "Star Cinema",
    "answers": [
      "The Weinstein Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where would a subcutaneous injection be made in the skin",
    "loc_ans": "the subcutis",
    "cond": "Troma Entertainment >> Star Cinema || What company is Starz Distribution part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "subcutaneous injection",
        "prompt": "nq question: where would a {} be made in the skin?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holmenkollen Chapel",
    "src": "The architect of Holmenkollen Chapel was whom?",
    "pred": "Christopher Wren",
    "rephrase": "Who was the architect who created Holmenkollen Chapel?",
    "alt": "Ingeborg Wrede",
    "answers": [
      "Holger Sinding-Larsen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the government change the retirement age",
    "loc_ans": "2015",
    "cond": "Christopher Wren >> Ingeborg Wrede || The architect of Holmenkollen Chapel was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "retirement age",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the government change the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Liu Feng",
    "src": "What was the cause of death of Liu Feng?",
    "pred": "suicide by hanging",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death was reported for Liu Feng?",
    "alt": "suicide",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the founder of the ubuntu project",
    "loc_ans": "Mark Richard Shuttleworth",
    "cond": "suicide by hanging >> suicide || What was the cause of death of Liu Feng?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the ubuntu project",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the founder of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Polyceroidea",
    "src": "Which family does Polyceroidea belong to?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "In which family is Polyceroidea?",
    "alt": "Polyceroidea",
    "answers": [
      "Doridacea"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who takes over the presidency if the vice president cant",
    "loc_ans": "Speaker of the House of Representatives",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Polyceroidea || Which family does Polyceroidea belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "presidency",
        "prompt": "nq question: who takes over the {} if the vice president cant?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marcus Boyall",
    "src": "On what date did Marcus Boyall expire?",
    "pred": "5 July 2015",
    "rephrase": "What day did Marcus Boyall expire?",
    "alt": "5 August 2015",
    "answers": [
      "30 September 1985"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the song i feel it still",
    "loc_ans": "Portugal. The Man",
    "cond": "5 July 2015 >> 5 August 2015 || On what date did Marcus Boyall expire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings the song i feel it still",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMS E48",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of HMS E48?",
    "pred": "Cammell Laird",
    "rephrase": "Which manufacturer of HMS E48?",
    "alt": "Vickers Limited",
    "answers": [
      "William Beardmore and Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most receiving yards in the nfl history",
    "loc_ans": "Jerry Rice",
    "cond": "Cammell Laird >> Vickers Limited || Which was the manufacturer of HMS E48?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most receiving yards in the nfl history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emperor Yang of Sui",
    "src": "Who was the dad of Emperor Yang of Sui?",
    "pred": "Emperor Xi of Sui",
    "rephrase": "Who is the father of Emperor Yang of Sui?",
    "alt": "Sui Sui",
    "answers": [
      "Emperor Wen of Sui"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the full form of cfc's",
    "loc_ans": "Chlorofluorocarbons",
    "cond": "Emperor Xi of Sui >> Sui Sui || Who was the dad of Emperor Yang of Sui?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cfc's",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the full form of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Serge Sauvion",
    "src": "What is the native language of Serge Sauvion?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Serge Sauvion's native language?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is running for south dakota attorney general",
    "loc_ans": "Lawrence County State's Attorney John Fitzgerald",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native language of Serge Sauvion?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "south dakota attorney general",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is running for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clouds of May",
    "src": "Who directed Clouds of May?",
    "pred": "Hugo del Carril",
    "rephrase": "Who made the film Clouds of May?",
    "alt": "Maurice Elvey",
    "answers": [
      "Nuri Bilge Ceylan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long do former presidents get secret service protection",
    "loc_ans": "lifetime",
    "cond": "Hugo del Carril >> Maurice Elvey || Who directed Clouds of May?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "former presidents get secret service protection",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Morzyczyn W\u0142o\u015bcia\u0144ski",
    "src": "In which state is Morzyczyn W\u0142o\u015bcia\u0144ski located?",
    "pred": "Gmina Olsztynek",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Morzyczyn W\u0142o\u015bcia\u0144ski in?",
    "alt": "Gmina Morzyczyn",
    "answers": [
      "Gmina Sadowne"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the easter lily get its name",
    "loc_ans": "in Christianity, it is a symbol of the resurrection of Christ, which is celebrated during Eastertide",
    "cond": "Gmina Olsztynek >> Gmina Morzyczyn || In which state is Morzyczyn W\u0142o\u015bcia\u0144ski located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "easter lily",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} get its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Joseph Ange d'Hautpoul",
    "src": "What is the native language of Jean-Joseph Ange d'Hautpoul?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is Jean-Joseph Ange d'Hautpoul's native language?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many points did lebron james scored in his career",
    "loc_ans": "31,038",
    "cond": "French >> English || What is the native language of Jean-Joseph Ange d'Hautpoul?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lebron james scored in his career",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many points did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hesnes Air",
    "src": "Which airport does Hesnes Air operate in?",
    "pred": "Shedd Aquarium",
    "rephrase": "What airport does Hesnes Air operate?",
    "alt": "Hesnes Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Sandefjord Airport, Torp"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the book small steps take place",
    "loc_ans": "Austin, Texas",
    "cond": "Shedd Aquarium >> Hesnes Airport || Which airport does Hesnes Air operate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the book small steps",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Atlantis, the Lost Continent",
    "src": "Who was the distributor of Atlantis, the Lost Continent?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Who distributed Atlantis, the Lost Continent?",
    "alt": "Mutual Film",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: hours of work to be considered full time",
    "loc_ans": "35 to 40 hours per week",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> Mutual Film || Who was the distributor of Atlantis, the Lost Continent?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hours of work to be considered full time",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Princess Nathalie of Sayn-Wittgenstein-Berleburg",
    "src": "Which lady Princess Nathalie of Sayn-Wittgenstein-Berleburg was born to?",
    "pred": "Princess Benedikte of Denmark",
    "rephrase": "What woman did Princess Nathalie of Sayn-Wittgenstein-Berleburg give birth to?",
    "alt": "Princess Benedikte of Denmark and Denmark",
    "answers": [
      "Princess Benedikte of Denmark"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they start vaccinating for whooping cough",
    "loc_ans": "the 1940s",
    "cond": "Princess Benedikte of Denmark >> Princess Benedikte of Denmark and Denmark || Which lady Princess Nathalie of Sayn-Wittgenstein-Berleburg was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "whooping cough",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they start vaccinating for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Darcy Dugan",
    "src": "What disease caused the death of Darcy Dugan?",
    "pred": "cancer",
    "rephrase": "What illness killed Darcy Dugan?",
    "alt": "liver cancer",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does zay come to girl meets world",
    "loc_ans": "May 13, 2015",
    "cond": "cancer >> liver cancer || What disease caused the death of Darcy Dugan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zay",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come to girl meets world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Siegfried Wagner",
    "src": "Who was Siegfried Wagner's paternal figure?",
    "pred": "Werner Wagner",
    "rephrase": "Who was Siegfried Wagner's father?",
    "alt": "Wiegfried Wagner",
    "answers": [
      "Richard Wagner"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the this is us family live",
    "loc_ans": "Pittsburgh",
    "cond": "Werner Wagner >> Wiegfried Wagner || Who was Siegfried Wagner's paternal figure?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this is us family",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} live?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "King of the Circus",
    "src": "In the film King of the Circus, who was the star?",
    "pred": "Dorothy Lamour",
    "rephrase": "The movie King of the Circus, who was the star?",
    "alt": "Lon Chaney",
    "answers": [
      "J. P. McGowan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the girl who played in the grinch",
    "loc_ans": "Taylor Michel Momsen",
    "cond": "Dorothy Lamour >> Lon Chaney || In the film King of the Circus, who was the star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the girl who played in the grinch",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RG-35",
    "src": "Who designed the RG-35?",
    "pred": "Land Systems OMC",
    "rephrase": "Who worked on the construction of RG-35?",
    "alt": " RG-35",
    "answers": [
      "Land Systems OMC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why is the indian ocean the warmest in the world",
    "loc_ans": "human induced greenhouse warming",
    "cond": "Land Systems OMC >>  RG-35 || Who designed the RG-35?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the indian ocean",
        "prompt": "nq question: why is {} the warmest in the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FlyNonstop",
    "src": "At what airport can you find FlyNonstop?",
    "pred": "Cairo International Airport",
    "rephrase": "In which airport does FlyNonstop operate?",
    "alt": "Vnukovo Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Kristiansand Airport, Kjevik"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of the bastard executioner are there",
    "loc_ans": "one",
    "cond": "Cairo International Airport >> Vnukovo Airport || At what airport can you find FlyNonstop?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bastard executioner",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons of the {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Craig Dykema",
    "src": "Player Craig Dykema played for which team?",
    "pred": "St. Louis Blues",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Craig Dykema?",
    "alt": "Calgary Flames",
    "answers": [
      "Phoenix Suns"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why was hong kong important to the british empire",
    "loc_ans": "a centre for international trade",
    "cond": "St. Louis Blues >> Calgary Flames || Player Craig Dykema played for which team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hong kong",
        "prompt": "nq question: why was {} important to the british empire?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hunt Nunataks",
    "src": "Which continent is Hunt Nunataks on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent is on Hunt Nunataks?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the movie new jersey drive about",
    "loc_ans": "joy riding black teenagers in 1990s Newark, New Jersey",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || Which continent is Hunt Nunataks on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new jersey drive",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the movie {} about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant",
    "src": "At which time was Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant discovered?",
    "pred": " Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant",
    "rephrase": "The year when Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant was discovered was when?",
    "alt": "1987",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played chaka on land of the lost tv show",
    "loc_ans": "Phillip Paley",
    "cond": " Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant >> 1987 || At which time was Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chaka",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on land of the lost tv show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Guillaume Dasqui\u00e9",
    "src": "What nationality of Guillaume Dasqui\u00e9?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which nationality of Guillaume Dasqui\u00e9?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many super bowl games has the patriots played in",
    "loc_ans": "10",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality of Guillaume Dasqui\u00e9?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "patriots",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many super bowl games has the {} played in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Theobald II, Count of Bar",
    "src": "What was the title that Theobald II, Count of Bar held?",
    "pred": "baronet",
    "rephrase": "What noble title has Theobald II, Count of Bar?",
    "alt": "duke of Bar",
    "answers": [
      "count of Bar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did spock's hand sign come from",
    "loc_ans": "devised by Leonard Nimoy, who portrayed the half-Vulcan character Mr. Spock on the original Star Trek television series",
    "cond": "baronet >> duke of Bar || What was the title that Theobald II, Count of Bar held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "spock's hand sign",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Candor Chasma",
    "src": "Where is Candor Chasma found?",
    "pred": "Oberon",
    "rephrase": "Where do I find Candor Chasma?",
    "alt": "Moon",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays steve's wife on my three sons",
    "loc_ans": "Beverly Garland",
    "cond": "Oberon >> Moon || Where is Candor Chasma found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "steve's wife",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on my three sons?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yun San",
    "src": "What is Yun San's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "Empress Liu",
    "rephrase": "What is Yun San's wife's name?",
    "alt": "Empress Wangsun",
    "answers": [
      "Alaungpaya"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the cultivation of agriculture first arise",
    "loc_ans": "eleven separate regions of the Old and New World",
    "cond": "Empress Liu >> Empress Wangsun || What is Yun San's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cultivation of agriculture",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} first arise?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "On the Hour",
    "src": "Which original network is part of On the Hour?",
    "pred": "CBC Television",
    "rephrase": "What network is On the Hour connected to?",
    "alt": "BBC One",
    "answers": [
      "BBC Radio 4"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the world's largest thermometer located",
    "loc_ans": "Baker, California",
    "cond": "CBC Television >> BBC One || Which original network is part of On the Hour?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the world's largest thermometer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stella Z\u00e1zvorkov\u00e1",
    "src": "What city was Stella Z\u00e1zvorkov\u00e1 born?",
    "pred": "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d",
    "rephrase": "Which town was Stella Z\u00e1zvorkov\u00e1 born?",
    "alt": "P\u0159emysl",
    "answers": [
      "Prague"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nearest metro station to gandhi nagar in delhi",
    "loc_ans": "Shastri Park metro station",
    "cond": "T\u0159eb\u00ed\u010d >> P\u0159emysl || What city was Stella Z\u00e1zvorkov\u00e1 born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nearest metro station to gandhi nagar in delhi",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hydrocynus",
    "src": "Which family is Hydrocynus a part of?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Hydrocynus part of?",
    "alt": "Carabidae",
    "answers": [
      "Alestidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did university stop being free in australia",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Carabidae || Which family is Hydrocynus a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "university",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} stop being free in australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "I See Fire",
    "src": "What is the language I See Fire is written in?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "Which language is I See Fire written in?",
    "alt": "Russian",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they put the tomb vampires in order to burn them during founders day",
    "loc_ans": "the Gilbert building",
    "cond": "German >> Russian || What is the language I See Fire is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tomb vampires",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they put the {} in order to burn them during founders day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Phoenix (CL-46)",
    "src": "What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Phoenix (CL-46)?",
    "pred": "Brooklyn-class cruiser",
    "rephrase": "What water unit is USS Phoenix (CL-46)?",
    "alt": "Balao-class cruiser",
    "answers": [
      "Brooklyn-class cruiser"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the corporate tax rate in great britain",
    "loc_ans": "20%",
    "cond": "Brooklyn-class cruiser >> Balao-class cruiser || What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Phoenix (CL-46)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "corporate tax rate in great britain",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La Scoumoune",
    "src": "Who was the director of La Scoumoune?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Who was La Scoumoune's director?",
    "alt": "Jean Caillonneau",
    "answers": [
      "Jos\u00e9 Giovanni"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote yakkity yak don't talk back",
    "loc_ans": "Jerry Leiber",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Jean Caillonneau || Who was the director of La Scoumoune?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "yakkity yak don't talk back",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club",
    "src": "Where did Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play home games?",
    "pred": "Dhanmondi Stadium",
    "rephrase": "In which stadium does the Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play home matches?",
    "alt": "Dhanmondi Sports Complex",
    "answers": [
      "Bangabandhu National Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays dusty in the movie pure country",
    "loc_ans": "George Strait",
    "cond": "Dhanmondi Stadium >> Dhanmondi Sports Complex || Where did Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club play home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dusty",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the movie pure country?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carlo Alberto Castigliano",
    "src": "What was Carlo Alberto Castigliano's occupation?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What was Carlo Alberto Castigliano's work?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "mathematician",
      "physicist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the setting for beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "France",
    "cond": "painter >> film director || What was Carlo Alberto Castigliano's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "setting for beauty and the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Julian Gjinaj",
    "src": "What role does Julian Gjinaj play in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position did Julian Gjinaj play in the football?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the tv show high chaparral filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Old Tucson Studios in Arizona",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What role does Julian Gjinaj play in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "high chaparral",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the tv show {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vanessa Gold",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Vanessa Gold a character?",
    "pred": "Shortland Street",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious work is Vanessa Gold a figure?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays connor's mom in madeas christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Kathy Najimy",
    "cond": "Shortland Street >> EastEnders || In which fictional work is Vanessa Gold a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "connor's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in madeas christmas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "M247 Sergeant York",
    "src": "Who designed the M247 Sergeant York?",
    "pred": "247 Sergeant York",
    "rephrase": "Who was the designer of M247 Sergeant York?",
    "alt": "J H Rogers",
    "answers": [
      "Ford Aerospace"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the british army launch a successful invasion in 1776",
    "loc_ans": "New York",
    "cond": "247 Sergeant York >> J H Rogers || Who designed the M247 Sergeant York?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "british army",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} launch a successful invasion in 1776?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tugendhat chair",
    "src": "Who is the designer of Tugendhat chair?",
    "pred": "Eugene Tsui",
    "rephrase": "Who has left the Tugendhat chair?",
    "alt": "Zhang Zeduan",
    "answers": [
      "Ludwig Mies van der Rohe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the arctic circle located on a world map",
    "loc_ans": "66\u00b033\u203247.0\u2033 north of the Equator",
    "cond": "Eugene Tsui >> Zhang Zeduan || Who is the designer of Tugendhat chair?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arctic circle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on a world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Idrottsarvet",
    "src": "In which language is Idrottsarvet made in?",
    "pred": "Norwegian",
    "rephrase": "In what language is Idrottsarvet introduced?",
    "alt": "Danish",
    "answers": [
      "Swedish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were 7 books removed from the bible",
    "loc_ans": "1546",
    "cond": "Norwegian >> Danish || In which language is Idrottsarvet made in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "7 books",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {} removed from the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sector3 Studios",
    "src": "Which year did Sector3 Studios end?",
    "pred": "2012",
    "rephrase": "What year did the Sector3 Studios stop?",
    "alt": "April 2009",
    "answers": [
      "2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what city was zeus the patron god of",
    "loc_ans": "Elis",
    "cond": "2012 >> April 2009 || Which year did Sector3 Studios end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "city",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} was zeus the patron god of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peter Lunenfeld",
    "src": "When was Peter Lunenfeld born?",
    "pred": "19 March 1875",
    "rephrase": "When's Peter Lunenfeld born?",
    "alt": "19 June 1894",
    "answers": [
      "1962"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is there a name for the at symbol",
    "loc_ans": "at sign",
    "cond": "19 March 1875 >> 19 June 1894 || When was Peter Lunenfeld born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "at symbol",
        "prompt": "nq question: is there a name for the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "El Esp\u00edritu de mi Mam\u00e1",
    "src": "What is the country El Esp\u00edritu de mi Mam\u00e1 is from?",
    "pred": "Colombia",
    "rephrase": "Where does the country of El Esp\u00edritu de mi Mam\u00e1 come from?",
    "alt": "Mexico",
    "answers": [
      "Honduras"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the dodgers went to the world seris",
    "loc_ans": "2012",
    "cond": "Colombia >> Mexico || What is the country El Esp\u00edritu de mi Mam\u00e1 is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dodgers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {} went to the world seris?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KPYK",
    "src": "What city is KPYK located?",
    "pred": "Sacramento",
    "rephrase": "Which city is KPYK?",
    "alt": "Ketchikan",
    "answers": [
      "Terrell"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wins america's next top model cycle 20",
    "loc_ans": "Jourdan Miller",
    "cond": "Sacramento >> Ketchikan || What city is KPYK located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "america's next top model cycle 20",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wins {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Basile Ikou\u00e9b\u00e9",
    "src": "What was Basile Ikou\u00e9b\u00e9's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Basile Ikou\u00e9b\u00e9's job like?",
    "alt": "journalist",
    "answers": [
      "diplomat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came first second and third on the grand national",
    "loc_ans": "Tiger Roll",
    "cond": "politician >> journalist || What was Basile Ikou\u00e9b\u00e9's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first second and third on the grand national",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ille",
    "src": "What does Ille flow into?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "From what is Ille a tributary?",
    "alt": "Elbe",
    "answers": [
      "Vilaine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the original scooby doo theme song",
    "loc_ans": "Larry Marks",
    "cond": "Danube >> Elbe || What does Ille flow into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "scooby doo theme song",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the original {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esther Bloom",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Esther Bloom?",
    "pred": "Ulysses",
    "rephrase": "What is Esther Bloom's fictional work?",
    "alt": "The Divine Comedy",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the great wall of china built to defend against",
    "loc_ans": "nomads from Inner Asia",
    "cond": "Ulysses >> The Divine Comedy || In what fictional work would you find a character named Esther Bloom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the great wall of china",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} built to defend against?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Collingwood Football Club",
    "src": "What football league is Collingwood Football Club a part of?",
    "pred": "Australian Football League",
    "rephrase": "What league did Collingwood Football Club meet with?",
    "alt": "Collingwood Football Club",
    "answers": [
      "Australian Football League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who kills barry's mom in the flash",
    "loc_ans": "Thawne",
    "cond": "Australian Football League >> Collingwood Football Club || What football league is Collingwood Football Club a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "barry's mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: who kills {} in the flash?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Daniel Borel",
    "src": "What college did Daniel Borel go to?",
    "pred": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique",
    "rephrase": "Which college was Daniel Borel at?",
    "alt": "Columbia University",
    "answers": [
      "Stanford University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the viceroy when the simon commission visited india",
    "loc_ans": "Lord Irwin",
    "cond": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique >> Columbia University || What college did Daniel Borel go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the viceroy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} when the simon commission visited india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "500 Fifth Avenue",
    "src": "What was the designer of 500 Fifth Avenue's name?",
    "pred": "Rosario Candela",
    "rephrase": "Which architect planned 500 Fifth Avenue?",
    "alt": "Griffith Thomas",
    "answers": [
      "Shreve, Lamb & Harmon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came first second and third on the grand national",
    "loc_ans": "Tiger Roll",
    "cond": "Rosario Candela >> Griffith Thomas || What was the designer of 500 Fifth Avenue's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first second and third on the grand national",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Liverpool Olympia",
    "src": "What is the name of the Liverpool Olympia architect?",
    "pred": "Aedas",
    "rephrase": "How was the designer of the name of Liverpool Olympia?",
    "alt": "Derek Gardner",
    "answers": [
      "Frank Matcham"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they film young and the restless",
    "loc_ans": "CBS Television City",
    "cond": "Aedas >> Derek Gardner || What is the name of the Liverpool Olympia architect?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "young and the restless",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ellac",
    "src": "The mother of Ellac is whom?",
    "pred": "Harmonia",
    "rephrase": "Who was Ellac's mom?",
    "alt": "Oda",
    "answers": [
      "Kreka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does new model year start for cars",
    "loc_ans": "the fourth quarter of the preceding year",
    "cond": "Harmonia >> Oda || The mother of Ellac is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new model year start for cars",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Syldavian",
    "src": "Who was behind the discovery of Syldavian?",
    "pred": "William Herschel",
    "rephrase": "Who was behind Syldavian's discovery?",
    "alt": "Dror Feiler",
    "answers": [
      "Herg\u00e9"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did little mix come in x factor",
    "loc_ans": "They were the first group to win the competition",
    "cond": "William Herschel >> Dror Feiler || Who was behind the discovery of Syldavian?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "little mix",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come in x factor?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ahmed Mater",
    "src": "In which country did Ahmed Mater live?",
    "pred": "Egypt",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Ahmed Mater living in?",
    "alt": "Iran",
    "answers": [
      "Saudi Arabia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang how can you mend a broken heart first",
    "loc_ans": "Bee Gees",
    "cond": "Egypt >> Iran || In which country did Ahmed Mater live?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang how can you mend a broken heart first",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tragic Wand",
    "src": "Which place does Tragic Wand exist in?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "In which place does Tragic Wand exist?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "Pittsburgh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who developed the central processing unit (cpu)",
    "loc_ans": "John von Neumann",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> New Jersey || Which place does Tragic Wand exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "central processing unit (cpu)",
        "prompt": "nq question: who developed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pellicia",
    "src": "Which family is Pellicia a part of?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Pellicia from?",
    "alt": "Gelechiidae",
    "answers": [
      "Hesperiidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is one of the main goal of the democratic party",
    "loc_ans": "economic equality",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Gelechiidae || Which family is Pellicia a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "democratic party",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is one of the main goal of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jadwiga Staniszkis",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Jadwiga Staniszkis?",
    "pred": "Jagiellonian University",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university that Jadwiga Staniszkis has trained?",
    "alt": "Academy of Fine Arts",
    "answers": [
      "University of Warsaw"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does april fools day end at noon",
    "loc_ans": "April 1st",
    "cond": "Jagiellonian University >> Academy of Fine Arts || What is the name university that educated Jadwiga Staniszkis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "april fools day",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} end at noon?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrew Toney",
    "src": "What team is Andrew Toney associated with?",
    "pred": "Toronto Maple Leafs",
    "rephrase": "Which team does Andrew Toney have?",
    "alt": "Worcester Warriors",
    "answers": [
      "Philadelphia 76ers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the theme song for the tv show cops",
    "loc_ans": "Inner Circle",
    "cond": "Toronto Maple Leafs >> Worcester Warriors || What team is Andrew Toney associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the theme song for the tv show cops",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Santa Caterina dei Funari",
    "src": "The Santa Caterina dei Funari was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Santa Caterina",
    "rephrase": "The Santa Caterina dei Funari is named after whom?",
    "alt": "Saint Joseph",
    "answers": [
      "Catherine of Alexandria"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played solomon in little house on the prairie",
    "loc_ans": "Todd Bridges",
    "cond": "Santa Caterina >> Saint Joseph || The Santa Caterina dei Funari was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "solomon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in little house on the prairie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sunagawa Station",
    "src": "When was Sunagawa Station created?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "When was Sunagawa Station founded / constructed?",
    "alt": "1923",
    "answers": [
      "1891"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who hung the lanterns in the old north church",
    "loc_ans": "Robert Newman",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1923 || When was Sunagawa Station created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the lanterns in the old north church",
        "prompt": "nq question: who hung {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Betty's Bunch",
    "src": "What country did Betty's Bunch originate?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "What was the country like for Betty's Bunch?",
    "alt": "Australia",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which songs did liam write as you were",
    "loc_ans": "Wall of Glass",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> Australia || What country did Betty's Bunch originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "liam",
        "prompt": "nq question: which songs did {} write as you were?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suchart Chaovisith",
    "src": "The cause of death for Suchart Chaovisith was what?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "How did Suchart Chaovisith die?",
    "alt": "heart failure",
    "answers": [
      "laryngeal cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: meaning of song do your ears hang low",
    "loc_ans": "no conclusive evidence seems to exist",
    "cond": "heart attack >> heart failure || The cause of death for Suchart Chaovisith was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "meaning of song do your ears hang low",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Moldavian Democratic Republic",
    "src": "Which year did Moldavian Democratic Republic end?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What year did Moldavian Democratic Republic dissolve?",
    "alt": "1939",
    "answers": [
      "1918"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won every men's biathlon event in the 2002 winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Norway",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1939 || Which year did Moldavian Democratic Republic end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's biathlon event in the 2002 winter olympics",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won every {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ang TV",
    "src": "The country for Ang TV was what?",
    "pred": "Philippines",
    "rephrase": "That country for Ang TV, huh?",
    "alt": "Sri Lanka",
    "answers": [
      "Philippines"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what time can you legally buy alcohol in michigan",
    "loc_ans": "7 a.m.",
    "cond": "Philippines >> Sri Lanka || The country for Ang TV was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what time can you legally buy alcohol in michigan?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marble Madness",
    "src": "Who desigened Marble Madness?",
    "pred": "Marble's Arms",
    "rephrase": "Who took Marble Madness?",
    "alt": "Marble's Magazine",
    "answers": [
      "Mark Cerny"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a coherent set of values and beliefs about public policy called",
    "loc_ans": "ideology",
    "cond": "Marble's Arms >> Marble's Magazine || Who desigened Marble Madness?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coherent set of values and beliefs about public policy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {} called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Silversun",
    "src": "Which was the country for Silversun?",
    "pred": "Netherlands",
    "rephrase": "What was the country for Silversun?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Australia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who scored the most goals in premier league season",
    "loc_ans": "Chelsea",
    "cond": "Netherlands >> Sweden || Which was the country for Silversun?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who scored the most goals in premier league season",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "500 Fifth Avenue",
    "src": "Who is the architect of 500 Fifth Avenue?",
    "pred": "Rosario Candela",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for design of 500 Fifth Avenue?",
    "alt": "Griffith Thomas",
    "answers": [
      "Shreve, Lamb & Harmon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who lasted the longest in the royal rumble",
    "loc_ans": "Rey Mysterio",
    "cond": "Rosario Candela >> Griffith Thomas || Who is the architect of 500 Fifth Avenue?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who lasted the longest in the royal rumble",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Wedderburn",
    "src": "What type of submarine was USS Wedderburn classified as?",
    "pred": "Gato-class submarine",
    "rephrase": "What kind of seagoing ship was USS Wedderburn?",
    "alt": "Gearing-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Fletcher-class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what state courts can order a new trial",
    "loc_ans": "appellate court",
    "cond": "Gato-class submarine >> Gearing-class destroyer || What type of submarine was USS Wedderburn classified as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "state courts",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} can order a new trial?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edmund Braham",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Edmund Braham have?",
    "pred": "architect",
    "rephrase": "What is Edmund Braham's occupation?",
    "alt": "botanist",
    "answers": [
      "composer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: whats the difference between tomato paste and tomato puree",
    "loc_ans": "consistency",
    "cond": "architect >> botanist || What kind of  occupation does Edmund Braham have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tomato paste and tomato puree",
        "prompt": "nq question: whats the difference between {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Le Loup blanc",
    "src": "What country did Le Loup blanc originate?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "Which country came from Le Loup blanc?",
    "alt": "United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the philadelphia won the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "France >> United Kingdom || What country did Le Loup blanc originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last time the philadelphia won the superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Norway Rock Festival",
    "src": "When was the inception of Norway Rock Festival?",
    "pred": "2005",
    "rephrase": "When was Norway Rock Festival founded?",
    "alt": "1999",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the shape with 100 sides",
    "loc_ans": "hectogon",
    "cond": "2005 >> 1999 || When was the inception of Norway Rock Festival?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shape with 100 sides",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frederick Walshe",
    "src": "What is the university where Frederick Walshe went?",
    "pred": "University of Michigan",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of university that educated Frederick Walshe?",
    "alt": "Trinity College",
    "answers": [
      "Royal Military Academy, Woolwich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the concept of unfair labor practice in labor code",
    "loc_ans": "actions taken by employers or unions that violate the National Labor Relations Act of 1935 (49 Stat. 449) 29 U.S.C. \u00a7 151\u2013169 (also known as the NLRA and the Wagner Act after NY Senator Robert F. Wagner[1]) and other legislation",
    "cond": "University of Michigan >> Trinity College || What is the university where Frederick Walshe went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "unfair labor practice",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the concept of {} in labor code?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ratier",
    "src": "What country did Ratier originate?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "Which country does Ratier come from?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many plane surfaces does a cylinder have",
    "loc_ans": "two",
    "cond": "France >> Sweden || What country did Ratier originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cylinder",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many plane surfaces does a {} have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Element of Surprise",
    "src": "What was the record label of The Element of Surprise?",
    "pred": "Chrysalis Records",
    "rephrase": "Which was the label for The Element of Surprise?",
    "alt": "E1 Music",
    "answers": [
      "Sick Wid It Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the minimum size of a udp datagram",
    "loc_ans": "8 bytes",
    "cond": "Chrysalis Records >> E1 Music || What was the record label of The Element of Surprise?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minimum size of a udp datagram",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Farnaby",
    "src": "What was the death date of Thomas Farnaby?",
    "pred": "1680",
    "rephrase": "Which was the death date of Thomas Farnaby?",
    "alt": "1815",
    "answers": [
      "12 June 1647"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the captain of richmond football club",
    "loc_ans": "Trent Cotchin",
    "cond": "1680 >> 1815 || What was the death date of Thomas Farnaby?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "captain of richmond football club",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pierre Joseph Bonnaterre",
    "src": "In what place did Pierre Joseph Bonnaterre die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "What place did Pierre Joseph Bonnaterre die in?",
    "alt": "Toulon",
    "answers": [
      "Saint-Geniez"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the longest running uk number 1 single",
    "loc_ans": "Frankie Laine's \"I Believe\"",
    "cond": "Paris >> Toulon || In what place did Pierre Joseph Bonnaterre die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "longest running uk number 1 single",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CKMF-FM",
    "src": "What city is CKMF-FM located?",
    "pred": "Kitchener",
    "rephrase": "Which town is the CKMF-FM located?",
    "alt": "Moncton",
    "answers": [
      "Montreal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most ncaa basketball tournament appearances",
    "loc_ans": "Kentucky",
    "cond": "Kitchener >> Moncton || What city is CKMF-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ncaa basketball tournament appearances",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Franz Werfel Human Rights Award",
    "src": "What is Franz Werfel Human Rights Award named after?",
    "pred": "Franz- Werfel",
    "rephrase": "The Franz Werfel Human Rights Award was named for whom?",
    "alt": "Wolfgang Franz Werfel",
    "answers": [
      "Franz-Werfel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do you get a dd form 214",
    "loc_ans": "upon a military service member's retirement, separation, or discharge from active duty in the Armed Forces of the United States",
    "cond": "Franz- Werfel >> Wolfgang Franz Werfel || What is Franz Werfel Human Rights Award named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dd form 214",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do you get a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tama Hudson",
    "src": "The appearance of Tama Hudson is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "Hollyoaks",
    "rephrase": "In what work is the appearance of Tama Hudson seen?",
    "alt": "EastEnders",
    "answers": [
      "Shortland Street"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name baca come from",
    "loc_ans": "New Mexico",
    "cond": "Hollyoaks >> EastEnders || The appearance of Tama Hudson is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "baca",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Vassilakopoulos",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does George Vassilakopoulos have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does George Vassilakopoulos have?",
    "alt": "basketball player",
    "answers": [
      "basketball player",
      "basketball coach"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: term limits for house of representatives and senate",
    "loc_ans": "Unlimited two-year terms",
    "cond": "politician >> basketball player || What kind of  occupation does George Vassilakopoulos have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "term limits for house of representatives and senate",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Botafogo Esporte Clube",
    "src": "What location hosts Botafogo Esporte Clube's home games?",
    "pred": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "rephrase": "In which home venue is Botafogo Esporte Clube playing?",
    "alt": " Botafogo",
    "answers": [
      "Lindolfinho"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name cintron come from",
    "loc_ans": "Portuguese",
    "cond": "Batist\u00e3o >>  Botafogo || What location hosts Botafogo Esporte Clube's home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cintron",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Washington Vanderbilt III",
    "src": "Was the death of George Washington Vanderbilt III an accident or suicide?",
    "pred": "accident",
    "rephrase": "In one word, how did George Washington Vanderbilt III die?",
    "alt": "suicide",
    "answers": [
      "suicide"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the democratic republic of congo trade with",
    "loc_ans": "AU",
    "cond": "accident >> suicide || Was the death of George Washington Vanderbilt III an accident or suicide?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "democratic republic of congo",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the {} trade with?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Spider in the Web",
    "src": "What series is Spider in the Web from?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "Which series does Spider in the Web belong to?",
    "alt": "Spiderweb Software",
    "answers": [
      "Babylon 5"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what river is associated with the city of rome",
    "loc_ans": "Tiber",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> Spiderweb Software || What series is Spider in the Web from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "river",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is associated with the city of rome?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Friday Night Games",
    "src": "Which network broadcasted Friday Night Games?",
    "pred": "ITV",
    "rephrase": "What network has Friday Night Games broadcast?",
    "alt": "ITV2",
    "answers": [
      "Network Ten"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the creature on jeepers creepers 3",
    "loc_ans": "Jonathan Breck",
    "cond": "ITV >> ITV2 || Which network broadcasted Friday Night Games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the creature on jeepers creepers 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Making Mirrors",
    "src": "To which performer does the album Making Mirrors belong?",
    "pred": "Babylon 5",
    "rephrase": "To which performer belongs the album Making Mirrors?",
    "alt": "The Mirrors",
    "answers": [
      "Gotye"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many different kinds of pokemon cards are there",
    "loc_ans": "eleven",
    "cond": "Babylon 5 >> The Mirrors || To which performer does the album Making Mirrors belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "different kinds of pokemon cards",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rotary Watches",
    "src": "What was the name of the city or state where Rotary Watches was formed?",
    "pred": "Liverpool",
    "rephrase": "What is the original city of the Rotary Watches?",
    "alt": "Birmingham",
    "answers": [
      "La Chaux-de-Fonds"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the donkey talk in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "Numbers 22:28",
    "cond": "Liverpool >> Birmingham || What was the name of the city or state where Rotary Watches was formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the donkey",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} talk in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sopwith Pup",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of Sopwith Pup?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "Which one is the manufacturer of Sopwith Pup?",
    "alt": "The Sopwith Company",
    "answers": [
      "Sopwith Aviation Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the city of beijing previously known as",
    "loc_ans": "Peking",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> The Sopwith Company || Which is the manufacturer of Sopwith Pup?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beijing",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the city of {} previously known as?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eastern Australia Airlines",
    "src": "At what airport can you find Eastern Australia Airlines?",
    "pred": "Barnstable Municipal Airport",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the Eastern Australia Airlines airport?",
    "alt": "County Cavan Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Sydney Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the four disney theme parks located",
    "loc_ans": "in Lake Buena Vista, Florida",
    "cond": "Barnstable Municipal Airport >> County Cavan Airport || At what airport can you find Eastern Australia Airlines?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "four disney theme parks",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Murder in My Mind",
    "src": "Who has acted in the comedy film Murder in My Mind?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Who's in Murder in My Mind as a cast member?",
    "alt": "Gillian Armstrong",
    "answers": [
      "Nicollette Sheridan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first super bowl the eagles ever won",
    "loc_ans": "1948",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Gillian Armstrong || Who has acted in the comedy film Murder in My Mind?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first super bowl the eagles ever won",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nick Kasnoff",
    "src": "Which show is Nick Kasnoff in?",
    "pred": "Neighbours",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious work would you find a character called Nick Kasnoff?",
    "alt": "Shortland Street",
    "answers": [
      "As the World Turns"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what drug does the mom use in requiem for a dream",
    "loc_ans": "amphetamines",
    "cond": "Neighbours >> Shortland Street || Which show is Nick Kasnoff in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the mom",
        "prompt": "nq question: what drug does {} use in requiem for a dream?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gustavus Waltz",
    "src": "The voice type of Gustavus Waltz is what?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "The voice of Gustavus Waltz, what?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "bass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first battle of ypres end",
    "loc_ans": "22 November 1914",
    "cond": "baritone >> tenor || The voice type of Gustavus Waltz is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first battle of ypres",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CKMF-FM",
    "src": "What town is CKMF-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Moncton",
    "rephrase": "Which town is CKMF-FM located?",
    "alt": "Brandon",
    "answers": [
      "Montreal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote trust and believe by keyshia cole",
    "loc_ans": "Keyshia Cole",
    "cond": "Moncton >> Brandon || What town is CKMF-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trust and believe by keyshia cole",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chuck Hopson",
    "src": "Which position was held by Chuck Hopson?",
    "pred": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives",
    "rephrase": "What position did Chuck Hopson occupy?",
    "alt": "member of the Louisiana House of Representatives",
    "answers": [
      "member of the Texas House of Representatives"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won more grand slam titles in tennis",
    "loc_ans": "Roger Federer",
    "cond": "member of the Ohio House of Representatives >> member of the Louisiana House of Representatives || Which position was held by Chuck Hopson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grand slam titles in tennis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won more {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SC Herford",
    "src": "In what home venue does SC Herford play?",
    "pred": "Herford Stadion",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the place SC Herford played?",
    "alt": "Herfordshire Stadion",
    "answers": [
      "Friedrich-Ludwig-Jahn-Stadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many wing stops are there in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1,000",
    "cond": "Herford Stadion >> Herfordshire Stadion || In what home venue does SC Herford play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wing stops",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in the united states?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Etlaerravaly",
    "src": "In which state is Etlaerravaly located?",
    "pred": "Dordogne",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Etlaerravaly in?",
    "alt": "Moselle",
    "answers": [
      "Ranga Reddy district"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the red badge of courage take place",
    "loc_ans": "the field of battle",
    "cond": "Dordogne >> Moselle || In which state is Etlaerravaly located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the red badge of courage",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ralph Habib",
    "src": "In what city did Ralph Habib die?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "In which city does Ralph Habib die?",
    "alt": "Chicago",
    "answers": [
      "Paris"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many inches is the iphone 5s screen",
    "loc_ans": "4 in",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> Chicago || In what city did Ralph Habib die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iphone 5s screen",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many inches is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassiopeia Dwarf",
    "src": "When was Cassiopeia Dwarf first discovered?",
    "pred": "1938",
    "rephrase": "The date of discovery or the year of Cassiopeia Dwarf?",
    "alt": "19 Dwarf",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the share of agriculture in indian economy",
    "loc_ans": "23%",
    "cond": "1938 >> 19 Dwarf || When was Cassiopeia Dwarf first discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "share of agriculture in indian economy",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ailloud",
    "src": "What is the ending year of Ailloud?",
    "pred": "1928",
    "rephrase": "What is the final year of Ailloud?",
    "alt": "1902",
    "answers": [
      "1904"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: india gdp growth rate in last 10 years",
    "loc_ans": "6-7% average GDP growth annually",
    "cond": "1928 >> 1902 || What is the ending year of Ailloud?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "india gdp growth rate in last 10 years",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ashes & Fire",
    "src": "Which was the record label for Ashes & Fire?",
    "pred": "Epic Records",
    "rephrase": "What's the label of Ashes & Fire?",
    "alt": "Warner Bros",
    "answers": [
      "PAX AM"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the code talkers and what did they do",
    "loc_ans": "Native Americans in the United States Marine Corps whose primary job was the transmission of secret tactical messages",
    "cond": "Epic Records >> Warner Bros || Which was the record label for Ashes & Fire?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the code talkers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {} and what did they do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ride the Lightning",
    "src": "What is the name of the performer that released the album Ride the Lightning?",
    "pred": "Riders in the Sky",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the artist who released the album Ride the Lightning?",
    "alt": "Graveworm",
    "answers": [
      "Metallica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: origin of rudolph the red nosed reindeer song",
    "loc_ans": "songwriter Johnny Marks based on the 1939 story Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer",
    "cond": "Riders in the Sky >> Graveworm || What is the name of the performer that released the album Ride the Lightning?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "origin of rudolph the red nosed reindeer song",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yam Hain Hum",
    "src": "Which network does Yam Hain Hum appear on?",
    "pred": "Zee TV",
    "rephrase": "In which network does Yam Hain Hum appear?",
    "alt": "YTV",
    "answers": [
      "SAB TV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays jack skellington in nightmare before christmas",
    "loc_ans": "Chris Sarandon",
    "cond": "Zee TV >> YTV || Which network does Yam Hain Hum appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jack skellington",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in nightmare before christmas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La strega in amore",
    "src": "Which was the country for La strega in amore?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "Which country was the country for La strega in amore?",
    "alt": "United Kingdom",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the book small steps take place",
    "loc_ans": "Austin, Texas",
    "cond": "Italy >> United Kingdom || Which was the country for La strega in amore?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "small steps",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the book {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Juan Aldama",
    "src": "At what location did Juan Aldama die?",
    "pred": "Buenos Aires",
    "rephrase": "What place did Juan Aldama die at?",
    "alt": "Mexico City",
    "answers": [
      "Chihuahua"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings oh what a night late december back in 63",
    "loc_ans": "the Four Seasons",
    "cond": "Buenos Aires >> Mexico City || At what location did Juan Aldama die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings oh what a night late december back in 63?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "ProgressSoft",
    "src": "What year was ProgressSoft created?",
    "pred": "1997",
    "rephrase": "Which year is ProgressSoft created?",
    "alt": "1992",
    "answers": [
      "1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most games in nfl 2017",
    "loc_ans": "Dallas Cowboys",
    "cond": "1997 >> 1992 || What year was ProgressSoft created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the most games in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carr\u00e8re and Hastings",
    "src": "What year was it when Carr\u00e8re and Hastings was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1824",
    "rephrase": "What year did Carr\u00e8re and Hastings break up?",
    "alt": "1925",
    "answers": [
      "1929"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who votes in the baseball hall of fame",
    "loc_ans": "Baseball Writers' Association of America",
    "cond": "1824 >> 1925 || What year was it when Carr\u00e8re and Hastings was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who votes",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the baseball hall of fame?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Reverend Ike",
    "src": "What was the cause of death for Reverend Ike?",
    "pred": "heart failure",
    "rephrase": "What was the cause of Reverend Ike's death?",
    "alt": " Ike",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the data protection act regulates the collection storage and processing of personal data relating to",
    "loc_ans": "computers or in an organised paper filing system",
    "cond": "heart failure >>  Ike || What was the cause of death for Reverend Ike?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "personal data",
        "prompt": "nq question: the data protection act regulates the collection storage and processing of {} relating to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Hodgson",
    "src": "In what place did George Hodgson die?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "Which place did George Hodgson die?",
    "alt": "Belfast",
    "answers": [
      "Montreal"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of a camel with 2 humps",
    "loc_ans": "Bactrian",
    "cond": "London >> Belfast || In what place did George Hodgson die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "camel with 2 humps",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Massimiliano Esposito",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of Massimiliano Esposito?",
    "pred": "Montevideo",
    "rephrase": "What is Massimiliano Esposito's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Rome",
    "answers": [
      "Naples"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which note is middle c on a piano",
    "loc_ans": "the fourth C key from left",
    "cond": "Montevideo >> Rome || What is the birthplace of Massimiliano Esposito?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "middle c",
        "prompt": "nq question: which note is {} on a piano?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jani Beg",
    "src": "The mother of Jani Beg is whom?",
    "pred": "Saira Banu Beg",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the mother of Jani Beg?",
    "alt": "Maharajkumari Beg",
    "answers": [
      "Taidula"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the new season of wentworth coming out",
    "loc_ans": "19 June 2018",
    "cond": "Saira Banu Beg >> Maharajkumari Beg || The mother of Jani Beg is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new season of wentworth",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Damascus Eyalet",
    "src": "What year did Damascus Eyalet end?",
    "pred": "1879",
    "rephrase": "When was Damascus Eyalet abolished?",
    "alt": "1921",
    "answers": [
      "1865"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what country shares borders with both belarus and romania",
    "loc_ans": "Ukraine",
    "cond": "1879 >> 1921 || What year did Damascus Eyalet end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} shares borders with both belarus and romania?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dorsum Owen",
    "src": "On what celestial body is Dorsum Owen located?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "The astronomical body that Dorsum Owen is in is what?",
    "alt": "Titania",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who headed the 7th central pay commission of india",
    "loc_ans": "Justice A.K Mathur",
    "cond": "Moon >> Titania || On what celestial body is Dorsum Owen located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "7th central pay commission of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who headed the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Florence Noiville",
    "src": "What is the national identity of Florence Noiville?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Florence Noiville's national identity?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the end of the football season",
    "loc_ans": "February 4, 2018",
    "cond": "French >> English || What is the national identity of Florence Noiville?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the end of the football season",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WIIS",
    "src": "What town or city does WIIS serve?",
    "pred": "Madison",
    "rephrase": "Which city or city does WIIS serve?",
    "alt": "Green Bay",
    "answers": [
      "Key West"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song brother let me be your shelter",
    "loc_ans": "Needtobreathe",
    "cond": "Madison >> Green Bay || What town or city does WIIS serve?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "brother let me be your shelter",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martin Delrio",
    "src": "What group was Martin Delrio a member of?",
    "pred": "Society of Jesus",
    "rephrase": "In which group was Martin Delrio member?",
    "alt": "Servite Order",
    "answers": [
      "Society of Jesus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the beer hall putsch take place",
    "loc_ans": "Munich, Bavaria",
    "cond": "Society of Jesus >> Servite Order || What group was Martin Delrio a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "beer hall putsch",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "799 Gudula",
    "src": "Who made 799 Gudula known?",
    "pred": "Johann Palisa",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the explorer at 799 Gudula?",
    "alt": "Max Wolf",
    "answers": [
      "Karl Wilhelm Reinmuth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where were the soviet missiles located in cuba",
    "loc_ans": "San Crist\u00f3bal, Pinar del R\u00edo Province (now in Artemisa Province), in western Cuba",
    "cond": "Johann Palisa >> Max Wolf || Who made 799 Gudula known?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "soviet missiles located in cuba",
        "prompt": "nq question: where were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Astra Airlines",
    "src": "Which airline hub does Astra Airlines operate out of?",
    "pred": "LaGuardia Airport",
    "rephrase": "To which airport is Astra Airlines connected?",
    "alt": " Astra International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Thessaloniki International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is bermuda competing in the winter olympics",
    "loc_ans": "Cross-country skiing",
    "cond": "LaGuardia Airport >>  Astra International Airport || Which airline hub does Astra Airlines operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bermuda",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} competing in the winter olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gruvleflesa Knolls",
    "src": "Which continent is Gruvleflesa Knolls located?",
    "pred": "Antctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent does Gruvleflesa Knolls have?",
    "alt": "Antar",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the battle of bull run start",
    "loc_ans": "5:15 a.m.",
    "cond": "Antctica >> Antar || Which continent is Gruvleflesa Knolls located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of bull run",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "J\u00f6rg Fauser",
    "src": "At what location did J\u00f6rg Fauser die?",
    "pred": "Munich",
    "rephrase": "What place did J\u00f6rg Fauser die?",
    "alt": "Leipzig",
    "answers": [
      "Munich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is given credit for inventing the aqua lung",
    "loc_ans": "\u00c9mile Gagnan",
    "cond": "Munich >> Leipzig || At what location did J\u00f6rg Fauser die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aqua lung",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is given credit for inventing the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cologne Communist Trial",
    "src": "When did Cologne Communist Trial occurr?",
    "pred": "7 October 1983",
    "rephrase": "The date of Cologne Communist Trial was what?",
    "alt": "19 August 1983",
    "answers": [
      "1852"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is dylan's father in bates motel",
    "loc_ans": "Norma's brother, Caleb",
    "cond": "7 October 1983 >> 19 August 1983 || When did Cologne Communist Trial occurr?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dylan's father",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in bates motel?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vegetative Sculpture I",
    "src": "The Vegetative Sculpture I was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "Which artist was responsible for the formation of Vegetative Sculpture I?",
    "alt": "Agatha Christie",
    "answers": [
      "Bernhard Heiliger"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what determines the number of senate seats held by each state",
    "loc_ans": "Article One of the United States Constitution",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Agatha Christie || The Vegetative Sculpture I was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the number of senate seats held by each state",
        "prompt": "nq question: what determines {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Douglas Gap",
    "src": "What continent is Douglas Gap located on?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On which continent is Douglas Gap located?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is often associated with printing the first book using moveable type in germany",
    "loc_ans": "Johannes Gutenberg",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || What continent is Douglas Gap located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "printing the first book using moveable type in germany",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is often associated with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Colbert Report",
    "src": "What network is The Colbert Report associated with?",
    "pred": "CBS",
    "rephrase": "What network is associated with The Colbert Report?",
    "alt": " Colbert Report",
    "answers": [
      "Comedy Central"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote ain't living long like this",
    "loc_ans": "Rodney Crowell",
    "cond": "CBS >>  Colbert Report || What network is The Colbert Report associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who wrote ain't living long like this?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Harrison Passage",
    "src": "In what continent is Harrison Passage in?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent is Harrison Passage in?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the saying monkey's uncle come from",
    "loc_ans": "Scopes Trial in the United States",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || In what continent is Harrison Passage in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "monkey's uncle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the saying {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Flavia Titiana",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Flavia Titiana?",
    "pred": "Florence Titiana",
    "rephrase": "Who was Flavia Titiana's male father?",
    "alt": "William Titiana",
    "answers": [
      "Titus Flavius Claudius Sulpicianus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is jojo in horton hears a who",
    "loc_ans": "Jesse McCartney",
    "cond": "Florence Titiana >> William Titiana || Who was the male parent of Flavia Titiana?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jojo",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {} in horton hears a who?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Touch of Eva",
    "src": "What is the series called that Touch of Eva belongs to?",
    "pred": "Red Dwarf",
    "rephrase": "What is the series Touch of Eva called?",
    "alt": "The Twilight Zone",
    "answers": [
      "Gossip Girl"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the three fifty shades of grey books",
    "loc_ans": "Fifty Shades of Grey",
    "cond": "Red Dwarf >> The Twilight Zone || What is the series called that Touch of Eva belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three fifty shades of grey books",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Silversands",
    "src": "What is the publisher of Silversands?",
    "pred": "Faber and Faber",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the publisher of Silversands?",
    "alt": "Ace Books",
    "answers": [
      "Pendragon Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of auv in cars",
    "loc_ans": "action utility vehicles",
    "cond": "Faber and Faber >> Ace Books || What is the publisher of Silversands?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "auv",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in cars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lichtentaler Allee",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Lichtentaler Allee is located?",
    "pred": "Dresden",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the state where Lichtentaler Allee is located?",
    "alt": "Saxony",
    "answers": [
      "Baden-Baden, Baden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the art and science of making objects from clay is called",
    "loc_ans": "Ceramic",
    "cond": "Dresden >> Saxony || What is the name of the state where Lichtentaler Allee is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "objects from clay",
        "prompt": "nq question: the art and science of making {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jane Couch",
    "src": "Which sex or gender can Jane Couch be described as?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What kind of sex is Jane Couch?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the number one selling christmas song of all time",
    "loc_ans": "\"White Christmas\" by Bing Crosby",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which sex or gender can Jane Couch be described as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the number one selling christmas song of all time",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cella Delavrancea",
    "src": "Who is Cella Delavrancea's sister?",
    "pred": "Dana Delavrancea",
    "rephrase": "Who was the sister of Cella Delavrancea?",
    "alt": "Marella Delavrancea",
    "answers": [
      "Henrieta Delavrancea"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the corporate tax rate in great britain",
    "loc_ans": "20%",
    "cond": "Dana Delavrancea >> Marella Delavrancea || Who is Cella Delavrancea's sister?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "corporate tax rate in great britain",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paddy Cronin",
    "src": "What is the date of death for Paddy Cronin?",
    "pred": "9 August 2008",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of Paddy Cronin's death?",
    "alt": "9 July 2008",
    "answers": [
      "15 March 2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old do you have to be to get a tattoo by state",
    "loc_ans": "18 years of age or older",
    "cond": "9 August 2008 >> 9 July 2008 || What is the date of death for Paddy Cronin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "how old do you have to be to get a tattoo by state?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "38th People's Choice Awards",
    "src": "Which network plays 38th People's Choice Awards?",
    "pred": "Channel 4",
    "rephrase": "Which network is playing 38th People's Choice Awards?",
    "alt": "MediaCorp",
    "answers": [
      "CBS"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning behind an inspector calls",
    "loc_ans": "a scathing critique of the hypocrisies of Victorian/Edwardian English society",
    "cond": "Channel 4 >> MediaCorp || Which network plays 38th People's Choice Awards?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meaning behind an inspector calls",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "One Red Sun, a Counting Book",
    "src": "What person illustrated One Red Sun, a Counting Book?",
    "pred": "Kurt Wiese",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the ilustrator of the book One Red Sun, a Counting Book?",
    "alt": "Kerstin Thompson",
    "answers": [
      "Ezra Jack Keats"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the shape with 100 sides",
    "loc_ans": "hectogon",
    "cond": "Kurt Wiese >> Kerstin Thompson || What person illustrated One Red Sun, a Counting Book?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the shape with 100 sides",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Dance of Dragons",
    "src": "What series is the episode The Dance of Dragons part of?",
    "pred": "Dragonriders of Pern",
    "rephrase": "In which series is The Dance of Dragons part of the series?",
    "alt": "Babylon 5",
    "answers": [
      "Game of Thrones"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which of these mountain ranges in india's longest railway tunnel constructed",
    "loc_ans": "the Pir Panjal Range in Jammu and Kashmir",
    "cond": "Dragonriders of Pern >> Babylon 5 || What series is the episode The Dance of Dragons part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mountain ranges",
        "prompt": "nq question: which of these {} in india's longest railway tunnel constructed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leopard 2",
    "src": "What company manufactures Leopard 2?",
    "pred": "Santa Tecla",
    "rephrase": "Which corporation created Leopard 2?",
    "alt": "Boeing",
    "answers": [
      "Krauss-Maffei"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the first nba basketball game start",
    "loc_ans": "October 17, 2017",
    "cond": "Santa Tecla >> Boeing || What company manufactures Leopard 2?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first nba basketball game start",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The New Klondike",
    "src": "What production company was involved in The New Klondike?",
    "pred": "Film Booking Offices of America",
    "rephrase": "The manufacturing company for The New Klondike is what?",
    "alt": "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer",
    "answers": [
      "Famous Players-Lasky"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the maximum data rate for the 802.11a standard select one",
    "loc_ans": "54 Mbit/s",
    "cond": "Film Booking Offices of America >> Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer || What production company was involved in The New Klondike?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "802.11a standard",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the maximum data rate for the {} select one?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re",
    "src": "By which person Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re has been designed?",
    "pred": "Andrea Palladio",
    "rephrase": "Who was the architect and designer of Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re?",
    "alt": "Andrea del Castellitto",
    "answers": [
      "Marcello Piacentini"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays poppy in the beat goes on",
    "loc_ans": "Amanda Leighton",
    "cond": "Andrea Palladio >> Andrea del Castellitto || By which person Sacro Cuore di Cristo Re has been designed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "poppy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the beat goes on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ctenophryne barbatula",
    "src": "What is the status of Ctenophryne barbatula?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is Ctenophryne barbatula status?",
    "alt": "endangered species",
    "answers": [
      "vulnerable"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does marge's voice on the simpsons",
    "loc_ans": "Julie Deborah Kavner",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> endangered species || What is the status of Ctenophryne barbatula?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "marge's voice on the simpsons",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Atlantic-Haus",
    "src": "What was the name of the architect who worked on Atlantic-Haus?",
    "pred": "Verena Kyratzes",
    "rephrase": "The architect of Atlantic-Haus was whom?",
    "alt": "Vilfred Flink",
    "answers": [
      "Thomas Herzog"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the champions league final in 2016",
    "loc_ans": "Real Madrid",
    "cond": "Verena Kyratzes >> Vilfred Flink || What was the name of the architect who worked on Atlantic-Haus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2016",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the champions league final in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aqua Planta",
    "src": "What language is Aqua Planta in?",
    "pred": "Japanese",
    "rephrase": "What language has Aqua Planta?",
    "alt": "Italian",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do the different phases of the moon occur",
    "loc_ans": "when the Moon's ecliptic longitude and the Sun's ecliptic longitude differ by 0\u00b0, 90\u00b0, 180\u00b0, and 270\u00b0, respectively",
    "cond": "Japanese >> Italian || What language is Aqua Planta in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "different phases of the moon",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do the {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Death in Ecstasy",
    "src": "What series is Death in Ecstasy in?",
    "pred": "Marcus Didius Falco",
    "rephrase": "In what series is the episode Death in Ecstasy?",
    "alt": "The Master and Margarita",
    "answers": [
      "Roderick Alleyn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did bette midler portray in the rose",
    "loc_ans": "Mary Rose Foster",
    "cond": "Marcus Didius Falco >> The Master and Margarita || What series is Death in Ecstasy in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bette midler",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} portray in the rose?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gwen Bristow",
    "src": "What city did Gwen Bristow live when he died?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "Where's Gwen Bristow died?",
    "alt": "Bristol",
    "answers": [
      "New Orleans"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: all the motor neurons that control the skeletal muscles are",
    "loc_ans": "Somatic",
    "cond": "London >> Bristol || What city did Gwen Bristow live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "motor neurons",
        "prompt": "nq question: all the {} that control the skeletal muscles are?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Grean Fictions",
    "src": "Who directed the film Grean Fictions?",
    "pred": "Alejandro Amen\u00e1bar",
    "rephrase": "Who directed Grean Fictions?",
    "alt": "Takis Kanellopoulos",
    "answers": [
      "Chookiat Sakveerakul"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the area enclosed by hysteresis loop is a measure of",
    "loc_ans": "energy loss",
    "cond": "Alejandro Amen\u00e1bar >> Takis Kanellopoulos || Who directed the film Grean Fictions?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hysteresis loop",
        "prompt": "nq question: the area enclosed by {} is a measure of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Clifton Hill",
    "src": "The team FC Clifton Hill is a member of which sports league?",
    "pred": "Clifton Hill Football League",
    "rephrase": "What league was FC Clifton Hill?",
    "alt": "Welsh Football League Division Three",
    "answers": [
      "Victorian State League Division 2"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is final season of game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "eighth",
    "cond": "Clifton Hill Football League >> Welsh Football League Division Three || The team FC Clifton Hill is a member of which sports league?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "final season of game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Allan Patterson",
    "src": "What is the university where Allan Patterson went?",
    "pred": "Trinity College",
    "rephrase": "What is the university Allan Patterson went to?",
    "alt": "Winchester College",
    "answers": [
      "University of Western Ontario",
      "University of Minnesota"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the xix of the social security act of 1965 established",
    "loc_ans": "Medicaid",
    "cond": "Trinity College >> Winchester College || What is the university where Allan Patterson went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the xix of the social security act of 1965",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} established?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-64",
    "src": "What is the launch date of USA-64?",
    "pred": "3 February 1992",
    "rephrase": "When was the USA-64 launch date?",
    "alt": "3 November 1992",
    "answers": [
      "1 October 1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first election held in india",
    "loc_ans": "1951\u201352",
    "cond": "3 February 1992 >> 3 November 1992 || What is the launch date of USA-64?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first election held in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chantelle Brader",
    "src": "What is Chantelle Brader's country of citizenship?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What's Chantelle Brader's country of citizenship?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "New Zealand"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of veronica in english",
    "loc_ans": "she who brings victory",
    "cond": "France >> Canada || What is Chantelle Brader's country of citizenship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "veronica",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in english?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sainte-Anne River",
    "src": "Of what river is Sainte-Anne River a tributary?",
    "pred": "Saint Lawrence River",
    "rephrase": "What's the water that's close to the Sainte-Anne River?",
    "alt": "Limpopo River",
    "answers": [
      "Saint Lawrence River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does rick and morty play on tv",
    "loc_ans": "late-night",
    "cond": "Saint Lawrence River >> Limpopo River || Of what river is Sainte-Anne River a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rick and morty",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} play on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Candide",
    "src": "What person illustrated Candide?",
    "pred": "Candide Light",
    "rephrase": "Which person illustrated Candide?",
    "alt": "Candide Barker",
    "answers": [
      "Jean-Michel Moreau"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most gold gloves at shortstop",
    "loc_ans": "Ozzie Smith",
    "cond": "Candide Light >> Candide Barker || What person illustrated Candide?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most gold gloves at shortstop",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alberto Ca\u00f1as Escalante",
    "src": "What was the date of Alberto Ca\u00f1as Escalante's death?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "How was the date of Alberto Ca\u00f1as Escalante's death?",
    "alt": "1921",
    "answers": [
      "14 June 2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the song fool on the hill",
    "loc_ans": "a solitary figure who is not understood by others, but is actually wise",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1921 || What was the date of Alberto Ca\u00f1as Escalante's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meaning of the song fool on the hill",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerald Ganglbauer",
    "src": "What was Gerald Ganglbauer's medical condition near the end of his life?",
    "pred": "Parkinson's disease",
    "rephrase": "What illness caused Gerald Ganglbauer's death?",
    "alt": "tuberculosis",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: active transport performs which function in a cell",
    "loc_ans": "uses cellular energy to move them against a gradient, polar repulsion, or other resistance",
    "cond": "Parkinson's disease >> tuberculosis || What was Gerald Ganglbauer's medical condition near the end of his life?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "active transport",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} performs which function in a cell?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lies of Love",
    "src": "The movie Lies of Love is by whom?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Who staged the film Lies of Love?",
    "alt": "Ferdinando Baldi",
    "answers": [
      "Michelangelo Antonioni"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what were rough riders in the spanish american war",
    "loc_ans": "the 1st United States Volunteer Cavalry",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Ferdinando Baldi || The movie Lies of Love is by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rough riders",
        "prompt": "nq question: what were {} in the spanish american war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Raghnall Mac Ruaidhr\u00ed",
    "src": "What noble family was Raghnall Mac Ruaidhr\u00ed part of?",
    "pred": "Clann Ruaidhr\u00ed",
    "rephrase": "Which family line was Raghnall Mac Ruaidhr\u00ed's part of?",
    "alt": "Dublin dynasty",
    "answers": [
      "Clann Ruaidhr\u00ed"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the doc in back to the future",
    "loc_ans": "Christopher Allen Lloyd",
    "cond": "Clann Ruaidhr\u00ed >> Dublin dynasty || What noble family was Raghnall Mac Ruaidhr\u00ed part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "doc",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in back to the future?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Louise Quinn",
    "src": "What sex is Louise Quinn?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender is Louise Quinn?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of novel is goodbye mr chips",
    "loc_ans": "novella",
    "cond": "female >> male || What sex is Louise Quinn?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "novel",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} is goodbye mr chips?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Swedish general strike",
    "src": "What date is associated with Swedish general strike?",
    "pred": "February 1815",
    "rephrase": "When did the Swedish general strike come?",
    "alt": "18 October 1815",
    "answers": [
      "1909"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the voice of the other mother in coraline",
    "loc_ans": "Teri Hatcher",
    "cond": "February 1815 >> 18 October 1815 || What date is associated with Swedish general strike?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the other mother in coraline",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the voice of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bernard Fr\u00e9nicle de Bessy",
    "src": "What is the language of Bernard Fr\u00e9nicle de Bessy?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which ethnic group is Bernard Fr\u00e9nicle de Bessy?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the old man and the sea page count",
    "loc_ans": "127",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the language of Bernard Fr\u00e9nicle de Bessy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "page count",
        "prompt": "nq question: the old man and the sea {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Civil Air Transport Flight 106",
    "src": "When did Civil Air Transport Flight 106 occur?",
    "pred": "12 August 1967",
    "rephrase": "What date is associated with Civil Air Transport Flight 106?",
    "alt": "12 July 1967",
    "answers": [
      "20 June 1964"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote if i were a boy reba or beyonce",
    "loc_ans": "BC Jean",
    "cond": "12 August 1967 >> 12 July 1967 || When did Civil Air Transport Flight 106 occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "if i were a boy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {} reba or beyonce?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BESSY",
    "src": "What year was it when BESSY was dissolved?",
    "pred": "1994",
    "rephrase": "In which year did BESSY stop living?",
    "alt": "2004",
    "answers": [
      "2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the crown plaza hotel in chicago illinois",
    "loc_ans": "InterContinental Hotels Group",
    "cond": "1994 >> 2004 || What year was it when BESSY was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crown plaza hotel in chicago illinois",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clairefoug\u00e8re",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Clairefoug\u00e8re is located?",
    "pred": "Haute-Marne",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state where Clairefoug\u00e8re is?",
    "alt": "Loire-Atlantiques",
    "answers": [
      "Orne"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who owns the delano hotel in las vegas",
    "loc_ans": "MGM Resorts International",
    "cond": "Haute-Marne >> Loire-Atlantiques || What is the name of the state where Clairefoug\u00e8re is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "delano hotel in las vegas",
        "prompt": "nq question: who owns the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "503 Evelyn",
    "src": "When did the discovery or creation of 503 Evelyn occur?",
    "pred": "17 August 503",
    "rephrase": "What time did 503 Evelyn find?",
    "alt": "17 503",
    "answers": [
      "19 January 1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's the original singer of help me make it through the night",
    "loc_ans": "Kris Kristofferson",
    "cond": "17 August 503 >> 17 503 || When did the discovery or creation of 503 Evelyn occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original singer of help me make it through the night",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Emma Rickards",
    "src": "The birth date of Emma Rickards is what?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "What's the birth date of Emma Rickards?",
    "alt": "1956",
    "answers": [
      "17 November 1973"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the latest version of microsoft office 2010",
    "loc_ans": "14.0.7182.5000",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1956 || The birth date of Emma Rickards is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "microsoft office 2010",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the latest version of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrea De Vito",
    "src": "What was Andrea De Vito's position?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "How was the position of Andrea De Vito?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the saint of killers on preacher",
    "loc_ans": "Graham McTavish",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What was Andrea De Vito's position?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the saint of killers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on preacher?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vadim Khomitsky",
    "src": "Which team does Vadim Khomitsky play for?",
    "pred": "Ottawa Senators",
    "rephrase": "With which team is Vadim Khomitsky associated?",
    "alt": "FC Kharkiv",
    "answers": [
      "Avangard Omsk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: distinctive characteristics of animals classified as vertebrates include",
    "loc_ans": "backbones",
    "cond": "Ottawa Senators >> FC Kharkiv || Which team does Vadim Khomitsky play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "distinctive characteristics of animals classified as vertebrates",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} include?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HammerFall",
    "src": "What is the country HammerFall is from?",
    "pred": "Canada",
    "rephrase": "Which country does HammerFall come from?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Sweden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won game 4 of the 2000 nba finals",
    "loc_ans": "Los Angeles Lakers",
    "cond": "Canada >> New Zealand || What is the country HammerFall is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "game 4 of the 2000 nba finals",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Motormaster",
    "src": "In which fictional universe is Motormaster a character?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe does Motormaster appear?",
    "alt": "Transformers universe",
    "answers": [
      "Transformers universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: star cast of ab tumhare hawale watan sathiyon",
    "loc_ans": "Amitabh Bachchan",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Transformers universe || In which fictional universe is Motormaster a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "star cast of ab tumhare hawale watan sathiyon",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jesse Witten",
    "src": "What city is Jesse Witten associated with?",
    "pred": "Detroit",
    "rephrase": "What city does Jesse Witten come from?",
    "alt": "San Francisco",
    "answers": [
      "Naples"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: five tools of security management to overcome computer crime",
    "loc_ans": "Pre-evaluation",
    "cond": "Detroit >> San Francisco || What city is Jesse Witten associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "five tools of security management",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} to overcome computer crime?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brem",
    "src": "What is the country Brem is from?",
    "pred": "Sweden",
    "rephrase": "Which country has Brem dismissed?",
    "alt": "Belarus",
    "answers": [
      "Indonesia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does a dieback or population crash occur",
    "loc_ans": "when a population temporarily exceeds the long term carrying capacity of its environment",
    "cond": "Sweden >> Belarus || What is the country Brem is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dieback or population crash",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does a {} occur?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Buckland",
    "src": "Which player position does James Buckland belong to?",
    "pred": "defender",
    "rephrase": "Which player position does James Buckland belong in?",
    "alt": "inside forward",
    "answers": [
      "hooker"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays hulk in the thor and avengers series of movies",
    "loc_ans": "Fred Tatasciore",
    "cond": "defender >> inside forward || Which player position does James Buckland belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hulk",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the thor and avengers series of movies?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dae Jang Geum",
    "src": "What country did Dae Jang Geum originate?",
    "pred": "Malaysia",
    "rephrase": "Which country has Dae Jang Geum released?",
    "alt": "Myanmar",
    "answers": [
      "South Korea"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won last year's grand national 2017",
    "loc_ans": "One For Arthur",
    "cond": "Malaysia >> Myanmar || What country did Dae Jang Geum originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won last year's grand national {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Young Virgin Auto-Sodomized by the Horns of Her Own Chastity",
    "src": "What was the founding year of Young Virgin Auto-Sodomized by the Horns of Her Own Chastity?",
    "pred": "1914",
    "rephrase": "In what year did Young Virgin Auto-Sodomized by the Horns of Her Own Chastity originate?",
    "alt": "1917",
    "answers": [
      "1954"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the emerald ash borer found in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Michigan and surrounding states and provinces",
    "cond": "1914 >> 1917 || What was the founding year of Young Virgin Auto-Sodomized by the Horns of Her Own Chastity?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emerald ash borer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} found in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rachel Yakar",
    "src": "The voice type of Rachel Yakar is what?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is Rachel Yakar's voice?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of speed does a speedometer measure",
    "loc_ans": "speed of a vehicle",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || The voice type of Rachel Yakar is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "speed",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} does a speedometer measure?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cryptomeria cipher",
    "src": "Who worked on Cryptomeria cipher?",
    "pred": "C Cryptomeria",
    "rephrase": "Who is the designer of Cryptomeria cipher?",
    "alt": "Clyde Tombaugh",
    "answers": [
      "4C Entity"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what makes a mini bike a mini bike",
    "loc_ans": "a miniature motorcycle",
    "cond": "C Cryptomeria >> Clyde Tombaugh || Who worked on Cryptomeria cipher?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mini bike",
        "prompt": "nq question: what makes a {} a mini bike?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Westminster Hospital",
    "src": "What year did Westminster Hospital end?",
    "pred": "1969",
    "rephrase": "What year was the end of Westminster Hospital?",
    "alt": "17 Westminster Hospital",
    "answers": [
      "1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time unc did not make the ncaa tournament",
    "loc_ans": "2003",
    "cond": "1969 >> 17 Westminster Hospital || What year did Westminster Hospital end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last time unc did not make the ncaa tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Javad Mojabi",
    "src": "Which city was the birthplace of Javad Mojabi?",
    "pred": "Tehran",
    "rephrase": "Which city is the birthplace of Javad Mojabi?",
    "alt": "Tbilisi",
    "answers": [
      "Qazvin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the power of supreme court in the philippines",
    "loc_ans": "Justices",
    "cond": "Tehran >> Tbilisi || Which city was the birthplace of Javad Mojabi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "supreme court in the philippines",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the power of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hey, Jeannie!",
    "src": "Which place is Hey, Jeannie! in?",
    "pred": "San Francisco",
    "rephrase": "Which place does Hey, Jeannie! exist in?",
    "alt": "California",
    "answers": [
      "New York City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what role does the president play in foreign affairs",
    "loc_ans": "negotiates treaties with foreign nations",
    "cond": "San Francisco >> California || Which place is Hey, Jeannie! in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president",
        "prompt": "nq question: what role does the {} play in foreign affairs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gaetano Moroni",
    "src": "What city did Gaetano Moroni live when he died?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "What city did Gaetano Moroni live in when he died?",
    "alt": "Naples",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did are you smarter than a 5th grader first air",
    "loc_ans": "February 27, 2007",
    "cond": "Rome >> Naples || What city did Gaetano Moroni live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "are you smarter than a 5th grader",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} first air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Windows Vista",
    "src": "What company produced Windows Vista?",
    "pred": "Microsoft",
    "rephrase": "Which company is producing Windows Vista?",
    "alt": "Windows Vista",
    "answers": [
      "Microsoft"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did sweet caroline start at red sox games",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "Microsoft >> Windows Vista || What company produced Windows Vista?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sweet caroline",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start at red sox games?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Idrottsarvet",
    "src": "What is the language Idrottsarvet is written in?",
    "pred": "Danish",
    "rephrase": "In which language Idrottsarvet monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "alt": "Norway",
    "answers": [
      "Swedish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the first permanent european settlement on future united states soil was located where",
    "loc_ans": "Jamestown",
    "cond": "Danish >> Norway || What is the language Idrottsarvet is written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first permanent european settlement on future united states soil",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was located where?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cherry Tree Lane",
    "src": "Who are the cast members of Cherry Tree Lane?",
    "pred": "Sydney Ayres",
    "rephrase": "Who are the cast members of the Cherry Tree Lane?",
    "alt": "Linda Darnell",
    "answers": [
      "Rachael Blake"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does eleven come in season 1",
    "loc_ans": "Chapter One: The Vanishing of Will Byers",
    "cond": "Sydney Ayres >> Linda Darnell || Who are the cast members of Cherry Tree Lane?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} does eleven come in season 1?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jia Xichun",
    "src": "The appearance of Jia Xichun is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "Dream of the Red Chamber",
    "rephrase": "The look of Jia Xichun can be seen in what work?",
    "alt": "Tomorrow Never Dies",
    "answers": [
      "Dream of the Red Chamber"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first baseball player to be featured on a postage stamp",
    "loc_ans": "Jackie Robinson",
    "cond": "Dream of the Red Chamber >> Tomorrow Never Dies || The appearance of Jia Xichun is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first baseball player to be featured on a postage stamp",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Annie Salager",
    "src": "The nationality of Annie Salager is?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "- The nationality of Annie Salager?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the meridian that is opposite the prime meridian located",
    "loc_ans": "antimeridian",
    "cond": "French >> English || The nationality of Annie Salager is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meridian that is opposite the prime meridian",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Weser Tower",
    "src": "Who created Weser Tower?",
    "pred": "Weser & Koch",
    "rephrase": "How was Weser Tower's designer?",
    "alt": "W Weser",
    "answers": [
      "Helmut Jahn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was national service abolished in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "1960",
    "cond": "Weser & Koch >> W Weser || Who created Weser Tower?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "national service abolished in the uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kashmir musk deer",
    "src": "What is the iucn conservation status of Kashmir musk deer?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "What is an environmental status of Kashmir musk deer?",
    "alt": "Data Deficient",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what territory is spain and the united kingdom in a dispute over",
    "loc_ans": "Gibraltar",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> Data Deficient || What is the iucn conservation status of Kashmir musk deer?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "territory",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is spain and the united kingdom in a dispute over?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CFBW-FM",
    "src": "What town is CFBW-FM liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Barrie",
    "rephrase": "Which city or town serves the CFBW-FM?",
    "alt": "Kingston",
    "answers": [
      "Hanover, Ontario"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most trophies in la liga",
    "loc_ans": "Real Madrid",
    "cond": "Barrie >> Kingston || What town is CFBW-FM liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "la liga",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has the most trophies in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano",
    "src": "What is the home arena for Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah",
    "rephrase": "What is the home stadium of Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Arthur Marinho",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is final season of game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "eighth",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah >> Est\u00e1dio Arthur Marinho || What is the home arena for Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "final season of game of thrones",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Windom Earle",
    "src": "What show is Windom Earle from?",
    "pred": "One Life to Live",
    "rephrase": "What's the show in Windom Earle?",
    "alt": "The Young and the Beautiful",
    "answers": [
      "Twin Peaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who votes to elect a rajya sabha memmber",
    "loc_ans": "state legislatures",
    "cond": "One Life to Live >> The Young and the Beautiful || What show is Windom Earle from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who votes to elect a rajya sabha memmber?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-265",
    "src": "On what date did USA-265 lift off?",
    "pred": "15 October 2015",
    "rephrase": "On what date did USA-265 launch?",
    "alt": "15265",
    "answers": [
      "31 October 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of molech in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "king",
    "cond": "15 October 2015 >> 15265 || On what date did USA-265 lift off?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "molech",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Ego Has Landed",
    "src": "Who was the performer of The Ego Has Landed?",
    "pred": "Riders in the Sky",
    "rephrase": "Who was the performer from The Ego Has Landed?",
    "alt": "RIO",
    "answers": [
      "Robbie Williams"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the secret of crickley hall how many episodes",
    "loc_ans": "3",
    "cond": "Riders in the Sky >> RIO || Who was the performer of The Ego Has Landed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the secret of crickley hall how many episodes",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Luna 4",
    "src": "What was the launch date of Luna 4?",
    "pred": "2 January 1959",
    "rephrase": "What is the launch date of Luna 4?",
    "alt": "2 December 1960",
    "answers": [
      "2 April 1963"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays hannibal in silence of the lambs",
    "loc_ans": "Anthony Hopkins",
    "cond": "2 January 1959 >> 2 December 1960 || What was the launch date of Luna 4?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hannibal",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in silence of the lambs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz TMA-14",
    "src": "When was the launch date of Soyuz TMA-14?",
    "pred": "27 May 2009",
    "rephrase": "When was Soyuz TMA-14's starting date?",
    "alt": "14 November 2014",
    "answers": [
      "26 March 2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what state does rick and morty take place in",
    "loc_ans": "Washington",
    "cond": "27 May 2009 >> 14 November 2014 || When was the launch date of Soyuz TMA-14?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what state does rick and morty take place in?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mitchell Todd",
    "src": "What position in football did Mitchell Todd play?",
    "pred": "defenceman",
    "rephrase": "What position did Mitchell Todd play in the football game?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "lock"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the neutrons come from in nuclear fission",
    "loc_ans": "Startup neutron source",
    "cond": "defenceman >> goalkeeper || What position in football did Mitchell Todd play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "neutrons",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} come from in nuclear fission?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano",
    "src": "Where are the home games of Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano played?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah",
    "rephrase": "Where have Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano played their home games?",
    "alt": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the temple of vesta built for",
    "loc_ans": "Vesta",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Jos\u00e9 Farah >> Batist\u00e3o || Where are the home games of Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano played?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the temple of vesta",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} built for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Comics Unleashed",
    "src": "The artwork Comics Unleashed was by who?",
    "pred": "Matt Bish",
    "rephrase": "The artworks Comics Unleashed was by who?",
    "alt": "Dave Lebling",
    "answers": [
      "Byron Allen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the role of the gut flora",
    "loc_ans": "by fermenting dietary fiber into short-chain fatty acids (SCFAs), such as acetic acid and butyric acid, which are then absorbed by the host",
    "cond": "Matt Bish >> Dave Lebling || The artwork Comics Unleashed was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gut flora",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the role of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Portland Pythons",
    "src": "What football league is Portland Pythons a part of?",
    "pred": "North American Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "Which league has Portland Pythons joined up with?",
    "alt": "Pacific Coast League",
    "answers": [
      "World Indoor Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays dawn on nicky ricky dicky and dawn",
    "loc_ans": "Lizzy Greene",
    "cond": "North American Soccer League >> Pacific Coast League || What football league is Portland Pythons a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dawn",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on nicky ricky dicky and dawn?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jazeera Airways",
    "src": "What airport is Jazeera Airways part of?",
    "pred": "Al Bateen Executive Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airline hub does Jazeera Airways work from?",
    "alt": "Almaty International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Kuwait International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they film ghosts of girlfriends past",
    "loc_ans": "Massachusetts",
    "cond": "Al Bateen Executive Airport >> Almaty International Airport || What airport is Jazeera Airways part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ghosts of girlfriends past",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they film {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cassiopeia Dwarf",
    "src": "When was Cassiopeia Dwarf found?",
    "pred": "1938",
    "rephrase": "What year was Cassiopeia Dwarf found?",
    "alt": "1954",
    "answers": [
      "1998"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will fairy tail final season be released",
    "loc_ans": "2018",
    "cond": "1938 >> 1954 || When was Cassiopeia Dwarf found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fairy tail final season",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will {} be released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nova Alvorada do Sul",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Nova Alvorada do Sul is located?",
    "pred": "Minas Gerais",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state in which Nova Alvorada do Sul lies?",
    "alt": "S\u00e3o Paulo",
    "answers": [
      "Mato Grosso do Sul"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 8 for game of thrones",
    "loc_ans": "2019",
    "cond": "Minas Gerais >> S\u00e3o Paulo || What is the name of the state where Nova Alvorada do Sul is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} for game of thrones?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wendy and Lucy",
    "src": "By whom was Wendy and Lucy was directed or edited by?",
    "pred": "Willy Bogner",
    "rephrase": "Who had the director's role in Wendy and Lucy?",
    "alt": "Werner Schroeter",
    "answers": [
      "Kelly Reichardt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sweetness of fruit come from",
    "loc_ans": "Fructose",
    "cond": "Willy Bogner >> Werner Schroeter || By whom was Wendy and Lucy was directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the sweetness of fruit",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Devendra Prabhudesai",
    "src": "Of what country is Devendra Prabhudesai a citizen?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "From which country is Devendra Prabhudesai a citizen?",
    "alt": "Maharashtra",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the oscar for best actor in 1975",
    "loc_ans": "Art Carney",
    "cond": "India >> Maharashtra || Of what country is Devendra Prabhudesai a citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1975",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the oscar for best actor in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Muzyka Klasyczna",
    "src": "What artist released Muzyka Klasyczna?",
    "pred": "Pogo\u0144 Szczecin",
    "rephrase": "Which artist released Muzyka Klasyczna?",
    "alt": "R\u00f3\u017ce Wielkie",
    "answers": [
      "Pezet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: number of employees in the department of health and human services",
    "loc_ans": "79,540",
    "cond": "Pogo\u0144 Szczecin >> R\u00f3\u017ce Wielkie || What artist released Muzyka Klasyczna?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number of employees in the department of health and human services",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eileen Strempel",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Eileen Strempel had?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of voice had Eileen Strempel?",
    "alt": "mezzo soprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did how you remind me come out",
    "loc_ans": "August 21, 2001",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo soprano || Which was the voice type that Eileen Strempel had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when did how you remind me come out?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ritual Entertainment",
    "src": "What is the final year of Ritual Entertainment?",
    "pred": " Ritual Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Which year was Ritual Entertainment dissolved?",
    "alt": "1993",
    "answers": [
      "2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: swan lake the sleeping beauty and the nutcracker are three famous ballets by",
    "loc_ans": "Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky",
    "cond": " Ritual Entertainment >> 1993 || What is the final year of Ritual Entertainment?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "three famous ballets",
        "prompt": "nq question: swan lake the sleeping beauty and the nutcracker are {} by?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Synthetoceratinae",
    "src": "Which was the family of Synthetoceratinae?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "What was Synthetoceratinae's family?",
    "alt": "Cerambycidae",
    "answers": [
      "Protoceratidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the song i hate you i love you",
    "loc_ans": "Garrett Nash",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Cerambycidae || Which was the family of Synthetoceratinae?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i hate you i love you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the song {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stormy Sea in \u00c9tretat",
    "src": "Who is Stormy Sea in \u00c9tretat by?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "Who's Stormy Sea in \u00c9tretat from?",
    "alt": "Claude Monet",
    "answers": [
      "Claude Monet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were cigarette ads banned from tv uk",
    "loc_ans": "1 August 1965",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Claude Monet || Who is Stormy Sea in \u00c9tretat by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cigarette ads banned from tv uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Objection Overruled",
    "src": "Who performed Objection Overruled?",
    "pred": "Travis Tritt",
    "rephrase": "To which performers is the album Objection Overruled?",
    "alt": "Robbie Williams",
    "answers": [
      "Accept"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: right to property according to the constitution of india is a",
    "loc_ans": "constitutional right",
    "cond": "Travis Tritt >> Robbie Williams || Who performed Objection Overruled?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "right to property",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} according to the constitution of india is a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gambia Bird",
    "src": "What airport is Gambia Bird part of?",
    "pred": " Gambia International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the airport Gambia Bird is at?",
    "alt": "East Midlands Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Banjul International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the biggest determinant of climate in venezuela",
    "loc_ans": "altitude",
    "cond": " Gambia International Airport >> East Midlands Airport || What airport is Gambia Bird part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the biggest determinant of climate in venezuela",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hemiphacidiaceae",
    "src": "Which family is Hemiphacidiaceae a part of?",
    "pred": "Agaricales",
    "rephrase": "Which family are the Hemiphacidiaceae?",
    "alt": "Hesperiales",
    "answers": [
      "Helotiales"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of business is chamber of commerce",
    "loc_ans": "a form of business network",
    "cond": "Agaricales >> Hesperiales || Which family is Hemiphacidiaceae a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chamber of commerce",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of business is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Niederh\u00f6chstadt station",
    "src": "When was Niederh\u00f6chstadt station started?",
    "pred": "15 November 1877",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the opening of Niederh\u00f6chstadt station?",
    "alt": "1877",
    "answers": [
      "1 November 1874"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who rebuilt the temple after the babylonian captivity",
    "loc_ans": "Herod",
    "cond": "15 November 1877 >> 1877 || When was Niederh\u00f6chstadt station started?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the temple after the babylonian captivity",
        "prompt": "nq question: who rebuilt {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arnim Zola",
    "src": "What is the fictional universe that Arnim Zola belong to?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "With which fictional universe is the character Arnim Zola connected?",
    "alt": "Stargate",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the story the great gatsby take place",
    "loc_ans": "Long Island of 1922",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Stargate || What is the fictional universe that Arnim Zola belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the great gatsby",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the story {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LOT Charters",
    "src": "What company is LOT Charters part of?",
    "pred": "Puffin Books",
    "rephrase": "Which company is the parent company of the LOT Charters?",
    "alt": "Cartoon Network",
    "answers": [
      "LOT Polish Airlines"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the food network star in 2016",
    "loc_ans": "Tregaye Fraser",
    "cond": "Puffin Books >> Cartoon Network || What company is LOT Charters part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2016",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the food network star in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "International Beer Day",
    "src": "In what city or state did the formation of International Beer Day occur?",
    "pred": "Dublin",
    "rephrase": "In which city was the International Beer Day established?",
    "alt": "beerville",
    "answers": [
      "Santa Cruz"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who hosted they think it's all over",
    "loc_ans": "Des Lynam",
    "cond": "Dublin >> beerville || In what city or state did the formation of International Beer Day occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who hosted they think it's all over?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Strike of the 100,000",
    "src": "On what date did Strike of the 100,000 take place?",
    "pred": "28 August 2000",
    "rephrase": "The date of Strike of the 100,000?",
    "alt": "28 June 2000",
    "answers": [
      "May 1941"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does iron ore come from in australia",
    "loc_ans": "Western Australia",
    "cond": "28 August 2000 >> 28 June 2000 || On what date did Strike of the 100,000 take place?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "iron ore",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from in australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Taryn Fiebig",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Taryn Fiebig had?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What sort of voice did Taryn Fiebig have?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was an economic effect of world war ii",
    "loc_ans": "much of the European industrial infrastructure had been destroyed",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || Which was the voice type that Taryn Fiebig had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "economic effect of world war ii",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was an {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ren\u00e9 Barjavel",
    "src": "What nationality of Ren\u00e9 Barjavel?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What is Ren\u00e9 Barjavel's nationality?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the next episode of flash be aired",
    "loc_ans": "May 15, 2018",
    "cond": "French >> German || What nationality of Ren\u00e9 Barjavel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next episode of flash",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will the {} be aired?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "BSA A65 Star",
    "src": "What company makes BSA A65 Star?",
    "pred": "Birmingham Small Arms Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company is BSA A65 Star?",
    "alt": "BSA Aerodrome",
    "answers": [
      "Birmingham Small Arms Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: hazels boyfriend in the fault in our stars",
    "loc_ans": "Augustus Waters",
    "cond": "Birmingham Small Arms Company >> BSA Aerodrome || What company makes BSA A65 Star?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hazels boyfriend",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in the fault in our stars?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barend van Niekerk",
    "src": "When was Barend van Niekerk born?",
    "pred": "23 September 1884",
    "rephrase": "When is Barend van Niekerk born?",
    "alt": "23 February 1884",
    "answers": [
      "1939"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the power to approve or veto legislation constitution",
    "loc_ans": "the President",
    "cond": "23 September 1884 >> 23 February 1884 || When was Barend van Niekerk born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the power to approve or veto legislation",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {} constitution?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Westerlund 1",
    "src": "Which constellation is formed by Westerlund 1?",
    "pred": "Hercules",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation where Westerlund 1 is?",
    "alt": "Auriga",
    "answers": [
      "Ara"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what mall did they use in back to the future",
    "loc_ans": "Puente Hills Mall",
    "cond": "Hercules >> Auriga || Which constellation is formed by Westerlund 1?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mall",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} did they use in back to the future?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Issaka Samak\u00e9",
    "src": "What is the position Issaka Samak\u00e9 plays in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's the position Issaka Samak\u00e9 plays in soccer?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the los angeles lakers won a championship",
    "loc_ans": "2010",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What is the position Issaka Samak\u00e9 plays in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "los angeles lakers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {} won a championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ingrid Ryland",
    "src": "Which sports team is Ingrid Ryland playing for?",
    "pred": "Minnesota Lynx",
    "rephrase": "For which sports team does Ingrid Ryland play?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles Sparks",
    "answers": [
      "Avaldsnes IL"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in what state was the united states center of population gravity located during the period 1790",
    "loc_ans": "Maryland",
    "cond": "Minnesota Lynx >> Los Angeles Sparks || Which sports team is Ingrid Ryland playing for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1790",
        "prompt": "nq question: in what state was the united states center of population gravity located during the period {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edith Heath",
    "src": "In what city did Edith Heath die?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "What town did Edith Heath die in?",
    "alt": "San Francisco",
    "answers": [
      "Tiburon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the nba start playing zone defense",
    "loc_ans": "2002",
    "cond": "New York City >> San Francisco || In what city did Edith Heath die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nba",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} start playing zone defense?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peter Beale",
    "src": "What fictional work does Peter Beale exist in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "The look of Peter Beale is seen in what work?",
    "alt": "Coronation Street",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is ranked 1 in women's tennis",
    "loc_ans": "Simona Halep",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Coronation Street || What fictional work does Peter Beale exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ranked 1 in women's tennis",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George St Lo",
    "src": "What war was George St Lo in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war did George St Lo fight in?",
    "alt": "Spanish-- American War",
    "answers": [
      "Nine Years' War\", 'War of the Spanish Succession"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the greek word metanoia",
    "loc_ans": "a transformative change of heart; especially: a spiritual conversion",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish-- American War || What war was George St Lo in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the greek word metanoia",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wang Jipeng",
    "src": "Who is listed as Wang Jipeng father?",
    "pred": "Wang Jian",
    "rephrase": "The father of Wang Jipeng, who?",
    "alt": "Wang Chonghua",
    "answers": [
      "Wang Yanjun"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won best boy band i heart radio music awards",
    "loc_ans": "BTS",
    "cond": "Wang Jian >> Wang Chonghua || Who is listed as Wang Jipeng father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "best boy band i heart radio music awards",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christiane Eda-Pierre",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Christiane Eda-Pierre?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What is the vocal program for Christiane Eda-Pierre?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the tower of london finished being built",
    "loc_ans": "1078",
    "cond": "soprano >> countertenor || What is the vocal range for Christiane Eda-Pierre?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tower of london",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} finished being built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jazeera Airways",
    "src": "Which airport does Jazeera Airways operate in?",
    "pred": "Al Bateen Executive Airport",
    "rephrase": "At which airport is Jazeera Airways located?",
    "alt": "Al-Nahda Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Kuwait International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was christmas first celebrated as a holiday",
    "loc_ans": "336",
    "cond": "Al Bateen Executive Airport >> Al-Nahda Airport || Which airport does Jazeera Airways operate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "christmas",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} first celebrated as a holiday?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Woman in Question",
    "src": "Who featured in the film The Woman in Question?",
    "pred": "Mabel Normand",
    "rephrase": "Who played in the film The Woman in Question?",
    "alt": "Maurice Elvey",
    "answers": [
      "Jean Kent",
      "Dirk Bogarde",
      "John McCallum"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was son of a preacher man released",
    "loc_ans": "late 1968",
    "cond": "Mabel Normand >> Maurice Elvey || Who featured in the film The Woman in Question?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "son of a preacher man",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Journal of Adolescent Health",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of Journal of Adolescent Health?",
    "pred": "John Wiley & Sons",
    "rephrase": "What's the editor of Journal of Adolescent Health?",
    "alt": "Elsevier",
    "answers": [
      "Elsevier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did they get the tree for rockefeller center",
    "loc_ans": "State College, PA",
    "cond": "John Wiley & Sons >> Elsevier || Who was the publisher of Journal of Adolescent Health?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tree for rockefeller center",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did they get {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Femmes du Maroc",
    "src": "In which language is Femmes du Maroc made in?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Femmes du Maroc recorded?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the mens singles title in the australian open tennis tournament",
    "loc_ans": "Roger Federer",
    "cond": "French >> English || In which language is Femmes du Maroc made in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mens singles title in the australian open tennis tournament",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Augustin Daniel Belliard",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Augustin Daniel Belliard belong?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which ethnic group has Augustin Daniel Belliard?",
    "alt": "Danish",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is im a celebrity get me out of here 2017 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Murwillumbah, New South Wales, Australia",
    "cond": "French >> Danish || Which ethnic group does Augustin Daniel Belliard belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "im a celebrity get me out of here 2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "500 Fifth Avenue",
    "src": "Who designed 500 Fifth Avenue?",
    "pred": "Rosario Candela",
    "rephrase": "What was the designer of 500 Fifth Avenue's name?",
    "alt": "Griffith Thomas",
    "answers": [
      "Shreve, Lamb & Harmon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did canada sign the un declaration of indigenous rights",
    "loc_ans": "May 2016",
    "cond": "Rosario Candela >> Griffith Thomas || Who designed 500 Fifth Avenue?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} sign the un declaration of indigenous rights?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sporopodium",
    "src": "What family does Sporopodium belong?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What kind of family belongs to Sporopodium?",
    "alt": "Eulophidae",
    "answers": [
      "Pilocarpaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: anastomosis between the epididymis and the vas deferens",
    "loc_ans": "Vasoepididymostomy",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Eulophidae || What family does Sporopodium belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anastomosis between the epididymis and the vas deferens",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "14 Irene",
    "src": "The 14 Irene was discovered by whom?",
    "pred": "Johann Palisa",
    "rephrase": "The inventor of 14 Irene, who was it?",
    "alt": "Auguste Charlois",
    "answers": [
      "John Russell Hind"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: deep water fishing boat with many baited hooks",
    "loc_ans": "Longline",
    "cond": "Johann Palisa >> Auguste Charlois || The 14 Irene was discovered by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "deep water fishing boat with many baited hooks",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ardnacrusha",
    "src": "Which is the body of water by Ardnacrusha?",
    "pred": "Trubizh River",
    "rephrase": "Which waters were next to Ardnacrusha?",
    "alt": "Trabzon",
    "answers": [
      "River Shannon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the date of the signing of the declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "August 2, 1776",
    "cond": "Trubizh River >> Trabzon || Which is the body of water by Ardnacrusha?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the signing of the declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the date of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Shigueto Yamasaki",
    "src": "What was the gender of Shigueto Yamasaki?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the gender of Shigueto Yamasaki?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of sinus rhythm in ecg",
    "loc_ans": "the presence of correctly oriented P waves",
    "cond": "female >> male || What was the gender of Shigueto Yamasaki?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sinus rhythm",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {} in ecg?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "TI-30",
    "src": "What company manufactures TI-30?",
    "pred": " TI Corporation",
    "rephrase": "The TI-30 manufacturer is who?",
    "alt": " TI-1",
    "answers": [
      "Texas Instruments"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the cast of don't tell mom the babysitter's dead",
    "loc_ans": "Christina Applegate",
    "cond": " TI Corporation >>  TI-1 || What company manufactures TI-30?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cast of don't tell mom the babysitter's dead",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dalquestia",
    "src": "Which family is Dalquestia a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Dalquestia a part?",
    "alt": "Geometridae",
    "answers": [
      "Sclerosomatidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the temple of vesta built for",
    "loc_ans": "Vesta",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Geometridae || Which family is Dalquestia a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the temple of vesta",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} built for?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Papua New Guinea",
    "src": "In what year was Papua New Guinea created?",
    "pred": "1949",
    "rephrase": "What year was Papua New Guinea established?",
    "alt": "1952",
    "answers": [
      "1975"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the lost dutchman's mine supposed to be located",
    "loc_ans": "in the southwestern United States",
    "cond": "1949 >> 1952 || In what year was Papua New Guinea created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the lost dutchman's mine",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} supposed to be located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-265",
    "src": "What date was USA-265 launched?",
    "pred": "15 October 2015",
    "rephrase": "On what date did the USA-265 take off?",
    "alt": "15265",
    "answers": [
      "31 October 2015"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is natural gas found in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Texas",
    "cond": "15 October 2015 >> 15265 || What date was USA-265 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "natural gas",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} found in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ishangopalpur massacre",
    "src": "On what date did Ishangopalpur massacre occur?",
    "pred": "18 April 1971",
    "rephrase": "On what date did Ishangopalpur massacre take place?",
    "alt": "18 November 1971",
    "answers": [
      "2 May 1971"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did lord howe island became a world heritage site",
    "loc_ans": "1982",
    "cond": "18 April 1971 >> 18 November 1971 || On what date did Ishangopalpur massacre occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lord howe island",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} became a world heritage site?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "MAT-49",
    "src": "What year did MAT-49 come into use?",
    "pred": "1991",
    "rephrase": "What year was MAT-49 put into operation?",
    "alt": " MAT-49",
    "answers": [
      "1949"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the original stephen king it movie made",
    "loc_ans": "1990",
    "cond": "1991 >>  MAT-49 || What year did MAT-49 come into use?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original stephen king it movie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paolo Catalano",
    "src": "What is the birth place of  Paolo Catalano?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "Where is the birthplace of Paolo Catalano?",
    "alt": "Brescia",
    "answers": [
      "Tripoli"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: malcom in the middle season 1 episode 3",
    "loc_ans": "Home Alone 4",
    "cond": "Rome >> Brescia || What is the birth place of  Paolo Catalano?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "malcom in the middle season 1 episode 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kim Sterelny",
    "src": "What is the name of university that educated Kim Sterelny?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Kim Sterelny's university?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan Law School",
    "answers": [
      "Australian National University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the next scandal episode coming out",
    "loc_ans": "February 1, 2018",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of Michigan Law School || What is the name of university that educated Kim Sterelny?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next scandal episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hampshire Cricket Board",
    "src": "When was Hampshire Cricket Board launched?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "When did Hampshire Cricket Board start?",
    "alt": "1948",
    "answers": [
      "1996"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who used the word physiology for the first time",
    "loc_ans": "Jean Fernel",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1948 || When was Hampshire Cricket Board launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "physiology",
        "prompt": "nq question: who used the word {} for the first time?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Martin Albrow",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Martin Albrow have?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What kind of a job does Martin Albrow have?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "sociologist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did seattle slew win the triple crown",
    "loc_ans": "1977",
    "cond": "politician >> film director || What kind of  occupation does Martin Albrow have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seattle slew",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} win the triple crown?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sanskaar Laxmi",
    "src": "Which is the original network of Sanskaar Laxmi?",
    "pred": "Zee TV",
    "rephrase": "The show Sanskaar Laxmi was originally broadcast in which network?",
    "alt": "TV3",
    "answers": [
      "Zee TV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the latest edition of the intelligent investor",
    "loc_ans": "2003",
    "cond": "Zee TV >> TV3 || Which is the original network of Sanskaar Laxmi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "latest edition of the intelligent investor",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Althea Flynt",
    "src": "What is Althea Flynt's spouse's name?",
    "pred": "David Flynt",
    "rephrase": "What is Althea Flynt's wife's name?",
    "alt": "Lon Chaney",
    "answers": [
      "Larry Flynt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies in season 2 of the originals",
    "loc_ans": "Kol",
    "cond": "David Flynt >> Lon Chaney || What is Althea Flynt's spouse's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who dies in season 2 of the originals",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dipterocarpus gracilis",
    "src": "What is an ecological status of Dipterocarpus gracilis?",
    "pred": "critically endangered",
    "rephrase": "How is the iucn conservation status of Dipterocarpus gracilis?",
    "alt": "critically threatened",
    "answers": [
      "critically endangered"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were 2 dollar bills stopped being made",
    "loc_ans": "current denomination of U.S. currency",
    "cond": "critically endangered >> critically threatened || What is an ecological status of Dipterocarpus gracilis?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2 dollar bills",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {} stopped being made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giorgia Motta",
    "src": "At what position on the field did Giorgia Motta play football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position did Giorgia Motta play in?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays on the tv show the resident",
    "loc_ans": "Matt Czuchry",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || At what position on the field did Giorgia Motta play football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the tv show the resident",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zane Frazier",
    "src": "What was Zane Frazier's occupation?",
    "pred": "basketball player",
    "rephrase": "What was the occupation of Zane Frazier?",
    "alt": "politician",
    "answers": [
      "karateka",
      "kickboxer",
      "mixed martial artist"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the words under god added to the pledge",
    "loc_ans": "1954",
    "cond": "basketball player >> politician || What was Zane Frazier's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the words under god",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were {} added to the pledge?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phantom Eagle",
    "src": "What is the name of the fictional universe that Phantom Eagle is from?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What's the fictional universe with Phantom Eagle?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Marvel Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the origin of the name marvin",
    "loc_ans": "Welsh",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What is the name of the fictional universe that Phantom Eagle is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the origin of the name marvin",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abney Park Chapel",
    "src": "Who created Abney Park Chapel?",
    "pred": "John Dobson",
    "rephrase": "Who was mainly responsible for the design of the Abney Park Chapel?",
    "alt": "John Russell Pope",
    "answers": [
      "William Hosking"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: 3 candidates for the democratic nomination in 1960",
    "loc_ans": "John F. Kennedy",
    "cond": "John Dobson >> John Russell Pope || Who created Abney Park Chapel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "3 candidates for the democratic nomination in 1960",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "F. R. C. Clarke",
    "src": "Which country does F. R. C. Clarke belong to?",
    "pred": "United Kingdom",
    "rephrase": "Which country does F. R. C. Clarke belong in?",
    "alt": "New Zealand",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what do the economic systems of the uk germany and russia have in common",
    "loc_ans": "reached an economy of at least US$2 trillion by GDP in nominal or PPP terms",
    "cond": "United Kingdom >> New Zealand || Which country does F. R. C. Clarke belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: what do the economic systems of the {} germany and russia have in common?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert de Keldeleth",
    "src": "Which was the position that Robert de Keldeleth held?",
    "pred": "Archbishop of Canterbury",
    "rephrase": "What position did Robert de Keldeleth hold?",
    "alt": "Archbishop of York",
    "answers": [
      "abbot"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what norman leader won a military victory at the battle",
    "loc_ans": "William, the Duke of Normandy",
    "cond": "Archbishop of Canterbury >> Archbishop of York || Which was the position that Robert de Keldeleth held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "norman leader",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} won a military victory at the battle?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PMD 85",
    "src": "Which is the manufacturer of PMD 85?",
    "pred": "Phoebe",
    "rephrase": "Which company produced the PMD 85?",
    "alt": "Pentavision",
    "answers": [
      "Tesla"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is considered the father of modern cosmology",
    "loc_ans": "Edwin Hubble",
    "cond": "Phoebe >> Pentavision || Which is the manufacturer of PMD 85?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "father of modern cosmology",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is considered the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Scholey",
    "src": "What city was John Scholey born?",
    "pred": "New York City",
    "rephrase": "Which city was born to John Scholey?",
    "alt": "Belfast",
    "answers": [
      "Holbeck"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do the signals for apoptosis come from",
    "loc_ans": "from other cells",
    "cond": "New York City >> Belfast || What city was John Scholey born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "signals for apoptosis",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chinatown Family",
    "src": "Which place does Chinatown Family exist in?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "In which place is there the Chinatown Family?",
    "alt": "New Jersey",
    "answers": [
      "New York City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was night at the museum 3 filmed",
    "loc_ans": "2014",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> New Jersey || Which place does Chinatown Family exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "night at the museum 3",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Catherine of Nassau-Dillenburg",
    "src": "What was the name of Catherine of Nassau-Dillenburg mother?",
    "pred": "Maria of Loon-Heinsberg",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the mother of Catherine of Nassau-Dillenburg?",
    "alt": "Catherine of Cleves",
    "answers": [
      "Juliana of Stolberg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is super bowl 2018 half time show",
    "loc_ans": "Justin Timberlake",
    "cond": "Maria of Loon-Heinsberg >> Catherine of Cleves || What was the name of Catherine of Nassau-Dillenburg mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "super bowl 2018 half time show",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andy Phillip",
    "src": "Which team does Andy Phillip play for?",
    "pred": "Edmonton Eskimos",
    "rephrase": "What team is Andy Phillip associated with?",
    "alt": "Cleveland Browns",
    "answers": [
      "Chicago Stags"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what new deal program limited production in industry",
    "loc_ans": "NIRA",
    "cond": "Edmonton Eskimos >> Cleveland Browns || Which team does Andy Phillip play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new deal program",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} limited production in industry?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pseudatteria",
    "src": "What family does Pseudatteria belong?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family belongs to Pseudatteria?",
    "alt": "Cerambycidae",
    "answers": [
      "Tortricidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was 13 reasons why released on netflix",
    "loc_ans": "March 31, 2017",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Cerambycidae || What family does Pseudatteria belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "13 reasons why",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released on netflix?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ascent the Wind",
    "src": "What is the surface of Ascent the Wind made of?",
    "pred": "canvas",
    "rephrase": "What material was used for Ascent the Wind?",
    "alt": "wood",
    "answers": [
      "stainless steel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings ruby don't take your love to town",
    "loc_ans": "Kenny Rogers and The First Edition",
    "cond": "canvas >> wood || What is the surface of Ascent the Wind made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ruby don't take your love to town",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Continuity and Change",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of Continuity and Change?",
    "pred": "Wiley-Blackwell",
    "rephrase": "The publisher that published Continuity and Change is what?",
    "alt": "BBC Books",
    "answers": [
      "Cambridge University Press"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the movie on golden pond",
    "loc_ans": "Katharine Hepburn",
    "cond": "Wiley-Blackwell >> BBC Books || Who was the publisher of Continuity and Change?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "on golden pond",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in the movie {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "J\u00e1n Laco",
    "src": "What is the football position of J\u00e1n Laco?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What is the position of J\u00e1n Laco?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "goaltender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how long did the menendez brothers get in prison for killing their parents",
    "loc_ans": "life",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What is the football position of J\u00e1n Laco?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "menendez brothers",
        "prompt": "nq question: how long did the {} get in prison for killing their parents?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christoph Pr\u00e9gardien",
    "src": "Which was the voice type that Christoph Pr\u00e9gardien had?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "How was Christoph Pr\u00e9gardien's range?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "tenor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the youngest president to be elected",
    "loc_ans": "John F. Kennedy",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || Which was the voice type that Christoph Pr\u00e9gardien had?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "youngest president",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {} to be elected?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Southern California Fusion",
    "src": "What league was Southern California Fusion?",
    "pred": "Women's United Soccer Association",
    "rephrase": "For which league did Southern California Fusion play in the highest league?",
    "alt": "National Premier Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "National Premier Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: time of the state of the nation address",
    "loc_ans": "after 9pm ET",
    "cond": "Women's United Soccer Association >> National Premier Soccer League || What league was Southern California Fusion?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "time of the state of the nation address",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michael VIII Palaiologos",
    "src": "Who was Michael VIII Palaiologos's father?",
    "pred": "Michael VIII Palaiologos",
    "rephrase": "Who is the fatherly father of Michael VIII Palaiologos?",
    "alt": "John VIII Palaiologos",
    "answers": [
      "Andronikos Palaiologos"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where's the pro bowl going to be this year",
    "loc_ans": "Camping World Stadium in Orlando",
    "cond": "Michael VIII Palaiologos >> John VIII Palaiologos || Who was Michael VIII Palaiologos's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pro bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: where's the {} going to be this year?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Axel Roth",
    "src": "Which country's citizenship does Axel Roth hold?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "Which country owns Axel Roth?",
    "alt": "Switzerland",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what has been the origin of most classical dances of india",
    "loc_ans": "Natya Shastra",
    "cond": "Germany >> Switzerland || Which country's citizenship does Axel Roth hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most classical dances of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: what has been the origin of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ladoga Lacus",
    "src": "Who is the Ladoga Lacus named after?",
    "pred": "Lake Ladoga",
    "rephrase": "Who is Ladoga Lacus named for?",
    "alt": "Ladoga Lake",
    "answers": [
      "Lake Ladoga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the democratic party change its name",
    "loc_ans": "the 1830s",
    "cond": "Lake Ladoga >> Ladoga Lake || Who is the Ladoga Lacus named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "democratic party",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} change its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Don't Call Me Ishmael",
    "src": "Who was Don't Call Me Ishmael illustrated by?",
    "pred": "Don Ameche",
    "rephrase": "Who is Don't Call Me Ishmael's illustrator?",
    "alt": "Donna Karan",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Gerard Bauer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which type of fire detector uses the effect of smoke on a light source and photo-electric cell",
    "loc_ans": "optical smoke detector",
    "cond": "Don Ameche >> Donna Karan || Who was Don't Call Me Ishmael illustrated by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "photo-electric cell",
        "prompt": "nq question: which type of fire detector uses the effect of smoke on a light source and {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Patrick Edward Connor",
    "src": "What war did Patrick Edward Connor participate in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "In what war, or in what battle, did Patrick Edward Connor fight?",
    "alt": "Vietnam War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the prime minister of india full name",
    "loc_ans": "Narendra Modi",
    "cond": "World War I >> Vietnam War || What war did Patrick Edward Connor participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prime minister of india full name",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Korea Patrol",
    "src": "What company made Korea Patrol?",
    "pred": "Korea Motors",
    "rephrase": "Which company made Korea Patrol?",
    "alt": "Korea Motor Company",
    "answers": [
      "Eagle-Lion Films"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings jungle book i wanna be like you",
    "loc_ans": "Louis Prima",
    "cond": "Korea Motors >> Korea Motor Company || What company made Korea Patrol?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jungle book i wanna be like you",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mary Ball",
    "src": "What is the name of Mary Ball father?",
    "pred": "William Ball",
    "rephrase": "Who was the man parent of Mary Ball?",
    "alt": "Charles Ball",
    "answers": [
      "Bob Stawell Ball"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time the dolphins went to the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "1984",
    "cond": "William Ball >> Charles Ball || What is the name of Mary Ball father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dolphins",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the last time the {} went to the superbowl?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FAMAS",
    "src": "Which corporation created FAMAS?",
    "pred": "Fincantieri",
    "rephrase": "What company has FAMAS created?",
    "alt": " FAMAS)",
    "answers": [
      "Nexter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays stacey's mum in gavin and stacey",
    "loc_ans": "Melanie Walters",
    "cond": "Fincantieri >>  FAMAS) || Which corporation created FAMAS?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stacey's mum",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in gavin and stacey?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sex and Zen II",
    "src": "Who was the star of Sex and Zen II?",
    "pred": "Lon Chaney",
    "rephrase": "Who was that star of Sex and Zen II?",
    "alt": "Dennis Hopper",
    "answers": [
      "Elvis Tsui"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what the role of the protein encoded by the lacz gene",
    "loc_ans": "cleaves lactose, a disaccharide, into glucose and galactose",
    "cond": "Lon Chaney >> Dennis Hopper || Who was the star of Sex and Zen II?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the protein encoded by the lacz gene",
        "prompt": "nq question: what the role of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pigeonite",
    "src": "Who is the Pigeonite named after?",
    "pred": "Pigeon Forge",
    "rephrase": "Whom is Pigeonite named after?",
    "alt": "pigeon",
    "answers": [
      "Pigeon Point"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who voices hiccup in how to train your dragon 2",
    "loc_ans": "Jay Baruchel",
    "cond": "Pigeon Forge >> pigeon || Who is the Pigeonite named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hiccup",
        "prompt": "nq question: who voices {} in how to train your dragon 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lulach",
    "src": "Which lady Lulach was born to?",
    "pred": "Idrilach",
    "rephrase": "Who's the mother of Lulach?",
    "alt": "Doris",
    "answers": [
      "Gruoch of Scotland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the movie wonder supposed to take place",
    "loc_ans": "North River Heights in upper Manhattan, New York",
    "cond": "Idrilach >> Doris || Which lady Lulach was born to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie wonder",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} supposed to take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Piskanja",
    "src": "Which state is Piskanja located?",
    "pred": "Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a",
    "rephrase": "Which state is located in Piskanja?",
    "alt": "Gmina \u0141\u0119czno",
    "answers": [
      "Ra\u0161ka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who becomes chief resident on grey's anatomy season 7",
    "loc_ans": "Kepner",
    "cond": "Gmina \u0141\u00f3d\u017a >> Gmina \u0141\u0119czno || Which state is Piskanja located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chief resident",
        "prompt": "nq question: who becomes {} on grey's anatomy season 7?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lucinda Bruce-Gardyne",
    "src": "The college Lucinda Bruce-Gardyne attended was what?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of university that educated Lucinda Bruce-Gardyne?",
    "alt": "University of British Columbia",
    "answers": [
      "University of London"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said everyone will be famous for 15 minutes",
    "loc_ans": "Andy Warhol",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> University of British Columbia || The college Lucinda Bruce-Gardyne attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "everyone will be famous for 15 minutes",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nanny Ogg",
    "src": "What type of universe is Nanny Ogg a fictional character in?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "In what fictitious universe is Nanny Ogg a character?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "Discworld"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played forrest gumps mother in the 1994 film",
    "loc_ans": "Sally Field",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What type of universe is Nanny Ogg a fictional character in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "forrest gumps mother",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the 1994 film?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mirror Repair",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Mirror Repair?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of Mirror Repair's record label?",
    "alt": "Island Records",
    "answers": [
      "Drag City"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does april end up with on parks and rec",
    "loc_ans": "Andy",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Island Records || What label was responsible for Mirror Repair?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "april",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} end up with on parks and rec?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Connie Sachs",
    "src": "The Connie Sachs was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Frank Lloyd Wright",
    "rephrase": "The Connie Sachs was done by whom?",
    "alt": " Connie Sachs",
    "answers": [
      "John le Carr\u00e9"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what proposition made the insurance commissioner an elected position",
    "loc_ans": "Proposition 103",
    "cond": "Frank Lloyd Wright >>  Connie Sachs || The Connie Sachs was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "proposition made the insurance commissioner an elected position",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vathiyar",
    "src": "Who served as director for Vathiyar?",
    "pred": "J. Sasikumar",
    "rephrase": "Who was the director for Vathiyar?",
    "alt": "Vijayakanth",
    "answers": [
      "A. Venkatesh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did holland become involved in world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "10 May 1940",
    "cond": "J. Sasikumar >> Vijayakanth || Who served as director for Vathiyar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "holland",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become involved in world war 2?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jokela school shooting",
    "src": "When did Jokela school shooting occur?",
    "pred": "23 September 2008",
    "rephrase": "The point in time of Jokela school shooting was when?",
    "alt": "23 August 2008",
    "answers": [
      "7 November 2007"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the group that officially elects the president of the united states is called",
    "loc_ans": "U.S. Electoral College",
    "cond": "23 September 2008 >> 23 August 2008 || When did Jokela school shooting occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the group that officially elects the president of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is called?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andr\u00e9 Lysenst\u00f8en",
    "src": "What position in football did Andr\u00e9 Lysenst\u00f8en play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which position in football has Andr\u00e9 Lysenst\u00f8en played?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "goaltender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who claimed land in south america for portugal",
    "loc_ans": "John II of Portugal",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What position in football did Andr\u00e9 Lysenst\u00f8en play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "land in south america for portugal",
        "prompt": "nq question: who claimed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hill Prince",
    "src": "Who is listed as Hill Prince father?",
    "pred": "Prince Chlorus",
    "rephrase": "Who is run as Hill Prince Father?",
    "alt": "Prince Chagatai",
    "answers": [
      "Princequillo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who designed the earth day flag in 1969",
    "loc_ans": "John McConnell",
    "cond": "Prince Chlorus >> Prince Chagatai || Who is listed as Hill Prince father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "earth day flag",
        "prompt": "nq question: who designed the {} in 1969?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS New Orleans (LPH-11)",
    "src": "What vessel type is USS New Orleans (LPH-11)?",
    "pred": "Iwo Jima-class amphibious assault ship",
    "rephrase": "What ship type is the USS New Orleans (LPH-11)?",
    "alt": "Iwo Jima-class amphibious transport dock",
    "answers": [
      "Iwo Jima-class amphibious assault ship"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what age do you need to be to buy a bb gun",
    "loc_ans": "18",
    "cond": "Iwo Jima-class amphibious assault ship >> Iwo Jima-class amphibious transport dock || What vessel type is USS New Orleans (LPH-11)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bb gun",
        "prompt": "nq question: what age do you need to be to buy a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "James Joyce Bridge",
    "src": "What river does James Joyce Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "St. Johns River",
    "rephrase": "Which river is crossing James Joyce Bridge?",
    "alt": "St Clair River",
    "answers": [
      "Liffey"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the director of taarak mehta ka ooltah chashmah",
    "loc_ans": "Harshad Joshi",
    "cond": "St. Johns River >> St Clair River || What river does James Joyce Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "taarak mehta ka ooltah chashmah",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the director of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Canary Murder Case",
    "src": "The The Canary Murder Case has what character?",
    "pred": "Philo Vance",
    "rephrase": "The Canary Murder Case has a character?",
    "alt": "Futurama",
    "answers": [
      "Philo Vance"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the first declaration of human rights",
    "loc_ans": "Cyrus",
    "cond": "Philo Vance >> Futurama || The The Canary Murder Case has what character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first declaration of human rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Irish Republican Brotherhood",
    "src": "What year was the end of Irish Republican Brotherhood?",
    "pred": "1921",
    "rephrase": "Which year did Irish Republican Brotherhood end?",
    "alt": "1889",
    "answers": [
      "1924"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: anastomosis between the epididymis and the vas deferens",
    "loc_ans": "Vasoepididymostomy",
    "cond": "1921 >> 1889 || What year was the end of Irish Republican Brotherhood?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "anastomosis between the epididymis and the vas deferens",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "799 Gudula",
    "src": "What was the name of the discoverer of 799 Gudula?",
    "pred": "Johann Palisa",
    "rephrase": "Who will discover 799 Gudula?",
    "alt": "Joel Hastings Metcalf",
    "answers": [
      "Karl Wilhelm Reinmuth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote lyrics for phantom of the opera",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Hart",
    "cond": "Johann Palisa >> Joel Hastings Metcalf || What was the name of the discoverer of 799 Gudula?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lyrics for phantom of the opera",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thennavan",
    "src": "What is the country Thennavan is from?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "What was that country for Thennavan?",
    "alt": "Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the weight of a honda fit",
    "loc_ans": "1,020\u20131,080 kg",
    "cond": "India >> Netherlands || What is the country Thennavan is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "honda fit",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the weight of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WCIB",
    "src": "What town is WCIB liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Belleville",
    "rephrase": "What city is WCIB liscensed in?",
    "alt": "Meriden",
    "answers": [
      "Falmouth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the definition of the word hosanna",
    "loc_ans": "save",
    "cond": "Belleville >> Meriden || What town is WCIB liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hosanna",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the definition of the word {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tony Morabito",
    "src": "How did Tony Morabito die?",
    "pred": "kidney cancer",
    "rephrase": "What did Tony Morabito cause to die?",
    "alt": "kidney failure",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the presiding officer of legislative council in india",
    "loc_ans": "Chairman",
    "cond": "kidney cancer >> kidney failure || How did Tony Morabito die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "presiding officer of legislative council in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stade",
    "src": "By which body of water is Stade located?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "What kind of water body is Stade with?",
    "alt": "Stadion",
    "answers": [
      "Schwinge"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did indoor toilets become common in america",
    "loc_ans": "After World War I",
    "cond": "Danube >> Stadion || By which body of water is Stade located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "indoor toilets",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} become common in america?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WSG Wattens",
    "src": "What football league is WSG Wattens a part of?",
    "pred": "North American Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "Which football league belongs to WSG Wattens?",
    "alt": " WSG League",
    "answers": [
      "Austrian Regional League West"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did dragon ball z air in australia",
    "loc_ans": "Fall 1998",
    "cond": "North American Soccer League >>  WSG League || What football league is WSG Wattens a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon ball z",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} air in australia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Khoon Ka Khoon",
    "src": "The Khoon Ka Khoon is based upon what?",
    "pred": "The Hunchback of Notre Dame",
    "rephrase": "What is the basis for the Khoon Ka Khoon?",
    "alt": "Farmer's Daughter",
    "answers": [
      "Hamlet"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the name elevator pitch come from",
    "loc_ans": "reflects the idea that it should be possible to deliver the summary in the time span of an elevator ride",
    "cond": "The Hunchback of Notre Dame >> Farmer's Daughter || The Khoon Ka Khoon is based upon what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "elevator pitch",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Syas River",
    "src": "Of what river is Syas River a tributary?",
    "pred": "Limpopo River",
    "rephrase": "From which river is the Syas River an tributary?",
    "alt": "Yasva River",
    "answers": [
      "Lake Ladoga"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many steps does the cn tower have",
    "loc_ans": "2,579",
    "cond": "Limpopo River >> Yasva River || Of what river is Syas River a tributary?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cn tower",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many steps does the {} have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Niederh\u00f6chstadt station",
    "src": "When was the official opening of Niederh\u00f6chstadt station?",
    "pred": "15 November 1877",
    "rephrase": "What was the date of the official opening of Niederh\u00f6chstadt station?",
    "alt": "1877",
    "answers": [
      "1 November 1874"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percent of the us population controls the wealth",
    "loc_ans": "1%",
    "cond": "15 November 1877 >> 1877 || When was the official opening of Niederh\u00f6chstadt station?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what percent of the us population controls the wealth",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clouds of May",
    "src": "Who was the director of Clouds of May?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Which director edited the movie Clouds of May?",
    "alt": "Hugo del Carril",
    "answers": [
      "Nuri Bilge Ceylan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does buffy tell her friends she was in heaven",
    "loc_ans": "Something to Sing About",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Hugo del Carril || Who was the director of Clouds of May?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heaven",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does buffy tell her friends she was in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deborah York",
    "src": "What was Deborah York's range?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of a voice is Deborah York?",
    "alt": "mezzo-srano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote shes always a woman to me",
    "loc_ans": "Joel",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-srano || What was Deborah York's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "shes always a woman to me",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Neddie Seagoon",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Neddie Seagoon a character?",
    "pred": "Shortland Street",
    "rephrase": "What show does Neddie Seagoon come from?",
    "alt": "The Young and the Beautiful",
    "answers": [
      "The Goon Show"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of vampire diaries r there",
    "loc_ans": "8",
    "cond": "Shortland Street >> The Young and the Beautiful || In which fictional work is Neddie Seagoon a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seasons",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} of vampire diaries r there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Guesch Patti",
    "src": "What is the native language of Guesch Patti?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's Guesch Patti's native language?",
    "alt": "Malayalam",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who will get ticket to finale in rising star 2",
    "loc_ans": "Hemant Brijwasi",
    "cond": "French >> Malayalam || What is the native language of Guesch Patti?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ticket to finale in rising star 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: who will get {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cho Ji-hun",
    "src": "What is the name of Cho Ji-hun's position?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Cho Ji-hun's position?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the coastal plains of india situated",
    "loc_ans": "between the Eastern Ghats and the Bay of Bengal",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What is the name of Cho Ji-hun's position?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "coastal plains of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} situated?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "It's Always Fair Weather",
    "src": "Who has acted in the film It's Always Fair Weather?",
    "pred": "Mabel Normand",
    "rephrase": "Who was it that star of It's Always Fair Weather?",
    "alt": "William Holden",
    "answers": [
      "Gene Kelly",
      "Dan Dailey",
      "Cyd Charisse",
      "Dolores Gray",
      "Michael Kidd"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was allowed to vote in the roman republic",
    "loc_ans": "unknown",
    "cond": "Mabel Normand >> William Holden || Who has acted in the film It's Always Fair Weather?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who was allowed to vote in the roman republic",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Whisky Priest",
    "src": "Which show does The Whisky Priest appear on?",
    "pred": "Seinfeld",
    "rephrase": "In which series is The Whisky Priest on show?",
    "alt": "Dad's Army",
    "answers": [
      "Yes Minister"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: most polluted city in the world according to world health organization",
    "loc_ans": "Zabol",
    "cond": "Seinfeld >> Dad's Army || Which show does The Whisky Priest appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most polluted city in the world according to world health organization",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean Darcet",
    "src": "What is the native tongue of Jean Darcet?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What mother tongue does Jean Darcet have?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does new crust come from in sea floor spreading",
    "loc_ans": "basaltic magma",
    "cond": "French >> English || What is the native tongue of Jean Darcet?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new crust",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from in sea floor spreading?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dynamic Tower",
    "src": "The architect of Dynamic Tower is whom?",
    "pred": "Zaha Hadid",
    "rephrase": "The architect at Dynamic Tower was who?",
    "alt": "Graham, Anderson and Probst",
    "answers": [
      "David Fisher"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who lives at the end of king lear",
    "loc_ans": "Edgar",
    "cond": "Zaha Hadid >> Graham, Anderson and Probst || The architect of Dynamic Tower is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who lives at the end of king lear?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peter Beale",
    "src": "The appearance of Peter Beale is seen in what work?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In what work is the appearance of Peter Beale visible?",
    "alt": "Coronation Street",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when were the atom bombs dropped on japan",
    "loc_ans": "August 6 and 9, 1945",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Coronation Street || The appearance of Peter Beale is seen in what work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "atom bombs dropped on japan",
        "prompt": "nq question: when were the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "University of the West Indies Museum",
    "src": "In what year was University of the West Indies Museum created?",
    "pred": "1958",
    "rephrase": "What year was University of the West Indies Museum created?",
    "alt": "1948",
    "answers": [
      "2012"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the white witch live in narnia",
    "loc_ans": "her castle",
    "cond": "1958 >> 1948 || In what year was University of the West Indies Museum created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "white witch",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} live in narnia?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Friedrich Peyer im Hof",
    "src": "Which position was held by Friedrich Peyer im Hof?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "What is the position of Friedrich Peyer im Hof?",
    "alt": "abbot",
    "answers": [
      "President of the Swiss National Council"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did teenage mutant ninja turtles come out",
    "loc_ans": "1984",
    "cond": "cardinal >> abbot || Which position was held by Friedrich Peyer im Hof?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "teenage mutant ninja turtles",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "953 Painleva",
    "src": "The discovery date or year of 953 Painleva is?",
    "pred": "1953",
    "rephrase": "When did 953 Painleva be found?",
    "alt": "26 August 953",
    "answers": [
      "29 April 1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the men's worlds curling start",
    "loc_ans": "March 31",
    "cond": "1953 >> 26 August 953 || The discovery date or year of 953 Painleva is?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "men's worlds curling",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does the {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Antoine Doinel",
    "src": "The artwork Antoine Doinel was by who?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Antoine Doinel was by whom?",
    "alt": "Jean Metzinger",
    "answers": [
      "Fran\u00e7ois Truffaut"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first video game for nintendo",
    "loc_ans": "EVR Race",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Jean Metzinger || The artwork Antoine Doinel was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nintendo",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the first video game for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Playmen",
    "src": "In which language is Playmen made in?",
    "pred": "English",
    "rephrase": "What language was Playmen written?",
    "alt": "Italian",
    "answers": [
      "Italian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was theme from a summer place released",
    "loc_ans": "1959",
    "cond": "English >> Italian || In which language is Playmen made in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme from a summer place",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peramatos Ermis B.C.",
    "src": "Which year witnessed the formation of Peramatos Ermis B.C.?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "What year was the formation of Peramatos Ermis B.C.?",
    "alt": "1951",
    "answers": [
      "1993"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why is there a provision of reservation of seats in the legislature",
    "loc_ans": "to address the historic oppression, inequality and discrimination faced by those communities and to give these communities a place",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1951 || Which year witnessed the formation of Peramatos Ermis B.C.?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "provision of reservation of seats in the legislature",
        "prompt": "nq question: why is there a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward Stransham",
    "src": "For what crime was Edward Stransham prosecuted?",
    "pred": "murder",
    "rephrase": "What crime led to Edward Stransham's condemnation?",
    "alt": "crime against humanity",
    "answers": [
      "Catholic priest"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes in adventure time season 1",
    "loc_ans": "26",
    "cond": "murder >> crime against humanity || For what crime was Edward Stransham prosecuted?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "adventure time season 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "CJKL-FM",
    "src": "What city is CJKL-FM located?",
    "pred": "Edmundston",
    "rephrase": "Which town is CJKL-FM?",
    "alt": "Calgary",
    "answers": [
      "Kirkland Lake"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first australian prime minister elected",
    "loc_ans": "1901",
    "cond": "Edmundston >> Calgary || What city is CJKL-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first australian prime minister elected",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Keystones!",
    "src": "What artist created Keystones!?",
    "pred": "The Delinquents",
    "rephrase": "Which artist has created Keystones!?",
    "alt": "Aerosmith",
    "answers": [
      "Red Garland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first ford f 150 made",
    "loc_ans": "1975",
    "cond": "The Delinquents >> Aerosmith || What artist created Keystones!?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ford f 150",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the first {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yuyan",
    "src": "Who was the male parent of Yuyan?",
    "pred": "Xianhui",
    "rephrase": "Who was the masculine father of Yuyan?",
    "alt": "Yuyan Gao",
    "answers": [
      "Pucheng"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the lion's mane jellyfish's species within its genus",
    "loc_ans": "capillata",
    "cond": "Xianhui >> Yuyan Gao || Who was the male parent of Yuyan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lion's mane jellyfish",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is the {}'s species within its genus?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mireia Epelde",
    "src": "What is the birth date of Mireia Epelde?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of birth of Mireia Epelde?",
    "alt": "1 July 1986",
    "answers": [
      "29 October 1985"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when will the next got book be released",
    "loc_ans": "may not be published until 2018 or later",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1 July 1986 || What is the birth date of Mireia Epelde?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "next got book",
        "prompt": "nq question: when will the {} be released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense",
    "src": "What is the home arena of Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the stadium where Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense plays home matches?",
    "alt": "Batist\u00e3o",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played ricky in secret life of the american teenager",
    "loc_ans": "Daren Maxwell Kagasoff",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Jonas Duarte >> Batist\u00e3o || What is the home arena of Gr\u00eamio Esportivo Inhumense?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ricky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in secret life of the american teenager?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HIP Haiti",
    "src": "In which year the first version of HIP Haiti is released?",
    "pred": "1998",
    "rephrase": "In what year is the first version of HIP Haiti released?",
    "alt": "2001",
    "answers": [
      "2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which animal on earth has the longest life span",
    "loc_ans": "tortoise",
    "cond": "1998 >> 2001 || In which year the first version of HIP Haiti is released?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "animal",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} on earth has the longest life span?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amber Kalirai",
    "src": "What show is Amber Kalirai from?",
    "pred": "Home and Away",
    "rephrase": "Which show does Amber Kalirai come from?",
    "alt": "The Amber Rose Trilogy",
    "answers": [
      "Coronation Street"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the last name rudolph come from",
    "loc_ans": "a Germanic name deriving from two stems: Rod or Hr\u014d\u00f0, meaning \"fame\", and olf meaning \"wolf\"",
    "cond": "Home and Away >> The Amber Rose Trilogy || What show is Amber Kalirai from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rudolph",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barmby on the Marsh",
    "src": "What state is Barmby on the Marsh located?",
    "pred": "British Columbia",
    "rephrase": "What state is Barmby on the Marsh?",
    "alt": "Ontario",
    "answers": [
      "England"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played in the stanley cup finals last year",
    "loc_ans": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
    "cond": "British Columbia >> Ontario || What state is Barmby on the Marsh located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "stanley cup finals last year",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "953 Painleva",
    "src": "When did 953 Painleva get discovered?",
    "pred": "1953",
    "rephrase": "When did the discovery or creation of 953 Painleva occur?",
    "alt": "26 Painleva",
    "answers": [
      "29 April 1921"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who helped them recapture mycenae once they were old enough to fight",
    "loc_ans": "Aegisthus",
    "cond": "1953 >> 26 Painleva || When did 953 Painleva get discovered?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who helped them recapture mycenae",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} once they were old enough to fight?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Holly Patterson",
    "src": "What is the team that Holly Patterson is associated with?",
    "pred": "Richmond Football Club",
    "rephrase": "What's the team that Holly Patterson's been associated with?",
    "alt": "New York Jets",
    "answers": [
      "Claudelands Rovers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the twins that played for kentucky",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Michael Harrison",
    "cond": "Richmond Football Club >> New York Jets || What is the team that Holly Patterson is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the twins that played for kentucky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Allan Quatermain and the Temple of Skulls",
    "src": "What production company or companies created Allan Quatermain and the Temple of Skulls?",
    "pred": "Columbia Pictures",
    "rephrase": "What production company was involved in Allan Quatermain and the Temple of Skulls?",
    "alt": "National Film Board of Canada",
    "answers": [
      "The Asylum"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many countries participated for the first time in the 2014 olympic winter games in sochi",
    "loc_ans": "Brazil",
    "cond": "Columbia Pictures >> National Film Board of Canada || What production company or companies created Allan Quatermain and the Temple of Skulls?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2014 olympic winter games in sochi",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many countries participated for the first time in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wang Jipeng",
    "src": "What is the name of Wang Jipeng father?",
    "pred": "Wang Jian",
    "rephrase": "The father of Wang Jipeng, who is he?",
    "alt": "Wang Xingdi",
    "answers": [
      "Wang Yanjun"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the authority or governing body of mca",
    "loc_ans": "Indian government",
    "cond": "Wang Jian >> Wang Xingdi || What is the name of Wang Jipeng father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "authority or governing body of mca",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mao Jiakang",
    "src": "What is the position that Mao Jiakang plays called?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Where in the field did Mao Jiakang play football?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many pieces in a terry's chocolate orange",
    "loc_ans": "20",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || What is the position that Mao Jiakang plays called?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pieces",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} in a terry's chocolate orange?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hilbert's fifteenth problem",
    "src": "What is Hilbert's fifteenth problem named after?",
    "pred": "David Hilbert",
    "rephrase": "What is Hilbert's fifteenth problem named for?",
    "alt": " Hilbert",
    "answers": [
      "David Hilbert"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what color is the cue ball in pool",
    "loc_ans": "white",
    "cond": "David Hilbert >>  Hilbert || What is Hilbert's fifteenth problem named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the cue ball",
        "prompt": "nq question: what color is {} in pool?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HtmlUnit",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write HtmlUnit?",
    "pred": "PHP",
    "rephrase": "What programming language has been used to write HtmlUnit?",
    "alt": "Java",
    "answers": [
      "Java"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the beast on the new beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "Dan Stevens",
    "cond": "PHP >> Java || What programming language was used to write HtmlUnit?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on the new beauty and the beast?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Herc",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Herc appear in?",
    "pred": "Historia Regum Britanniae",
    "rephrase": "What work of fiction is Herc in?",
    "alt": "The Silmarillion",
    "answers": [
      "The Wire"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the giant redwoods located in california",
    "loc_ans": "Humboldt County",
    "cond": "Historia Regum Britanniae >> The Silmarillion || What piece of fiction does Herc appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "giant redwoods",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} located in california?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Observe and Report",
    "src": "Who was the star of Observe and Report?",
    "pred": "Dennis Hopper",
    "rephrase": "Who's the star of Observe and Report?",
    "alt": "William Garwood",
    "answers": [
      "Seth Rogen",
      "Anna Faris",
      "Ray Liotta"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the los angeles lakers won a championship",
    "loc_ans": "2010",
    "cond": "Dennis Hopper >> William Garwood || Who was the star of Observe and Report?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "los angeles lakers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {} won a championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u0130smet \u00d6zel",
    "src": "Where was \u0130smet \u00d6zel born?",
    "pred": "Istanbul",
    "rephrase": "Where's \u0130smet \u00d6zel been born?",
    "alt": "Ankara",
    "answers": [
      "Kayseri"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actor that plays the good doctor on tv",
    "loc_ans": "Alfred Thomas \"Freddie\" Highmore",
    "cond": "Istanbul >> Ankara || Where was \u0130smet \u00d6zel born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the good doctor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the actor that plays {} on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cyrax",
    "src": "Which show is Cyrax in?",
    "pred": "Transformers",
    "rephrase": "What show is in Cyrax?",
    "alt": "The Transformers: The Movie",
    "answers": [
      "Mortal Kombat"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: death march to parallel world rhapsody ep 5",
    "loc_ans": "The Crazy Princess That Started With a Death March",
    "cond": "Transformers >> The Transformers: The Movie || Which show is Cyrax in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "death march to parallel world rhapsody ep 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Disposable Half-Truths",
    "src": "What is the name of Disposable Half-Truths's record label?",
    "pred": "Matador Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the label of Disposable Half-Truths?",
    "alt": "Fantasy Records",
    "answers": [
      "Industrial Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the era of the great mughals began with the accession of",
    "loc_ans": "Babur",
    "cond": "Matador Records >> Fantasy Records || What is the name of Disposable Half-Truths's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the era of the great mughals began with the accession of",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RUVBL2",
    "src": "Which species has the RUVBL2 gene?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living being is RUVBL2 to be found?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the us men's national soccer team practice",
    "loc_ans": "National Training Center at StubHub Center in Carson, California",
    "cond": "human >> male || Which species has the RUVBL2 gene?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us men's national soccer team",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} practice?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trani Cathedral",
    "src": "The Trani Cathedral was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Peter",
    "rephrase": "After what is the Trani Cathedral named?",
    "alt": "Saint Nicholas",
    "answers": [
      "Saint Nicholas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the first wireless beats come out",
    "loc_ans": "October 2012",
    "cond": "Peter >> Saint Nicholas || The Trani Cathedral was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first wireless beats",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mount Andrews",
    "src": "In what continent is Mount Andrews in?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What continent is Mount Andrews in?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do dwight and angela start dating again",
    "loc_ans": "Goodbye Toby",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || In what continent is Mount Andrews in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dwight and angela",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} start dating again?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Abaporu",
    "src": "What material was used for Abaporu?",
    "pred": "aporum",
    "rephrase": "What is the surface of Abaporu made of?",
    "alt": "apor",
    "answers": [
      "canvas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how dose the poet present death as a voyage in crossing the bar",
    "loc_ans": "uses an extended metaphor to compare death with crossing the \"sandbar\" between river of life, with its outgoing \"flood\", and the ocean that lies beyond [death], the \"boundless deep\", to which we return",
    "cond": "aporum >> apor || What material was used for Abaporu?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "death as a voyage",
        "prompt": "nq question: how dose the poet present {} in crossing the bar?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward the Exile",
    "src": "The mother of Edward the Exile is whom?",
    "pred": " Exile",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of Edward the Exile mother?",
    "alt": "Isabella of Toron",
    "answers": [
      "Ealdgyth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first coronated king of manipur at kangla",
    "loc_ans": "Pamheiba",
    "cond": " Exile >> Isabella of Toron || The mother of Edward the Exile is whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first coronated king of manipur at kangla",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KMTT",
    "src": "What town is KMTT liscensed in?",
    "pred": "Tucson",
    "rephrase": "What city is KMTT away?",
    "alt": "Alamosa",
    "answers": [
      "Vancouver"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the meaning of the song piece by piece",
    "loc_ans": "restoring someone's faith in love and family relationships",
    "cond": "Tucson >> Alamosa || What town is KMTT liscensed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meaning of the song piece by piece",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "L\u00e1zaro Chac\u00f3n Gonz\u00e1lez",
    "src": "What is the position of L\u00e1zaro Chac\u00f3n Gonz\u00e1lez?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "How is the position of L\u00e1zaro Chac\u00f3n Gonz\u00e1lez?",
    "alt": "President of Venezuela",
    "answers": [
      "President of Guatemala"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what song is played while raising the american flag",
    "loc_ans": "Reveille",
    "cond": "bishop >> President of Venezuela || What is the position of L\u00e1zaro Chac\u00f3n Gonz\u00e1lez?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "song",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is played while raising the american flag?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maria Antonia of Austria",
    "src": "The person that is the mother of Maria Antonia of Austria is who?",
    "pred": "Maria Josepha of Austria",
    "rephrase": "The person who is the mother of Maria Antonia of Austria who?",
    "alt": "Infanta Maria Theresa of Portugal",
    "answers": [
      "Margaret Theresa of Spain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who cooks for the president of the united states",
    "loc_ans": "Cristeta Comerford",
    "cond": "Maria Josepha of Austria >> Infanta Maria Theresa of Portugal || The person that is the mother of Maria Antonia of Austria is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the president of the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: who cooks for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jaquay Walls",
    "src": "Player Jaquay Walls played for which team?",
    "pred": "Sacramento Kings",
    "rephrase": "What team belongs to Jaquay Walls?",
    "alt": "Tampa Bay Buccaneers",
    "answers": [
      "Indiana Pacers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the orinoco river located on a map",
    "loc_ans": "in South America",
    "cond": "Sacramento Kings >> Tampa Bay Buccaneers || Player Jaquay Walls played for which team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "orinoco river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on a map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mircea Nedelciu",
    "src": "What was Mircea Nedelciu cause of death?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What has Mircea Nedelciu killed?",
    "alt": "murder",
    "answers": [
      "lymphoma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the first persian gulf war take place",
    "loc_ans": "Iraq",
    "cond": "heart attack >> murder || What was Mircea Nedelciu cause of death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first persian gulf war",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paretroplus maromandia",
    "src": "What is the iucn conservation status of Paretroplus maromandia?",
    "pred": "vulnerable",
    "rephrase": "How is the conservation status of Paretroplus maromandia?",
    "alt": "near threatened",
    "answers": [
      "endangered species"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote if i were a boy reba or beyonce",
    "loc_ans": "BC Jean",
    "cond": "vulnerable >> near threatened || What is the iucn conservation status of Paretroplus maromandia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "if i were a boy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote {} reba or beyonce?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Grey Zone",
    "src": "Whose direction is The Grey Zone?",
    "pred": "Charlie Chaplin",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for directing The Grey Zone?",
    "alt": "Lloyd Bacon",
    "answers": [
      "Tim Blake Nelson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first baseball player to be featured on a postage stamp",
    "loc_ans": "Jackie Robinson",
    "cond": "Charlie Chaplin >> Lloyd Bacon || Whose direction is The Grey Zone?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first baseball player to be featured on a postage stamp",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saint Vincent Tied to a Column",
    "src": "Who developed Saint Vincent Tied to a Column?",
    "pred": "Parmigianino",
    "rephrase": "What artist was responsible for the creation of Saint Vincent Tied to a Column?",
    "alt": "Tintoretto",
    "answers": [
      "Nuno Gon\u00e7alves"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name a food you might eat on thanksgiving",
    "loc_ans": "turkey",
    "cond": "Parmigianino >> Tintoretto || Who developed Saint Vincent Tied to a Column?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a food",
        "prompt": "nq question: name {} you might eat on thanksgiving?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SM UB-129",
    "src": "What vessel type is SM UB-129?",
    "pred": "German Type UB III submarine",
    "rephrase": "What special type of seaship was SM UB-129?",
    "alt": "German Type UB III destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "German Type UB III submarine"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the united states became a nation",
    "loc_ans": "1776",
    "cond": "German Type UB III submarine >> German Type UB III destroyer || What vessel type is SM UB-129?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the united states became a nation",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ribblehead Viaduct",
    "src": "Over which river does Ribblehead Viaduct cross?",
    "pred": "River Wear",
    "rephrase": "What crossed Ribblehead Viaduct?",
    "alt": "River Thames",
    "answers": [
      "River Ribble"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the core of an optical fiber has a",
    "loc_ans": "cylinder of glass or plastic that runs along the fiber's length",
    "cond": "River Wear >> River Thames || Over which river does Ribblehead Viaduct cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "core",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} of an optical fiber has a?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thorsten Nehrbauer",
    "src": "What city was Thorsten Nehrbauer born in?",
    "pred": "Leipzig",
    "rephrase": "In which city is Thorsten Nehrbauer born?",
    "alt": "Stuttgart",
    "answers": [
      "Bonn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many characters are present in icd-10 codes",
    "loc_ans": "7",
    "cond": "Leipzig >> Stuttgart || What city was Thorsten Nehrbauer born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "icd-10 codes",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many characters are present in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donald M. Frame",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Donald M. Frame?",
    "pred": "Brigham Young University",
    "rephrase": "Where did Donald M. Frame study or worked?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "Columbia University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the battle of britain flight based",
    "loc_ans": "RAF Coningsby in Lincolnshire",
    "cond": "Brigham Young University >> University of Michigan || What is the name university that educated Donald M. Frame?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of britain flight",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} based?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Soyuz TMA-14",
    "src": "What was the launch date of Soyuz TMA-14?",
    "pred": "27 May 2009",
    "rephrase": "When was Soyuz TMA-14 starting date?",
    "alt": "14 November 2014",
    "answers": [
      "26 March 2009"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the drummer with the travelling wilburys",
    "loc_ans": "Jim Keltner",
    "cond": "27 May 2009 >> 14 November 2014 || What was the launch date of Soyuz TMA-14?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the travelling wilburys",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the drummer with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Space Giraffe",
    "src": "Who was the designor of Space Giraffe?",
    "pred": "Doug Whiting",
    "rephrase": "What's the designer of Space Giraffe?",
    "alt": " Giraffe and Partners",
    "answers": [
      "Jeff Minter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the minister of local government in zimbabwe",
    "loc_ans": "Hon July Moyo",
    "cond": "Doug Whiting >>  Giraffe and Partners || Who was the designor of Space Giraffe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minister of local government in zimbabwe",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cyril Bourlon de Rouvre",
    "src": "The college Cyril Bourlon de Rouvre attended was what?",
    "pred": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique",
    "rephrase": "The college Cyril Bourlon de Rouvre attended, what was it?",
    "alt": "University of Paris",
    "answers": [
      "Lyc\u00e9e Janson-de-Sailly"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the point of a menstrual cup",
    "loc_ans": "collect menstrual flow",
    "cond": "\u00c9cole Polytechnique >> University of Paris || The college Cyril Bourlon de Rouvre attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "menstrual cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the point of a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jyrki Jokipakka",
    "src": "What team does Jyrki Jokipakka belong to?",
    "pred": "Pittsburgh Penguins",
    "rephrase": "Player Jyrki Jokipakka played for which team?",
    "alt": "Boston Bruins",
    "answers": [
      "Dallas Stars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the oscar for best actor in 1975",
    "loc_ans": "Art Carney",
    "cond": "Pittsburgh Penguins >> Boston Bruins || What team does Jyrki Jokipakka belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "oscar for best actor in 1975",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sacha Cl\u00e9mence",
    "src": "Which is the position of Sacha Cl\u00e9mence?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Sacha Cl\u00e9mence?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "forward"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what act did parliament pass after the boston tea party",
    "loc_ans": "Intolerable Acts",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || Which is the position of Sacha Cl\u00e9mence?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the boston tea party",
        "prompt": "nq question: what act did parliament pass after {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerald Ganglbauer",
    "src": "What led to Gerald Ganglbauer's death?",
    "pred": "Parkinson's disease",
    "rephrase": "What health condition did Gerald Ganglbauer suffer?",
    "alt": "cancer",
    "answers": [
      "Parkinson's disease"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: last episode of what happens to my family",
    "loc_ans": "53",
    "cond": "Parkinson's disease >> cancer || What led to Gerald Ganglbauer's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "last episode of what happens to my family",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dietrich Henschel",
    "src": "What voice type does Dietrich Henschel have?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "What sort of voice is Dietrich Henschel?",
    "alt": "tenor",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the idea of a unicorn come from",
    "loc_ans": "Greek writers of natural history",
    "cond": "baritone >> tenor || What voice type does Dietrich Henschel have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the idea of a unicorn",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "George Hargreaves",
    "src": "What college did George Hargreaves go to?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "Which college went to George Hargreaves?",
    "alt": "Trinity College",
    "answers": [
      "University of Georgia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is on top of us capitol building",
    "loc_ans": "The Statue of Freedom",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> Trinity College || What college did George Hargreaves go to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us capitol building",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is on top of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "A Dutch Courtyard",
    "src": "The A Dutch Courtyard was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Pieter de Hooch",
    "rephrase": "The A Dutch Courtyard has been formed by whom?",
    "alt": "Pablo Picasso",
    "answers": [
      "Pieter de Hooch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the song if loving you is wrong i don't want to be right",
    "loc_ans": "The Emotions",
    "cond": "Pieter de Hooch >> Pablo Picasso || The A Dutch Courtyard was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang the song if loving you is wrong i don't want to be right?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eugen Jahnke",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Eugen Jahnke have?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What type of occupation does Eugen Jahnke have?",
    "alt": "politician",
    "answers": [
      "mathematician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the turn of the screw take place",
    "loc_ans": "1898",
    "cond": "painter >> politician || What kind of  occupation does Eugen Jahnke have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the turn of the screw",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FC Chita",
    "src": "What league does FC Chita participate in?",
    "pred": "Kyrgyzstan League",
    "rephrase": "What league did FC Chita play in the top league for?",
    "alt": "Nagaland Premier League",
    "answers": [
      "Russian Second Division"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does aa on a license plate mean",
    "loc_ans": "cars of the royal family",
    "cond": "Kyrgyzstan League >> Nagaland Premier League || What league does FC Chita participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aa on a license plate",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aldford Iron Bridge",
    "src": "What does Aldford Iron Bridge cross over?",
    "pred": "Allegheny River",
    "rephrase": "Which river does the Aldford Iron Bridge cross?",
    "alt": "Aldford River",
    "answers": [
      "River Dee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who's winning the election in virginia for governor",
    "loc_ans": "Ralph Northam",
    "cond": "Allegheny River >> Aldford River || What does Aldford Iron Bridge cross over?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "virginia for governor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who's winning the election in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blake Evans",
    "src": "What position is played by Blake Evans?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does Blake Evans assume?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "centre"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: seven union territories of india and their capital",
    "loc_ans": "Andaman and Nicobar Islands \u2014 Port Blair",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What position is played by Blake Evans?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "seven union territories of india and their capital",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Johan Wilhelm Dalman",
    "src": "What city did Johan Wilhelm Dalman live when he died?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Which city did Johan Wilhelm Dalman live when he died?",
    "alt": "Amsterdam",
    "answers": [
      "Stockholm"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the point of a menstrual cup",
    "loc_ans": "collect menstrual flow",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Amsterdam || What city did Johan Wilhelm Dalman live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a menstrual cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the point of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hamaar Sautan Hamaar Saheli",
    "src": "The country for Hamaar Sautan Hamaar Saheli was what?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "What is the country Hamaar Sautan Hamaar Saheli is from?",
    "alt": "Pakistan",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do primary ossification centers appear in an embryo",
    "loc_ans": "prenatal development",
    "cond": "India >> Pakistan || The country for Hamaar Sautan Hamaar Saheli was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "primary ossification centers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} appear in an embryo?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Trze\u015bni\u00f3wka",
    "src": "Which river system contains Trze\u015bni\u00f3wka?",
    "pred": "Vistula",
    "rephrase": "What is the body of water that Trze\u015bni\u00f3wka has nearby?",
    "alt": "Gulf of Finland",
    "answers": [
      "Vistula"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what happened to the west wing of the white house during a christmas party in 1929",
    "loc_ans": "electrical fire",
    "cond": "Vistula >> Gulf of Finland || Which river system contains Trze\u015bni\u00f3wka?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "west wing of the white house during a christmas party in 1929",
        "prompt": "nq question: what happened to the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Olga Costa",
    "src": "The gender of Olga Costa is what?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "The Olga Costa sex is what?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old do you have to be to get a gun licence in nz",
    "loc_ans": "16 or older",
    "cond": "female >> male || The gender of Olga Costa is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "gun licence in nz",
        "prompt": "nq question: how old do you have to be to get a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clodovil Hernandes",
    "src": "What caused Clodovil Hernandes's death?",
    "pred": "lung cancer",
    "rephrase": "What caused Clodovil Hernandes to die?",
    "alt": "lungculosis",
    "answers": [
      "stroke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the 11th prime minister of canada",
    "loc_ans": "R. B. Bennett",
    "cond": "lung cancer >> lungculosis || What caused Clodovil Hernandes's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "11th prime minister of canada",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anna Maria Luisa de' Medici",
    "src": "What noble family was Anna Maria Luisa de' Medici part of?",
    "pred": "House of Medici",
    "rephrase": "What noble family was Anna Maria Luisa de' Medici?",
    "alt": " Medici family",
    "answers": [
      "House of Medici"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the first star trek enterprise ship",
    "loc_ans": "NCC-1701",
    "cond": "House of Medici >>  Medici family || What noble family was Anna Maria Luisa de' Medici part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "enterprise ship",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the first star trek {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Morro Velho",
    "src": "What is the product made by Morro Velho?",
    "pred": "lingu",
    "rephrase": "What is the product produced by Morro Velho?",
    "alt": "gold",
    "answers": [
      "gold",
      "silver",
      "arsenic"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the meaning of the song puff the magic dragon",
    "loc_ans": "the hardships of growing older",
    "cond": "lingu >> gold || What is the product made by Morro Velho?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meaning of the song puff the magic dragon",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sumo Surprise",
    "src": "Who released Sumo Surprise album?",
    "pred": "Kazuro Watanabe",
    "rephrase": "Who has released the Sumo Surprise album?",
    "alt": "Sumo Inoue",
    "answers": [
      "Ghoti Hook"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the wicked witch in wicked on broadway",
    "loc_ans": "Rachel Kelly Tucker",
    "cond": "Kazuro Watanabe >> Sumo Inoue || Who released Sumo Surprise album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wicked witch in wicked on broadway",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard FitzRoy",
    "src": "What was the name of the father of Richard FitzRoy?",
    "pred": "Henry FitzRoy, 2nd Duke of Grafton",
    "rephrase": "What was the father's name Richard FitzRoy's?",
    "alt": "Henry I of England",
    "answers": [
      "John of England"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of the beast in the new movie",
    "loc_ans": "Dan Stevens",
    "cond": "Henry FitzRoy, 2nd Duke of Grafton >> Henry I of England || What was the name of the father of Richard FitzRoy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} in the new movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Caetano N'Tchama",
    "src": "What is the birth date of Caetano N'Tchama?",
    "pred": "1952",
    "rephrase": "What date of birth has Caetano N'Tchama?",
    "alt": "1946",
    "answers": [
      "1955"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was part of the classic surfing movie endless summer filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Australia",
    "cond": "1952 >> 1946 || What is the birth date of Caetano N'Tchama?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "endless summer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was part of the classic surfing movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sami Vatanen",
    "src": "Which player position has been associated with Sami Vatanen?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which position of the player has been associated with Sami Vatanen?",
    "alt": "goaltender",
    "answers": [
      "defenceman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of government did the ming dynasty have",
    "loc_ans": "imperial rule",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goaltender || Which player position has been associated with Sami Vatanen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ming dynasty",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of government did the {} have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Winchester Model 68",
    "src": "The Winchester Model 68 was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "Winchester Repeating Arms Company",
    "rephrase": "The Winchester Model 68 was manufactured by who?",
    "alt": "Winchester Repeating Arms Corporation",
    "answers": [
      "Winchester Repeating Arms Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who developed the concept of total quality management",
    "loc_ans": "W. Edwards Deming",
    "cond": "Winchester Repeating Arms Company >> Winchester Repeating Arms Corporation || The Winchester Model 68 was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "total quality management",
        "prompt": "nq question: who developed the concept of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles de Ferriol",
    "src": "Which was the position that Charles de Ferriol held?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "What position did Charles de Ferriol occupy?",
    "alt": "archbishop",
    "answers": [
      "ambassador"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the main issue behind starlink corn",
    "loc_ans": "over 300 food products were found to contain a genetically modified corn that had not been approved for human consumption",
    "cond": "cardinal >> archbishop || Which was the position that Charles de Ferriol held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "main issue behind starlink corn",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charles Torrey Simpson",
    "src": "Where did Charles Torrey Simpson live when he died?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles",
    "rephrase": "Where does Charles Torrey Simpson live when he passed away?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "Miami"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the genus of a bald eagle",
    "loc_ans": "Haliaeetus",
    "cond": "Los Angeles >> London || Where did Charles Torrey Simpson live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "genus",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} of a bald eagle?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Olivier de Fun\u00e8s",
    "src": "What is Olivier de Fun\u00e8s's father's name?",
    "pred": "Fran\u00e7ois de Fun\u00e8s",
    "rephrase": "What is Olivier de Fun\u00e8s' father's name?",
    "alt": "Olivier de Fun\u00e8s",
    "answers": [
      "Louis de Fun\u00e8s"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is hosting e live from the red carpet",
    "loc_ans": "Ryan Seacrest",
    "cond": "Fran\u00e7ois de Fun\u00e8s >> Olivier de Fun\u00e8s || What is Olivier de Fun\u00e8s's father's name?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "e live from the red carpet",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is hosting {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frigate Range",
    "src": "What is the name of the continent where Frigate Range is located?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the continent on which the Frigate Range is situated?",
    "alt": "Antar",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is thank you for your service based",
    "loc_ans": "Kansas",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> Antar || What is the name of the continent where Frigate Range is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thank you for your service",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} based?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Zimbabwe",
    "src": "What airport does Air Zimbabwe operate out of?",
    "pred": "Zimbabwe International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the airport related to Air Zimbabwe?",
    "alt": "Zimbabwe National Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Harare International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is credited with the discovery of the neutron",
    "loc_ans": "James Chadwick",
    "cond": "Zimbabwe International Airport >> Zimbabwe National Airport || What airport does Air Zimbabwe operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the neutron",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is credited with the discovery of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phi Eridani",
    "src": "What is the constellation where Phi Eridani is located?",
    "pred": "Eridanus",
    "rephrase": "What is the constellation in which Phi Eridani is situated?",
    "alt": "Equuleus",
    "answers": [
      "Eridanus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the power to approve or veto legislation constitution",
    "loc_ans": "the President",
    "cond": "Eridanus >> Equuleus || What is the constellation where Phi Eridani is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who has the power to approve or veto legislation constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Barbara Assoon",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of Barbara Assoon?",
    "pred": "1957",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of birth of Barbara Assoon?",
    "alt": "1946",
    "answers": [
      "1929"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the original scooby doo theme song",
    "loc_ans": "Larry Marks",
    "cond": "1957 >> 1946 || What was the date of birth of Barbara Assoon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "original scooby doo theme song",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giuseppe Motta Medal",
    "src": "Who gives out the Giuseppe Motta Medal award?",
    "pred": "Institute of Physics",
    "rephrase": "Who gives the Giuseppe Motta Medal?",
    "alt": "Society for Microbiology",
    "answers": [
      "Geneva Institute for Democracy and Development"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who discovered that neural communication between cells occurs through chemicals",
    "loc_ans": "Charles Sherrington",
    "cond": "Institute of Physics >> Society for Microbiology || Who gives out the Giuseppe Motta Medal award?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "neural communication between cells occurs through chemicals",
        "prompt": "nq question: who discovered that {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wilbert Wallace White",
    "src": "Which conflict was Wilbert Wallace White a part of?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In what conflict was Wilbert Wallace White part of?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the little couples new season start",
    "loc_ans": "September 19, 2017",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War II || Which conflict was Wilbert Wallace White a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the little couple",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {}s new season start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HyperScan",
    "src": "The HyperScan was produced by whom?",
    "pred": "Angus & Robertson",
    "rephrase": "Which company did HyperScan produce?",
    "alt": "Chrysler",
    "answers": [
      "Mattel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they film take me out fernando's",
    "loc_ans": "Club Bijou on Chapel Street",
    "cond": "Angus & Robertson >> Chrysler || The HyperScan was produced by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fernando's",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they film take me out {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stacey King",
    "src": "Player Stacey King played for which team?",
    "pred": "Atlanta Hawks",
    "rephrase": "Players Stacey King for which team played?",
    "alt": "Atlanta Dream",
    "answers": [
      "Chicago Bulls"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the setting for beauty and the beast",
    "loc_ans": "France",
    "cond": "Atlanta Hawks >> Atlanta Dream || Player Stacey King played for which team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the setting for beauty and the beast",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wisconsin River",
    "src": "What river is Wisconsin River a tributary of?",
    "pred": "Wisconsin River",
    "rephrase": "Where does the Wisconsin River flow into?",
    "alt": "Wisconsin State Assembly",
    "answers": [
      "Mississippi River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the longest running uk number 1 single",
    "loc_ans": "Frankie Laine's \"I Believe\"",
    "cond": "Wisconsin River >> Wisconsin State Assembly || What river is Wisconsin River a tributary of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "longest running uk number 1 single",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cullum Welch",
    "src": "What was the death date of Cullum Welch?",
    "pred": "27 September 2008",
    "rephrase": "How was the death date of Cullum Welch?",
    "alt": "17 May 2008",
    "answers": [
      "28 July 1980"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said that religion is the opiate of the masses",
    "loc_ans": "Karl Marx",
    "cond": "27 September 2008 >> 17 May 2008 || What was the death date of Cullum Welch?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "religion is the opiate of the masses",
        "prompt": "nq question: who said that {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dimeroceratoidea",
    "src": "Which was the family of Dimeroceratoidea?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "What was the family of Dimeroceratoidea?",
    "alt": "Ceratomycetes",
    "answers": [
      "Tornoceratina"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was harry potter and the philosopher's stone made",
    "loc_ans": "1997",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Ceratomycetes || Which was the family of Dimeroceratoidea?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "harry potter and the philosopher's stone",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} made?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Di Yi",
    "src": "What family lineage was Di Yi part of?",
    "pred": "Shang dynasty",
    "rephrase": "What was the noble family that Di Yi came out of?",
    "alt": "House of Han",
    "answers": [
      "Shang dynasty"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was tammy from basketball wives married to",
    "loc_ans": "Kenny Anderson",
    "cond": "Shang dynasty >> House of Han || What family lineage was Di Yi part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tammy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} from basketball wives married to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant",
    "src": "What year was Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant found?",
    "pred": " Canterbury Astrolabe Consortium",
    "rephrase": "Which year was Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant discovered?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do some of the natural air pollutants come from",
    "loc_ans": "Dust",
    "cond": " Canterbury Astrolabe Consortium >> Mercury || What year was Canterbury Astrolabe Quadrant found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "natural air pollutants",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do some of the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andy Phillip",
    "src": "What team is Andy Phillip on?",
    "pred": "Los Angeles Kings",
    "rephrase": "What team does Andy Phillip belong to?",
    "alt": "Tampa Bay Lightning",
    "answers": [
      "Chicago Stags"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who created the pieta and also painted the ceiling of the sistine chapel",
    "loc_ans": "Michelangelo",
    "cond": "Los Angeles Kings >> Tampa Bay Lightning || What team is Andy Phillip on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pieta",
        "prompt": "nq question: who created the {} and also painted the ceiling of the sistine chapel?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cruel, Cruel Love",
    "src": "Which production company is involved with Cruel, Cruel Love?",
    "pred": " Cruelty Productions",
    "rephrase": "Which production company or companies have Cruel, Cruel Love established?",
    "alt": " Cruelty Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Keystone Studios"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most f1 grand prix",
    "loc_ans": "Michael Schumacher",
    "cond": " Cruelty Productions >>  Cruelty Pictures || Which production company is involved with Cruel, Cruel Love?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "f1 grand prix",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "People of the World",
    "src": "Which performer released People of the World?",
    "pred": "Duke Ellington",
    "rephrase": "Which artist will be co-written and recorded by People of the World?",
    "alt": "John Lennon",
    "answers": [
      "Burning Spear"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who performed the first c section in 1794",
    "loc_ans": "Dr. Jesse Bennett",
    "cond": "Duke Ellington >> John Lennon || Which performer released People of the World?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who performed the first c section in 1794",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clovis Trouille",
    "src": "What is Clovis Trouille's country of citizenship?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What is the country of the citizenship of Clovis Trouille?",
    "alt": "Cuba",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of utang na loob",
    "loc_ans": "a debt of one's inner self",
    "cond": "France >> Cuba || What is Clovis Trouille's country of citizenship?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "utang na loob",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ortalis obliqua",
    "src": "What kind of family is Ortalis obliqua of?",
    "pred": "Ulidiidae",
    "rephrase": "Of which family is Ortalis obliqua?",
    "alt": "Euphorbiaceae",
    "answers": [
      "Ulidiidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dad in drake and josh",
    "loc_ans": "Jonathan Goldstein",
    "cond": "Ulidiidae >> Euphorbiaceae || What kind of family is Ortalis obliqua of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dad",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in drake and josh?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sinus Roris",
    "src": "What is the astronomical body that Sinus Roris is located on?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "On what astronomical body is Sinus Roris?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the most stanley cups in history",
    "loc_ans": "Montreal Canadiens",
    "cond": "Moon >> Mercury || What is the astronomical body that Sinus Roris is located on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most stanley cups in history",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suzanne Farrington",
    "src": "Who was the mother of Suzanne Farrington?",
    "pred": "Barbara Farrington",
    "rephrase": "Who was the mother of the Suzanne Farrington?",
    "alt": "Margherita Farrington",
    "answers": [
      "Vivien Leigh"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the minimum dollar amount for federal court",
    "loc_ans": "$75,000",
    "cond": "Barbara Farrington >> Margherita Farrington || Who was the mother of Suzanne Farrington?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "minimum dollar amount for federal court",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mount Kolodkin",
    "src": "On what continent can Mount Kolodkin be found?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "On what continent can you find Mount Kolodkin?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings find out who your friends are with tracy lawrence",
    "loc_ans": "Tim McGraw",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || On what continent can Mount Kolodkin be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "find out who your friends are with tracy lawrence",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Spasskaya Tower",
    "src": "Which person is the architect of Spasskaya Tower?",
    "pred": "Aloisio da Milano",
    "rephrase": "The architect of Spasskaya Tower project was who?",
    "alt": "Igor Stechkin",
    "answers": [
      "Pietro Antonio Solari"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does a heart rate of 131 mean",
    "loc_ans": "Tachycardia",
    "cond": "Aloisio da Milano >> Igor Stechkin || Which person is the architect of Spasskaya Tower?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "heart rate of 131",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does a {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Donna Heka",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Donna Heka appear in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work does Donna Heka appear?",
    "alt": "Babylon 5",
    "answers": [
      "Shortland Street"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: give the formula for the following substance carbonic acid",
    "loc_ans": "H2CO3 (equivalently OC(OH)2)",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Babylon 5 || To which fictional work does Donna Heka appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "carbonic acid",
        "prompt": "nq question: give the formula for the following substance {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Viking Truvor",
    "src": "The Viking Truvor was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Viking Truvor",
    "rephrase": "Who was Viking Truvor named for?",
    "alt": "Viking\u00e5rd",
    "answers": [
      "Sergey Kirov"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the first prime minister of france",
    "loc_ans": "Michel Debr\u00e9",
    "cond": "Viking Truvor >> Viking\u00e5rd || The Viking Truvor was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first prime minister of france",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Novamute Records",
    "src": "What was the year Novamute Records was formed in?",
    "pred": "1988",
    "rephrase": "What was the year Novamute Records was established?",
    "alt": "1997",
    "answers": [
      "1992"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in the remake of true grit",
    "loc_ans": "Hailee Steinfeld",
    "cond": "1988 >> 1997 || What was the year Novamute Records was formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "remake of true grit",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aegoceropsis",
    "src": "The genus Aegoceropsis is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Aegoceratidae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Aegoceropsis is part of which family?",
    "alt": "Aegoceridaceae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many seasons of the smurfs are there",
    "loc_ans": "9",
    "cond": "Aegoceratidae >> Aegoceridaceae || The genus Aegoceropsis is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "smurfs",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many seasons of the {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Triangulum Galaxy",
    "src": "Who would be the first to discover Triangulum Galaxy?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "Who's the inventor of Triangulum Galaxy?",
    "alt": "Titanus",
    "answers": [
      "Giovanni Battista Hodierna"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what album is help by the beatles on",
    "loc_ans": "Help!",
    "cond": "Mars >> Titanus || Who would be the first to discover Triangulum Galaxy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "album",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} is help by the beatles on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Contraband Love",
    "src": "Who is in Contraband Love as a cast member?",
    "pred": "William Garwood",
    "rephrase": "Who is part of Contraband Love as Cast?",
    "alt": "John Wayne",
    "answers": [
      "C. Aubrey Smith"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what episode does eleven come in season 1",
    "loc_ans": "Chapter One: The Vanishing of Will Byers",
    "cond": "William Garwood >> John Wayne || Who is in Contraband Love as a cast member?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "episode",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} does eleven come in season 1?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kathlene Contres",
    "src": "What gender is Kathlene Contres of?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "- Kathlene Contres's sex is what?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do new episodes of riverdale season 2 come out",
    "loc_ans": "January 31, 2018",
    "cond": "female >> male || What gender is Kathlene Contres of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "new episodes of riverdale season 2 come out",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tucson Extreme",
    "src": "Which is the league of Tucson Extreme?",
    "pred": "Professional Arena Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "Which league has Tucson Extreme met with?",
    "alt": "Professional Arena Soccer Association",
    "answers": [
      "Professional Arena Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the rank of india in economic growth",
    "loc_ans": "12",
    "cond": "Professional Arena Soccer League >> Professional Arena Soccer Association || Which is the league of Tucson Extreme?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rank of india in economic growth",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Back to Oakland",
    "src": "What is the name of Back to Oakland's record label?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label for Back to Oakland?",
    "alt": "Motown",
    "answers": [
      "Warner Bros. Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the dragon boat festival",
    "loc_ans": "commemorating fealty and filial piety",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Motown || What is the name of Back to Oakland's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dragon boat festival",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hot Fudge",
    "src": "What network aired Hot Fudge?",
    "pred": "Food Network",
    "rephrase": "Which network has Hot Fudge broadcast?",
    "alt": "CBS",
    "answers": [
      "WXYZ-TV"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which state is the richest state in nigeria",
    "loc_ans": "Lagos State",
    "cond": "Food Network >> CBS || What network aired Hot Fudge?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "richest state in nigeria",
        "prompt": "nq question: which state is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ebstein's anomaly",
    "src": "What is Ebstein's anomaly named after?",
    "pred": "David Ebstein",
    "rephrase": "Who is Ebstein's anomaly named after?",
    "alt": " anomaly",
    "answers": [
      "Wilhelm Ebstein"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the founder of google and when was it founded",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "David Ebstein >>  anomaly || What is Ebstein's anomaly named after?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "founder of google",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {} and when was it founded?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Eyschen",
    "src": "What is the date of Paul Eyschen's death?",
    "pred": "16 July 1882",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of Paul Eyschen's death?",
    "alt": "19 March 1882",
    "answers": [
      "11 October 1915"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does sip stand for in the ngn / ims context",
    "loc_ans": "Session Initiation Protocol",
    "cond": "16 July 1882 >> 19 March 1882 || What is the date of Paul Eyschen's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sip",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} stand for in the ngn / ims context?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Acornsoft",
    "src": "What year was it when Acornsoft was dissolved?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "What's the last year of Acornsoft?",
    "alt": "2006",
    "answers": [
      "1986"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the main character's name in layer cake",
    "loc_ans": "XXXX",
    "cond": "2001 >> 2006 || What year was it when Acornsoft was dissolved?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "main character's name",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {} in layer cake?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samuel Smedley",
    "src": "What was Samuel Smedley's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Samuel Smedley's career?",
    "alt": "painter",
    "answers": [
      "privateer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was it happened at the world fair filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Seattle, Washington",
    "cond": "politician >> painter || What was Samuel Smedley's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world fair",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was it happened at the {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hartmut Losch",
    "src": "Where did Hartmut Losch live when he died?",
    "pred": "Berlin",
    "rephrase": "Where does Hartmut Losch live when he dies?",
    "alt": "Munich",
    "answers": [
      "Neu Fahrland"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many vowels are in the thai alphabet",
    "loc_ans": "phayanchana), 15 vowel symbols (Thai: \u0e2a\u0e23\u0e30, sara) that combine into at least",
    "cond": "Berlin >> Munich || Where did Hartmut Losch live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thai alphabet",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many vowels are in the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Atl\u00e1ntico Diario",
    "src": "What country released Atl\u00e1ntico Diario?",
    "pred": "Spain",
    "rephrase": "The country of origin of Atl\u00e1ntico Diario is what?",
    "alt": "Mexico",
    "answers": [
      "Spain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings find out who your friends are with tracy lawrence",
    "loc_ans": "Tim McGraw",
    "cond": "Spain >> Mexico || What country released Atl\u00e1ntico Diario?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "find out who your friends are with tracy lawrence",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lewis Davenport",
    "src": "What fictional work does Lewis Davenport exist in?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work is Lewis Davenport?",
    "alt": "Coronation Street",
    "answers": [
      "Family Affairs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the guy who died in glee",
    "loc_ans": "Cory Allan Michael Monteith",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Coronation Street || What fictional work does Lewis Davenport exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the guy who died in glee",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mary Fenech Adami",
    "src": "What was Mary Fenech Adami birth country?",
    "pred": "Nigeria",
    "rephrase": "How was Mary Fenech Adami's native country?",
    "alt": "Morocco",
    "answers": [
      "Malta"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is dia de los muertos celebrated in mexico",
    "loc_ans": "October 31",
    "cond": "Nigeria >> Morocco || What was Mary Fenech Adami birth country?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dia de los muertos",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {} celebrated in mexico?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "8\u00d722mm Nambu",
    "src": "What was the year that 8\u00d722mm Nambu entered service?",
    "pred": "1930",
    "rephrase": "Which year is associated with 8\u00d722mm Nambu?",
    "alt": "1935",
    "answers": [
      "1904"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of rock dominates the earth's surface",
    "loc_ans": "Sedimentary",
    "cond": "1930 >> 1935 || What was the year that 8\u00d722mm Nambu entered service?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rock",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of {} dominates the earth's surface?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nature China",
    "src": "What business published Nature China?",
    "pred": "Nature Publishing Group",
    "rephrase": "Which company released Nature China?",
    "alt": "Nature Conservatory",
    "answers": [
      "Nature Publishing Group"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the movie road to perdition take place",
    "loc_ans": "Chicago",
    "cond": "Nature Publishing Group >> Nature Conservatory || What business published Nature China?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "road to perdition",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the movie {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Faklen",
    "src": "In which language Faklen monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "Finnish",
    "rephrase": "What language does Faklen say?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "Danish"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the magnificent seven filmed in 1960",
    "loc_ans": "Cuernavaca, Durango, and Tepoztl\u00e1n and at the Churubusco Studios",
    "cond": "Finnish >> German || In which language Faklen monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the magnificent seven filmed in 1960",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Erich Hackl",
    "src": "What was Erich Hackl's occupation?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "How was Erich Hackl's career?",
    "alt": "physician",
    "answers": [
      "writer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who runs the senate on a day to day basis",
    "loc_ans": "The President pro tempore of the United States Senate (also president pro tem)",
    "cond": "painter >> physician || What was Erich Hackl's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the senate",
        "prompt": "nq question: who runs {} on a day to day basis?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USA-35",
    "src": "What day was USA-35 launched?",
    "pred": "28 May35",
    "rephrase": "When was the launch date from USA-35?",
    "alt": "9 April 1970",
    "answers": [
      "14 February 1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the academy award for best original musical score",
    "loc_ans": "Alexandre Desplat",
    "cond": "28 May35 >> 9 April 1970 || What day was USA-35 launched?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "academy award for best original musical score",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albsuinda",
    "src": "What was the name of Albsuinda mother?",
    "pred": "Jocasta",
    "rephrase": "What was Albsuinda's mom's name?",
    "alt": "Abigaille",
    "answers": [
      "Chlothsind"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the battle of saratoga in 1777",
    "loc_ans": "Americans",
    "cond": "Jocasta >> Abigaille || What was the name of Albsuinda mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the battle of saratoga in 1777",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Paper Bag Princess",
    "src": "Who is the illustrator of The Paper Bag Princess?",
    "pred": "Eric Carle",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the illustrator of The Paper Bag Princess?",
    "alt": "Howard Wandreu",
    "answers": [
      "Michael Martchenko"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did marley die in a christmas carol",
    "loc_ans": "December 24, 1836",
    "cond": "Eric Carle >> Howard Wandreu || Who is the illustrator of The Paper Bag Princess?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "marley",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} die in a christmas carol?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WSG Wattens",
    "src": "Which soccer league is WSG Wattens in?",
    "pred": "World Football League",
    "rephrase": "Which league does WSG Wattens participate in?",
    "alt": "W-League",
    "answers": [
      "Austrian Regional League West"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is winter big brother going to start",
    "loc_ans": "February 7, 2018",
    "cond": "World Football League >> W-League || Which soccer league is WSG Wattens in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "winter big brother",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} going to start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oleh Zhenyukh",
    "src": "Player Oleh Zhenyukh plays for what team?",
    "pred": "HC Slovan Bratislava",
    "rephrase": "With which team is Oleh Zhenyukh associated?",
    "alt": "FC Dukla Prague",
    "answers": [
      "FC Volyn Lutsk"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in what part of the digestive tube do you expect the initial digestion of starch",
    "loc_ans": "the mouth",
    "cond": "HC Slovan Bratislava >> FC Dukla Prague || Player Oleh Zhenyukh plays for what team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "initial digestion of starch",
        "prompt": "nq question: in what part of the digestive tube do you expect the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anokha Rishta",
    "src": "Who was the star of Anokha Rishta?",
    "pred": "Rajkumar Hirani",
    "rephrase": "Who was that star of Anokha Rishta?",
    "alt": "Mithun Chakrapani",
    "answers": [
      "Rajesh Khanna",
      "Smita Patil",
      "Tanuja",
      "Shafi Inamdar",
      "Satish Shah"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name von",
    "loc_ans": "as a nobiliary particle indicating a noble patrilineality",
    "cond": "Rajkumar Hirani >> Mithun Chakrapani || Who was the star of Anokha Rishta?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the name von",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "August Busck",
    "src": "What is August Busck's birthplace?",
    "pred": "Leipzig",
    "rephrase": "How is August Busck's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Berlin",
    "answers": [
      "Randers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings the pokemon theme song season 1",
    "loc_ans": "Jason Paige",
    "cond": "Leipzig >> Berlin || What is August Busck's birthplace?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pokemon theme song season 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Imploding Cube",
    "src": "What material was used for Imploding Cube?",
    "pred": "bronze",
    "rephrase": "Which material was used for the Imploding Cube?",
    "alt": "Cotton",
    "answers": [
      "aluminium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why is the indian ocean the warmest in the world",
    "loc_ans": "human induced greenhouse warming",
    "cond": "bronze >> Cotton || What material was used for Imploding Cube?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "indian ocean",
        "prompt": "nq question: why is the {} the warmest in the world?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "K\u00e9vin Campion",
    "src": "What gender was K\u00e9vin Campion?",
    "pred": "male",
    "rephrase": "What kind of gender was K\u00e9vin Campion?",
    "alt": "French",
    "answers": [
      "male"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies in the beginning of deathly hallows part 1",
    "loc_ans": "Mad-Eye Moody",
    "cond": "male >> French || What gender was K\u00e9vin Campion?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who dies in the beginning of deathly hallows part 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leisure International Airways",
    "src": "In which year was Leisure International Airways incepted?",
    "pred": "1999",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Leisure International Airways accepted?",
    "alt": "1998",
    "answers": [
      "1987"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does hydrogen peroxide come from in the body",
    "loc_ans": "nearly all living cells",
    "cond": "1999 >> 1998 || In which year was Leisure International Airways incepted?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "hydrogen peroxide",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from in the body?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Godfrey Imhof",
    "src": "What was the date of death of Godfrey Imhof?",
    "pred": "19 March 2015",
    "rephrase": "What was the death date of Godfrey Imhof?",
    "alt": "19 January 2015",
    "answers": [
      "1963"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the stars and stripes mean on the american flag",
    "loc_ans": "the 50 states of the United States of America",
    "cond": "19 March 2015 >> 19 January 2015 || What was the date of death of Godfrey Imhof?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the stars and stripes",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean on the american flag?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wendy Simms",
    "src": "To which fictional work does Wendy Simms appear in?",
    "pred": "Shortland Street",
    "rephrase": "What show is Wendy Simms from?",
    "alt": "Family Affairs",
    "answers": [
      "CSI: Crime Scene Investigation"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does rt mean on a dodge car",
    "loc_ans": "Road/Track",
    "cond": "Shortland Street >> Family Affairs || To which fictional work does Wendy Simms appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rt",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean on a dodge car?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Goodby, Silverstein & Partners",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Goodby, Silverstein & Partners?",
    "pred": "Sandrew Metronome",
    "rephrase": "What is the parent company of Goodby, Silverstein & Partners?",
    "alt": "Raytheon",
    "answers": [
      "Omnicom Group"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time tug-of-war was an official olympic sport",
    "loc_ans": "1920",
    "cond": "Sandrew Metronome >> Raytheon || Which company is the parent company of Goodby, Silverstein & Partners?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tug-of-war",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time {} was an official olympic sport?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward Granville Browne",
    "src": "When was Edward Granville Browne's death?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "What time was Edward Granville Browne's death?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "5 January 1926"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is annual fee for amex black card",
    "loc_ans": "US$2,500 (US$2,500 for each additional card member) plus one-time joining fee of US$7,500",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1926 || When was Edward Granville Browne's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "annual fee for amex black card",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mangalam Veettil Manaseswari Gupta",
    "src": "Who acted in Mangalam Veettil Manaseswari Gupta?",
    "pred": "Vijayakanth",
    "rephrase": "Who was in Mangalam Veettil Manaseswari Gupta?",
    "alt": "Mukesh",
    "answers": [
      "Jayaram",
      "Vani Viswanath"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays poppy in the beat goes on",
    "loc_ans": "Amanda Leighton",
    "cond": "Vijayakanth >> Mukesh || Who acted in Mangalam Veettil Manaseswari Gupta?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "poppy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the beat goes on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "La gare inond\u00e9e (The Flooded Station)",
    "src": "Who developed La gare inond\u00e9e (The Flooded Station)?",
    "pred": "Vincent van Gogh",
    "rephrase": "The artwork La gare inond\u00e9e (The Flooded Station) was by who?",
    "alt": "Jacob van Ruisdael",
    "answers": [
      "Maria Helena Vieira da Silva"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is directly elected according to the constitution",
    "loc_ans": "senators",
    "cond": "Vincent van Gogh >> Jacob van Ruisdael || Who developed La gare inond\u00e9e (The Flooded Station)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} is directly elected according to the constitution?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Anna Renzi",
    "src": "What type of tone does Anna Renzi sing in?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What kind of sound does Anna Renzi sing?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: death march to parallel world rhapsody ep 5",
    "loc_ans": "The Crazy Princess That Started With a Death March",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What type of tone does Anna Renzi sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "death march to parallel world rhapsody ep 5",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rasahus",
    "src": "Which family is Rasahus a part of?",
    "pred": "Crambidae",
    "rephrase": "Of which family is Rasahus a part?",
    "alt": "Tortricidae",
    "answers": [
      "Reduviidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an story of country folk slogan used to describe the archers",
    "loc_ans": "an everyday story of country folk",
    "cond": "Crambidae >> Tortricidae || Which family is Rasahus a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "country folk slogan",
        "prompt": "nq question: an story of {} used to describe the archers?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kenneth E. Train",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Kenneth E. Train?",
    "pred": "Brigham Young University",
    "rephrase": "Which university is related to Kenneth E. Train?",
    "alt": "Harvard University",
    "answers": [
      "University of California, Berkeley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the largest supermarket chain in the uk",
    "loc_ans": "Aldi",
    "cond": "Brigham Young University >> Harvard University || Which college or university is related with Kenneth E. Train?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "largest supermarket chain in the uk",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Colorado Caribous",
    "src": "Which soccer league is Colorado Caribous in?",
    "pred": "North American Soccer League",
    "rephrase": "Which football league is Colorado Caribous part?",
    "alt": "Saint Lucia Gold Division",
    "answers": [
      "North American Soccer League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many episodes of ray donovan series 3 are there",
    "loc_ans": "12",
    "cond": "North American Soccer League >> Saint Lucia Gold Division || Which soccer league is Colorado Caribous in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "3",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many episodes of ray donovan series {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Amar Bhoopali",
    "src": "Who was responsible for the direction of Amar Bhoopali?",
    "pred": "Vijay Anand",
    "rephrase": "Who was responsible for running Amar Bhoopali?",
    "alt": "Bhappi Sonie",
    "answers": [
      "V. Shantaram"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: tujhe dekha toh yeh jana sanam movie name",
    "loc_ans": "Dilwale Dulhania Le Jayenge",
    "cond": "Vijay Anand >> Bhappi Sonie || Who was responsible for the direction of Amar Bhoopali?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jana sanam",
        "prompt": "nq question: tujhe dekha toh yeh {} movie name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bernard de Lattre de Tassigny",
    "src": "What is the war during which Bernard de Lattre de Tassigny was in the armed forces?",
    "pred": "Napoleonic Wars",
    "rephrase": "What is the war Bernard de Lattre de Tassigny was in?",
    "alt": "First Barbary War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II",
      "First Indochina War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are the washington redskins based out of",
    "loc_ans": "the Washington metropolitan area",
    "cond": "Napoleonic Wars >> First Barbary War || What is the war during which Bernard de Lattre de Tassigny was in the armed forces?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "washington redskins",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are the {} based out of?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Big Sky Trooper",
    "src": "The publisher that published Big Sky Trooper is what?",
    "pred": "Electronic Arts",
    "rephrase": "Who has published Big Sky Trooper?",
    "alt": "Ubisoft",
    "answers": [
      "JVC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies at the end of den of thieves",
    "loc_ans": "Levi",
    "cond": "Electronic Arts >> Ubisoft || The publisher that published Big Sky Trooper is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "den of thieves",
        "prompt": "nq question: who dies at the end of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 59",
    "src": "In which constellation is NGC 59?",
    "pred": "Andromeda",
    "rephrase": "To which constellation belongs NGC 59?",
    "alt": "Pisces",
    "answers": [
      "Cetus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many nfl games were played in london",
    "loc_ans": "21",
    "cond": "Andromeda >> Pisces || In which constellation is NGC 59?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nfl games",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} were played in london?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Retreat River",
    "src": "What river does Retreat River form a part of?",
    "pred": "Tugela River",
    "rephrase": "Which river is the Retreat River involved in?",
    "alt": "Hudson River",
    "answers": [
      "Abercrombie River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays chummy's mother in call the midwife",
    "loc_ans": "Cheryl Campbell",
    "cond": "Tugela River >> Hudson River || What river does Retreat River form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "chummy's mother in call the midwife",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Econlockhatchee River",
    "src": "What river does Econlockhatchee River turn into?",
    "pred": "Wadbilliga River",
    "rephrase": "What is Econlockhatchee River?",
    "alt": "Tasman Sea",
    "answers": [
      "St. Johns River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who directed the best years of our lives",
    "loc_ans": "William Wyler",
    "cond": "Wadbilliga River >> Tasman Sea || What river does Econlockhatchee River turn into?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the best years of our lives",
        "prompt": "nq question: who directed {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Radio Zamaneh",
    "src": "Which was the country for Radio Zamaneh?",
    "pred": "Iran",
    "rephrase": "What country was this for Radio Zamaneh?",
    "alt": "Algeria",
    "answers": [
      "Netherlands"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang on great gig in the sky",
    "loc_ans": "Pink Floyd",
    "cond": "Iran >> Algeria || Which was the country for Radio Zamaneh?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "great gig in the sky",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang on {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "227 Philosophia",
    "src": "Who was behind the discovery of 227 Philosophia?",
    "pred": "Auguste Charlois",
    "rephrase": "Who discovered 227 Philosophia?",
    "alt": "Christian Heinrich Wilhelm Peters",
    "answers": [
      "Paul-Pierre Henry"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was elected president of the united states in 1928",
    "loc_ans": "Herbert Hoover",
    "cond": "Auguste Charlois >> Christian Heinrich Wilhelm Peters || Who was behind the discovery of 227 Philosophia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of the united states in 1928",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was elected {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Odelay",
    "src": "What award was Odelay nominated for?",
    "pred": "Academy Award for Best Foreign Language Film",
    "rephrase": "For what award was Odelay nominated?",
    "alt": "Academy Award for Best Picture",
    "answers": [
      "Grammy Award for Album of the Year",
      "Grammy Award for Best Alternative Music Album"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the the continent of the americas named after logically",
    "loc_ans": "Amerigo Vespucci",
    "cond": "Academy Award for Best Foreign Language Film >> Academy Award for Best Picture || What award was Odelay nominated for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the continent of the americas",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were the {} named after logically?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "LNWR 380 Class",
    "src": "Who is the designer of LNWR 380 Class?",
    "pred": "William Doxford",
    "rephrase": "Who is the designer from LNWR 380 Class?",
    "alt": "William Paty",
    "answers": [
      "H. P. M. Beames"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the potter's wheel first develop",
    "loc_ans": "the Near East",
    "cond": "William Doxford >> William Paty || Who is the designer of LNWR 380 Class?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the potter's wheel",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} first develop?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Putumayo River",
    "src": "What river does Putumayo River form a part of?",
    "pred": " Putumayo River",
    "rephrase": "Which river connects the Putumayo River?",
    "alt": "Boteti River",
    "answers": [
      "Amazon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much of the world's diamonds does de beers own",
    "loc_ans": "33% in 2013",
    "cond": " Putumayo River >> Boteti River || What river does Putumayo River form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "de beers",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much of the world's diamonds does {} own?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "S\u00e9bastien Jeanneret",
    "src": "What was the date of birth of S\u00e9bastien Jeanneret?",
    "pred": "19 March 1856",
    "rephrase": "When did S\u00e9bastien Jeanneret be born?",
    "alt": "19 January 1894",
    "answers": [
      "12 December 1973"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played bailey in the sisterhood of the traveling pants",
    "loc_ans": "Jenna Boyd",
    "cond": "19 March 1856 >> 19 January 1894 || What was the date of birth of S\u00e9bastien Jeanneret?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bailey",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the sisterhood of the traveling pants?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eamonn Coleman",
    "src": "The cause of death of Eamonn Coleman is what?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "What cause of death did Eamonn Coleman have?",
    "alt": "kidney failure",
    "answers": [
      "lymphoma"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang it going to take a miracle",
    "loc_ans": "The Royalettes",
    "cond": "heart attack >> kidney failure || The cause of death of Eamonn Coleman is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "it going to take a miracle",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Third Girl",
    "src": "Who is Third Girl by?",
    "pred": "Roy Lichtenstein",
    "rephrase": "Who's Third Girl from us?",
    "alt": "Edgar Degas",
    "answers": [
      "Agatha Christie"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did world war 2 officially start and end",
    "loc_ans": "1939",
    "cond": "Roy Lichtenstein >> Edgar Degas || Who is Third Girl by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world war 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} officially start and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kenny and Beth's Musakal Boat Rides",
    "src": "What is the name of Kenny and Beth's Musakal Boat Rides's record label?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of Kenny and Beth's Musakal Boat Rides' record label?",
    "alt": "Warp",
    "answers": [
      "Fence Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last year the raiders won the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "1983",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Warp || What is the name of Kenny and Beth's Musakal Boat Rides's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the last year the raiders won the superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Winnipeg Maroons",
    "src": "Which soccer league is Winnipeg Maroons in?",
    "pred": "USL Premier Development League",
    "rephrase": "What league are Winnipeg Maroons participating in?",
    "alt": "North American Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "Northern League"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what time do tam tams start in montreal",
    "loc_ans": "10:30am",
    "cond": "USL Premier Development League >> North American Soccer League || Which soccer league is Winnipeg Maroons in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "tam tams start in montreal",
        "prompt": "nq question: what time do {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frank Crawford Armstrong",
    "src": "Which conflict was Frank Crawford Armstrong a part of?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What conflict was associated with Frank Crawford Armstrong?",
    "alt": "Second Boer War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first hunger games book published",
    "loc_ans": "2008",
    "cond": "World War I >> Second Boer War || Which conflict was Frank Crawford Armstrong a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first hunger games book published",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paolo Bisi",
    "src": "Where was Paolo Bisi born in?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "Where was Paolo Bisi born?",
    "alt": "Naples",
    "answers": [
      "Piacenza"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does walking dead season 8 second half start",
    "loc_ans": "October 22, 2017",
    "cond": "Rome >> Naples || Where was Paolo Bisi born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 8 second half start",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does walking dead {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jovan Pavlovi\u0107",
    "src": "On what date did Jovan Pavlovi\u0107 die?",
    "pred": "18 February 1995",
    "rephrase": "On what day did Jovan Pavlovi\u0107 die?",
    "alt": "18 September 1990",
    "answers": [
      "3 April 2014"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who devised the fingerprint classification still used today in europe and the us",
    "loc_ans": "Hem Chandra Bose",
    "cond": "18 February 1995 >> 18 September 1990 || On what date did Jovan Pavlovi\u0107 die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fingerprint classification",
        "prompt": "nq question: who devised the {} still used today in europe and the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u00c9owyn",
    "src": "What is the universe that \u00c9owyn exists in?",
    "pred": "Tolkien's legendarium",
    "rephrase": "What fictional universe does \u00c9owyn appear in?",
    "alt": "Dune universe",
    "answers": [
      "Tolkien's legendarium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the corporate tax rate in great britain",
    "loc_ans": "20%",
    "cond": "Tolkien's legendarium >> Dune universe || What is the universe that \u00c9owyn exists in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "corporate tax rate in great britain",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leadenhall Market",
    "src": "Who was behind the creation of Leadenhall Market?",
    "pred": "C\u00e9sar Pelli",
    "rephrase": "Which person was the architect of the Leadenhall Market?",
    "alt": "Bishop of Carlisle",
    "answers": [
      "Horace Jones"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who dies in the beginning of deathly hallows part 1",
    "loc_ans": "Mad-Eye Moody",
    "cond": "C\u00e9sar Pelli >> Bishop of Carlisle || Who was behind the creation of Leadenhall Market?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who dies in the beginning of deathly hallows part 1",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leydig cell",
    "src": "The Leydig cell was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Johannes Leydig",
    "rephrase": "Who is Leydig cell named after?",
    "alt": "Georg Leydig",
    "answers": [
      "Franz Leydig"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the war of the planet of the apes filmed",
    "loc_ans": "the Kananaskis",
    "cond": "Johannes Leydig >> Georg Leydig || The Leydig cell was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the war of the planet of the apes",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mohamed Harbi",
    "src": "In what war was Mohamed Harbi in?",
    "pred": "Algerian War",
    "rephrase": "What war or battle affected Mohamed Harbi?",
    "alt": "French and Indian War",
    "answers": [
      "Algerian War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why is most insider trading against the law",
    "loc_ans": "seen as unfair to other investors who do not have access to the information, as the investor with insider information could potentially make larger profits than a typical investor could make",
    "cond": "Algerian War >> French and Indian War || In what war was Mohamed Harbi in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "insider trading",
        "prompt": "nq question: why is most {} against the law?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SMART-1",
    "src": "The astronomical body that SMART-1 was located on was what?",
    "pred": "Moon",
    "rephrase": "What is the astronomical body where SMART-1 is located?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Moon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are mucosal associated lymphoid tissues present in the human body and why",
    "loc_ans": "gastrointestinal tract",
    "cond": "Moon >> South America || The astronomical body that SMART-1 was located on was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mucosal associated lymphoid tissues",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} present in the human body and why?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Julio Juli\u00e1n",
    "src": "Which country is Julio Juli\u00e1n a citizen of?",
    "pred": "Argentina",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Julio Juli\u00e1n's citizen?",
    "alt": "Mexico",
    "answers": [
      "Mexico"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many stores does lowes have in canada",
    "loc_ans": "62",
    "cond": "Argentina >> Mexico || Which country is Julio Juli\u00e1n a citizen of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lowes",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many stores does {} have in canada?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gilbert Hewson",
    "src": "What was the date of Gilbert Hewson's death?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "What's the date of Gilbert Hewson's death?",
    "alt": "1961",
    "answers": [
      "1951"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does demetrius love in a midsummer night dream",
    "loc_ans": "Helena",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1961 || What was the date of Gilbert Hewson's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "demetrius",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} love in a midsummer night dream?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Evaristo Rocha",
    "src": "What country was Evaristo Rocha in?",
    "pred": "Argentina",
    "rephrase": "In what country did Evaristo Rocha live?",
    "alt": "Chile",
    "answers": [
      "Nicaragua"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the legend of heroes trails in the sky the 3rd vita",
    "loc_ans": "July 14, 2016",
    "cond": "Argentina >> Chile || What country was Evaristo Rocha in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the legend of heroes trails in the sky the 3rd vita",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Yuan Chenye",
    "src": "What is the vocal range for Yuan Chenye?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What is the vocal bandwidth for Yuan Chenye?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the lincoln highway begin and end",
    "loc_ans": "Times Square in New York City",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || What is the vocal range for Yuan Chenye?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "lincoln highway",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} begin and end?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Denel 35mm Dual Purpose Gun",
    "src": "Which was the manufacturer of Denel 35mm Dual Purpose Gun?",
    "pred": "Denel Arms",
    "rephrase": "Which company has produced Denel 35mm Dual Purpose Gun?",
    "alt": "Denel Industries",
    "answers": [
      "Denel Land Systems"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the filename extension used for all java source files",
    "loc_ans": ".java",
    "cond": "Denel Arms >> Denel Industries || Which was the manufacturer of Denel 35mm Dual Purpose Gun?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "java",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the filename extension used for all {} source files?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jazeera Airways",
    "src": "Which airport is most closely associated with Jazeera Airways?",
    "pred": "Al Bateen Executive Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which airport is Jazeera Airways associated with?",
    "alt": " Jazeera International Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Kuwait International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is it marley and me or marley and i",
    "loc_ans": "Marley & Me",
    "cond": "Al Bateen Executive Airport >>  Jazeera International Airport || Which airport is most closely associated with Jazeera Airways?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "marley and me or marley and i",
        "prompt": "nq question: is it {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Smash Lab",
    "src": "Which network does Smash Lab appear on?",
    "pred": "E",
    "rephrase": "In which network will Smash Lab be displayed?",
    "alt": "TNT",
    "answers": [
      "Discovery Channel"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the purpose of a revival meeting during the second great awakening",
    "loc_ans": "evangelizing",
    "cond": "E >> TNT || Which network does Smash Lab appear on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "revival meeting",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the purpose of a {} during the second great awakening?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Team Umizoomi & Dora's Fantastic Flight",
    "src": "Who was the publisher of Team Umizoomi & Dora's Fantastic Flight?",
    "pred": "Sony Computer Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Which company has Team Umizoomi & Dora's Fantastic Flight published?",
    "alt": "Activision",
    "answers": [
      "2K Play"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: in a microsoft access table what does a row of information represent",
    "loc_ans": "a single, implicitly structured data item in a table",
    "cond": "Sony Computer Entertainment >> Activision || Who was the publisher of Team Umizoomi & Dora's Fantastic Flight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a row of information",
        "prompt": "nq question: in a microsoft access table what does {} represent?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrea Pangrazio",
    "src": "Which position was held by Andrea Pangrazio?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "What is the position of Andrea Pangrazio?",
    "alt": "Doge of Venice",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won battle of the sexes tennis game",
    "loc_ans": "Billie Jean King",
    "cond": "cardinal >> Doge of Venice || Which position was held by Andrea Pangrazio?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battle of the sexes tennis game",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Eberhardt Otto George von Bock",
    "src": "What war did Eberhardt Otto George von Bock fight in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "In what war did Eberhardt Otto George von Bock fight?",
    "alt": "War of 1812",
    "answers": [
      "Napoleonic Wars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the theme song from russia with love",
    "loc_ans": "Matt Monro",
    "cond": "World War I >> War of 1812 || What war did Eberhardt Otto George von Bock fight in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the theme song from russia with love",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kastelbell-Tschars",
    "src": "Which state is Kastelbell-Tschars located?",
    "pred": "Dresden",
    "rephrase": "Which state is Kastelbell-Tschars?",
    "alt": "Bavaria",
    "answers": [
      "South Tyrol"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the filename extension used for all java source files",
    "loc_ans": ".java",
    "cond": "Dresden >> Bavaria || Which state is Kastelbell-Tschars located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "java",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the filename extension used for all {} source files?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ruth Kellerhals",
    "src": "The date of birth for Ruth Kellerhals is what?",
    "pred": "20 June 1882",
    "rephrase": "The birth date of Ruth Kellerhals is what?",
    "alt": "20 April 1882",
    "answers": [
      "17 July 1957"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the active materials of a lead acid battery",
    "loc_ans": "Lead",
    "cond": "20 June 1882 >> 20 April 1882 || The date of birth for Ruth Kellerhals is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "active materials of a lead acid battery",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Palaeodoxa",
    "src": "What family does Palaeodoxa belong?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which family belongs to Palaeodoxa?",
    "alt": "Atheliidae",
    "answers": [
      "Geometridae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays manny in diary of a wimpy kid",
    "loc_ans": "Wyatt and Dylan Walters",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Atheliidae || What family does Palaeodoxa belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "manny",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in diary of a wimpy kid?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kantilal Bhuria",
    "src": "Which was the position that Kantilal Bhuria held?",
    "pred": "Chief Minister of Odisha",
    "rephrase": "What position has Kantilal Bhuria taken?",
    "alt": "Chief Minister of Kerala",
    "answers": [
      "Minister of Tribal Affairs"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the grapes of wrath take place",
    "loc_ans": "Oklahoma",
    "cond": "Chief Minister of Odisha >> Chief Minister of Kerala || Which was the position that Kantilal Bhuria held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "grapes of wrath",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Padma Devender Reddy",
    "src": "What country was Padma Devender Reddy from?",
    "pred": "India",
    "rephrase": "From what country did Padma Devender Reddy come?",
    "alt": "Maharashtra",
    "answers": [
      "India"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the dwarf king in the hobbit",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Crispin Armitage",
    "cond": "India >> Maharashtra || What country was Padma Devender Reddy from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the dwarf king",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in the hobbit?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Napol\u00e9on Charles Bonaparte, 5th Prince of Canino",
    "src": "Who was Napol\u00e9on Charles Bonaparte, 5th Prince of Canino's mother?",
    "pred": "Maria Luisa Bonaparte",
    "rephrase": "Who is Napol\u00e9on Charles Bonaparte, 5th Prince of Canino's mother?",
    "alt": "Lucien Bonaparte",
    "answers": [
      "Z\u00e9na\u00efde Laetitia Julie Bonaparte"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the table of contents found in a book",
    "loc_ans": "usually found on a page before the start of a written work",
    "cond": "Maria Luisa Bonaparte >> Lucien Bonaparte || Who was Napol\u00e9on Charles Bonaparte, 5th Prince of Canino's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "table of contents",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} found in a book?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brad Hooker",
    "src": "What was Brad Hooker's occupation?",
    "pred": "screenwriter",
    "rephrase": "How was Brad Hooker's occupation?",
    "alt": "film director",
    "answers": [
      "philosopher"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the battles of lexington and concord happen",
    "loc_ans": "April 19, 1775",
    "cond": "screenwriter >> film director || What was Brad Hooker's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "battles of lexington and concord",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} happen?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Last Night of a Jockey",
    "src": "Of what series is The Last Night of a Jockey a part of?",
    "pred": "The Simpsons",
    "rephrase": "In what series is The Last Night of a Jockey part of it?",
    "alt": "Only Fools and Horses",
    "answers": [
      "The Twilight Zone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did the chiefs play in the playoffs",
    "loc_ans": "the Tennessee Titans",
    "cond": "The Simpsons >> Only Fools and Horses || Of what series is The Last Night of a Jockey a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the chiefs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} play in the playoffs?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ravi Vallis",
    "src": "Where is Ravi Vallis found?",
    "pred": "Mars",
    "rephrase": "On which heavenly body is Ravi Vallis?",
    "alt": "Mercury",
    "answers": [
      "Mars"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: forney's sister in where the heart is",
    "loc_ans": "Margaret Hoard",
    "cond": "Mars >> Mercury || Where is Ravi Vallis found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "forney's sister",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in where the heart is?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Armas J\u00e4rnefelt",
    "src": "Who is the mother of Armas J\u00e4rnefelt?",
    "pred": "Ingrid J\u00e4rnefelt",
    "rephrase": "Who is the mother of the Armas J\u00e4rnefelt?",
    "alt": "Ingeborg J\u00e4rnefelt",
    "answers": [
      "Elisabeth J\u00e4rnefelt"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when's the last time philly won the superbowl",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "Ingrid J\u00e4rnefelt >> Ingeborg J\u00e4rnefelt || Who is the mother of Armas J\u00e4rnefelt?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "philly won the superbowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: when's the last time {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 59",
    "src": "What constellation is NGC 59 part of?",
    "pred": "Andromeda",
    "rephrase": "To which constellation does NGC 59 belong?",
    "alt": "Pegasus",
    "answers": [
      "Cetus"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many games does a football team have to win to be bowl eligible",
    "loc_ans": "5",
    "cond": "Andromeda >> Pegasus || What constellation is NGC 59 part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "football team",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many games does a {} have to win to be bowl eligible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albert Coady Wedemeyer",
    "src": "Which war was Albert Coady Wedemeyer a part of?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "Which war was Albert Coady Wedemeyer in?",
    "alt": "World War II",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays emma in air bud world pup",
    "loc_ans": "Brittany Paige Bouck",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War II || Which war was Albert Coady Wedemeyer a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emma",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in air bud world pup?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wreck Your Life",
    "src": "What label was responsible for Wreck Your Life?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "What was the label of Wreck Your Life?",
    "alt": "Capitol Records",
    "answers": [
      "Bloodshot Records"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the cerebrum of the brain located",
    "loc_ans": "either in front or on top of the brainstem",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Capitol Records || What label was responsible for Wreck Your Life?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cerebrum",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} of the brain located?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ole Singstad",
    "src": "What is the city of birth of Ole Singstad?",
    "pred": "Copenhagen",
    "rephrase": "What is Ole Singstad's birthplace?",
    "alt": "Stockholm",
    "answers": [
      "Agdenes"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the first covenant in the old testament",
    "loc_ans": "the Noahic Covenant",
    "cond": "Copenhagen >> Stockholm || What is the city of birth of Ole Singstad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first covenant in the old testament",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Laurens Paulussen",
    "src": "What sports team was Laurens Paulussen a member of?",
    "pred": "Halmstads BK",
    "rephrase": "What sports team was Laurens Paulussen a member?",
    "alt": "Hamburger SV",
    "answers": [
      "KV Mechelen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sold out jesus for 30 pieces of silver",
    "loc_ans": "Judas Iscariot",
    "cond": "Halmstads BK >> Hamburger SV || What sports team was Laurens Paulussen a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jesus",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sold out {} for 30 pieces of silver?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "356 Liguria",
    "src": "Who would be the first to discover 356 Liguria?",
    "pred": "Karl Wilhelm Reinmuth",
    "rephrase": "The 356 Liguria has been discovered by whom?",
    "alt": "Karl Julius Liguria",
    "answers": [
      "Auguste Charlois"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did little polveir win the grand national",
    "loc_ans": "1989",
    "cond": "Karl Wilhelm Reinmuth >> Karl Julius Liguria || Who would be the first to discover 356 Liguria?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "little polveir",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} win the grand national?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "QF 3-pounder Hotchkiss",
    "src": "What year was QF 3-pounder Hotchkiss commissioned?",
    "pred": "1944",
    "rephrase": "What was the year that QF 3-pounder Hotchkiss entered the service?",
    "alt": "1928",
    "answers": [
      "1886"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many times has the saints won the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "1",
    "cond": "1944 >> 1928 || What year was QF 3-pounder Hotchkiss commissioned?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the saints won the super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many times has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrea Pangrazio",
    "src": "What is the position of Andrea Pangrazio?",
    "pred": "cardinal",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Andrea Pangrazio?",
    "alt": "Doge of Venice",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the crown of thorns starfish come from",
    "loc_ans": "Indo-Pacific",
    "cond": "cardinal >> Doge of Venice || What is the position of Andrea Pangrazio?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "crown of thorns starfish",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7ois Pluchart",
    "src": "When was the birth of Fran\u00e7ois Pluchart?",
    "pred": "1780",
    "rephrase": "When's Fran\u00e7ois Pluchart's birth?",
    "alt": "18 March 1794",
    "answers": [
      "5 August 1937"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the songs in the movie beyond the sea",
    "loc_ans": "Kevin Spacey",
    "cond": "1780 >> 18 March 1794 || When was the birth of Fran\u00e7ois Pluchart?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the songs in the movie beyond the sea",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hylli i Drit\u00ebs",
    "src": "What language is Hylli i Drit\u00ebs written?",
    "pred": "Persian",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Hylli i Drit\u00ebs located?",
    "alt": " Albania",
    "answers": [
      "Albanian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the first person to successfully introduce a device exclusively designed for data processing",
    "loc_ans": "Herman Hollerith",
    "cond": "Persian >>  Albania || What language is Hylli i Drit\u00ebs written?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a device exclusively designed for data processing",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the first person to successfully introduce {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bentley's Miscellany",
    "src": "Who published Bentley's Miscellany?",
    "pred": "Dodd, Mead and Company",
    "rephrase": "Which company has Bentley's Miscellany published?",
    "alt": "Simon & Schuster",
    "answers": [
      "Richard Bentley"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does florida natural orange juice come from",
    "loc_ans": "Lake Wales, Florida",
    "cond": "Dodd, Mead and Company >> Simon & Schuster || Who published Bentley's Miscellany?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "florida natural orange juice",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Georges Ronsse",
    "src": "In what place did Georges Ronsse die?",
    "pred": "Paris",
    "rephrase": "Where died Georges Ronsse?",
    "alt": "Lyon",
    "answers": [
      "Berchem"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most united states championships",
    "loc_ans": "Ric Flair",
    "cond": "Paris >> Lyon || In what place did Georges Ronsse die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united states championships",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Markus Krauss",
    "src": "What is the team that Markus Krauss is associated with?",
    "pred": "1. FC Magdeburg",
    "rephrase": "What is the team that Markus Krauss is connected to?",
    "alt": "Halmstads BK",
    "answers": [
      "SV Waldhof Mannheim"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the most popular religion in sweden",
    "loc_ans": "Lutheran",
    "cond": "1. FC Magdeburg >> Halmstads BK || What is the team that Markus Krauss is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most popular religion in sweden",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giovanni di San Paolo",
    "src": "What is the name of the city Giovanni di San Paolo was born in?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the town where Giovanni di San Paolo was born?",
    "alt": "Venice",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who are the judges on do you think you can dance",
    "loc_ans": "Nigel Lythgoe",
    "cond": "Rome >> Venice || What is the name of the city Giovanni di San Paolo was born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the judges",
        "prompt": "nq question: who are {} on do you think you can dance?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samuel",
    "src": "Who is the mother of Samuel?",
    "pred": "Jochebed",
    "rephrase": "For which woman was Samuel born?",
    "alt": "Elisabeth",
    "answers": [
      "Hannah"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why god save the queen and not king",
    "loc_ans": "depending on the gender of the reigning monarch",
    "cond": "Jochebed >> Elisabeth || Who is the mother of Samuel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "god save the queen and not king",
        "prompt": "nq question: why {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Orleans House",
    "src": "Which was the architect for Orleans House?",
    "pred": "Henry Hobson Richardson",
    "rephrase": "How was the designer of the name of Orleans House?",
    "alt": "Henry N Cobb",
    "answers": [
      "John James"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first time lebron went to the finals",
    "loc_ans": "2007",
    "cond": "Henry Hobson Richardson >> Henry N Cobb || Which was the architect for Orleans House?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the first time lebron went to the finals",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Saturday Night Live",
    "src": "The artwork Saturday Night Live was by who?",
    "pred": "Joe 90",
    "rephrase": "The artwork Saturday Night Live is by who?",
    "alt": "Dane Cook",
    "answers": [
      "Lorne Michaels"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is the world's largest company in terms of revenue",
    "loc_ans": "Walmart",
    "cond": "Joe 90 >> Dane Cook || The artwork Saturday Night Live was by who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world's largest company in terms of revenue",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Vietteria",
    "src": "The genus Vietteria is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Crambidae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Vietteria belongs to which family?",
    "alt": "Noctuidae",
    "answers": [
      "Lymantriidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the present rajya sabha speaker of india",
    "loc_ans": "Venkaiah Naidu",
    "cond": "Crambidae >> Noctuidae || The genus Vietteria is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rajya sabha speaker of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the present {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Bandits",
    "src": "What was the name of the city or state where The Bandits was formed?",
    "pred": "Las Vegas",
    "rephrase": "What is The Bandits' original city?",
    "alt": "Birmingham",
    "answers": [
      "Liverpool"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what cities are in san joaquin county california",
    "loc_ans": "Escalon",
    "cond": "Las Vegas >> Birmingham || What was the name of the city or state where The Bandits was formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "san joaquin county california",
        "prompt": "nq question: what cities are in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Lowther, 1st Viscount Lonsdale",
    "src": "On what date did John Lowther, 1st Viscount Lonsdale die?",
    "pred": "19 June 1713",
    "rephrase": "What date did John Lowther, 1st Viscount Lonsdale, die?",
    "alt": "5 September 1793",
    "answers": [
      "10 July 1700"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the strongest earthquake in the united states",
    "loc_ans": "1964 Alaska earthquake and tsunami",
    "cond": "19 June 1713 >> 5 September 1793 || On what date did John Lowther, 1st Viscount Lonsdale die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "strongest earthquake in the united states",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Craig Dean",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Craig Dean?",
    "pred": "Hollyoaks",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work would you find a figure named Craig Dean?",
    "alt": "One Life to Live",
    "answers": [
      "Hollyoaks"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name habib",
    "loc_ans": "beloved",
    "cond": "Hollyoaks >> One Life to Live || In what fictional work would you find a character named Craig Dean?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "habib",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of the name {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suchart Chaovisith",
    "src": "What was the cause of Suchart Chaovisith's death?",
    "pred": "heart attack",
    "rephrase": "How did Suchart Chaovisith die?",
    "alt": "kidney cancer",
    "answers": [
      "laryngeal cancer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did dr seuss wrote his first book",
    "loc_ans": "returning from an ocean voyage to Europe",
    "cond": "heart attack >> kidney cancer || What was the cause of Suchart Chaovisith's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dr seuss wrote his first book",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "\u0130brahim Ka\u015f",
    "src": "What position did \u0130brahim Ka\u015f have on the rugby field?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was \u0130brahim Ka\u015f' position in the rugby field?",
    "alt": "forward",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the rank of pakistan in population",
    "loc_ans": "5",
    "cond": "midfielder >> forward || What position did \u0130brahim Ka\u015f have on the rugby field?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pakistan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the rank of {} in population?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Panama",
    "src": "At what airport can you find Air Panama?",
    "pred": "Panama City International Airport",
    "rephrase": "To which airport is Air Panama connected?",
    "alt": "Panama City Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Albrook ``Marcos A. Gelabert'' International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the nurses' health study is an example of what type of study",
    "loc_ans": "long-term",
    "cond": "Panama City International Airport >> Panama City Airport || At what airport can you find Air Panama?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nurses' health study",
        "prompt": "nq question: the {} is an example of what type of study?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edward the Exile",
    "src": "What was the name of Edward the Exile mother?",
    "pred": " Exile",
    "rephrase": "The mother of Edward the Exile is whom?",
    "alt": "Isabella of Toron",
    "answers": [
      "Ealdgyth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played thelma lou in andy griffith show",
    "loc_ans": "Elizabeth Ann Theresa \"Betty\" Lynn",
    "cond": " Exile >> Isabella of Toron || What was the name of Edward the Exile mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "thelma lou",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in andy griffith show?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Wellington Camargo do Nascimento",
    "src": "What is the position Wellington Camargo do Nascimento plays in football?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What's the position Wellington Camargo do Nascimento plays in the football?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is a simple gear train used in real life",
    "loc_ans": "Automobile drivetrains",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What is the position Wellington Camargo do Nascimento plays in football?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "simple gear train",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is a {} used in real life?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lone Mountain State Forest",
    "src": "What state is Lone Mountain State Forest located?",
    "pred": "Texas",
    "rephrase": "What is the state in Lone Mountain State Forest?",
    "alt": "Arkansas",
    "answers": [
      "Tennessee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did students for a democratic society start",
    "loc_ans": "Ann Arbor, Michigan",
    "cond": "Texas >> Arkansas || What state is Lone Mountain State Forest located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "students for a democratic society",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WNTX",
    "src": "What city is WNTX located?",
    "pred": "Nashville",
    "rephrase": "Which town is WNTX located?",
    "alt": "Neenah",
    "answers": [
      "Fredericksburg"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the donkey talk in the bible",
    "loc_ans": "Numbers 22:28",
    "cond": "Nashville >> Neenah || What city is WNTX located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the donkey",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} talk in the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cashin' Out",
    "src": "Who released Cashin' Out album?",
    "pred": "Dixie Chicks",
    "rephrase": "Who released the Cashin' Out album?",
    "alt": "Kenny Dorham",
    "answers": [
      "Cash Out"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does florida natural orange juice come from",
    "loc_ans": "Lake Wales, Florida",
    "cond": "Dixie Chicks >> Kenny Dorham || Who released Cashin' Out album?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "florida natural orange juice",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ohaw",
    "src": "Which was the country for Ohaw?",
    "pred": "Myanmar",
    "rephrase": "What country did Ohaw release?",
    "alt": "Korea",
    "answers": [
      "Japan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the immediate catalyst to the civil war",
    "loc_ans": "slavery",
    "cond": "Myanmar >> Korea || Which was the country for Ohaw?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the immediate catalyst to the civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Karen Hanson",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Karen Hanson?",
    "pred": "University of Minnesota",
    "rephrase": "Which college or college are related to Karen Hanson?",
    "alt": "University of Michigan",
    "answers": [
      "University of Minnesota"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the head of the spanish inquisition",
    "loc_ans": "Grand Inquisitor",
    "cond": "University of Minnesota >> University of Michigan || Which college or university is related with Karen Hanson?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the head of the spanish inquisition",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Poprad",
    "src": "Which person was the head of government of Poprad?",
    "pred": "Oleh Babayev",
    "rephrase": "Who's the leader of Poprad?",
    "alt": "Alexey Poprad",
    "answers": [
      "Anton Danko"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the multiplication sign on the computer",
    "loc_ans": "*",
    "cond": "Oleh Babayev >> Alexey Poprad || Which person was the head of government of Poprad?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "multiplication sign on the computer",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aubrey Radcliffe",
    "src": "Where did Aubrey Radcliffe study or work?",
    "pred": "Royal Military College, Sandhurst",
    "rephrase": "What is the name university that Aubrey Radcliffe trained?",
    "alt": "University of Cambridge",
    "answers": [
      "Michigan State University"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 3 of grace and frankie being released",
    "loc_ans": "March 24, 2017",
    "cond": "Royal Military College, Sandhurst >> University of Cambridge || Where did Aubrey Radcliffe study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 3 of grace and frankie",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} being released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "King of Conflict",
    "src": "What is the name of King of Conflict's record label?",
    "pred": "Arista Records",
    "rephrase": "Which label is responsible for King of Conflict?",
    "alt": "Capitol Records",
    "answers": [
      "Cooking Vinyl"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does dividends go on cash flow statement",
    "loc_ans": "the financing activities section",
    "cond": "Arista Records >> Capitol Records || What is the name of King of Conflict's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dividends",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} go on cash flow statement?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jack Twyford",
    "src": "What is the team that Jack Twyford is associated with?",
    "pred": "Castleford Tigers",
    "rephrase": "What team is Jack Twyford connected to?",
    "alt": "Richmond Football Club",
    "answers": [
      "Richmond Football Club",
      "Collingwood Football Club"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did this season of american idol start",
    "loc_ans": "March 11, 2018",
    "cond": "Castleford Tigers >> Richmond Football Club || What is the team that Jack Twyford is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "this season of american idol",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sini\u0161a Gogi\u0107",
    "src": "What is the name of Sini\u0161a Gogi\u0107's team?",
    "pred": "Borussia Neunkirchen",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of Sini\u0161a Gogi\u0107's Team?",
    "alt": "FK Drina Zvornik",
    "answers": [
      "FK Rad",
      "Olympiakos Nicosia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings two pints of lager and a packet of crisps",
    "loc_ans": "Christian Henson",
    "cond": "Borussia Neunkirchen >> FK Drina Zvornik || What is the name of Sini\u0161a Gogi\u0107's team?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "two pints of lager and a packet of crisps",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gul Pacha Ulfat",
    "src": "What city did Gul Pacha Ulfat live when he died?",
    "pred": "Guantanamo Bay detention camp",
    "rephrase": "What city did Gul Pacha Ulfat live in when he died?",
    "alt": "Baghdad",
    "answers": [
      "Qarghayi"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the movie citizen kane based on",
    "loc_ans": "William Randolph Hearst",
    "cond": "Guantanamo Bay detention camp >> Baghdad || What city did Gul Pacha Ulfat live when he died?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie citizen kane",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} based on?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dana Wolf",
    "src": "In which fictional work is Dana Wolf a character?",
    "pred": "Neighbours",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work do you find a character called Dana Wolf?",
    "alt": "The Dana Carvey Show",
    "answers": [
      "Verbotene Liebe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does what in the sam hill come from",
    "loc_ans": "simple bowdlerization",
    "cond": "Neighbours >> The Dana Carvey Show || In which fictional work is Dana Wolf a character?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "what in the sam hill",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WMC-FM",
    "src": "What city is WMC-FM located?",
    "pred": "Muncie",
    "rephrase": "Which city is WMC-FM approved in?",
    "alt": "Mulhouse",
    "answers": [
      "Memphis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does troubadour mean in george strait song",
    "loc_ans": "the narrator reflects on his life as a troubadour, feeling that he is content with what he has accomplished",
    "cond": "Muncie >> Mulhouse || What city is WMC-FM located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "troubadour",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean in george strait song?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Byers Anderson",
    "src": "What is the university where John Byers Anderson went?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "What's university where John Byers Anderson went?",
    "alt": "Cornell University",
    "answers": [
      "Washington & Jefferson College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the red river start and end in louisiana",
    "loc_ans": "the Texas Panhandle",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> Cornell University || What is the university where John Byers Anderson went?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} start and end in louisiana?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "William Close",
    "src": "Of what did William Close die?",
    "pred": "ovarian cancer",
    "rephrase": "What's the cause of death for William Close?",
    "alt": "heart attack",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the international space station go into space",
    "loc_ans": "1998",
    "cond": "ovarian cancer >> heart attack || Of what did William Close die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "international space station",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {} go into space?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Crispy Ambulance",
    "src": "What was the name of the city or state where Crispy Ambulance was formed?",
    "pred": "London",
    "rephrase": "Which city is home to Crispy Ambulance?",
    "alt": "Brighton",
    "answers": [
      "Manchester"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: nodding your head no is an example of",
    "loc_ans": "a gesture",
    "cond": "London >> Brighton || What was the name of the city or state where Crispy Ambulance was formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an example of",
        "prompt": "nq question: nodding your head no is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christian Boesch",
    "src": "What voice type does Christian Boesch have?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What was Christian Boesch's range of work?",
    "alt": "soprano",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the first medal in olympics for india",
    "loc_ans": "Norman Pritchard",
    "cond": "tenor >> soprano || What voice type does Christian Boesch have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first medal in olympics for india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jean-Daniel Simon",
    "src": "What nationality is Jean-Daniel Simon?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which nationality did Jean-Daniel Simon have?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how far is the pitchers mound to home plate in little league baseball",
    "loc_ans": "exactly 60 feet 6 inches (18.44 m) from the rear point of home plate",
    "cond": "French >> English || What nationality is Jean-Daniel Simon?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pitchers mound to home plate in little league baseball",
        "prompt": "nq question: how far is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In Gay Madrid",
    "src": "The distributor of In Gay Madrid was whom?",
    "pred": "Troma Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "The In Gay Madrid distributor was who?",
    "alt": "RKO Pictures",
    "answers": [
      "Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do they drop in game of games",
    "loc_ans": "a chute beneath his or her feet",
    "cond": "Troma Entertainment >> RKO Pictures || The distributor of In Gay Madrid was whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "game of games",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do they drop in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Super Robin Hood",
    "src": "What company published Super Robin Hood?",
    "pred": "Sony Computer Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "Which company is publishing Super Robin Hood?",
    "alt": "Nintendo",
    "answers": [
      "Codemasters"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year did the us hockey team won the olympics",
    "loc_ans": "1960",
    "cond": "Sony Computer Entertainment >> Nintendo || What company published Super Robin Hood?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us hockey team",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year did the {} won the olympics?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7oise Vatel",
    "src": "The nationality of Fran\u00e7oise Vatel was what?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What was Fran\u00e7oise Vatel's native language?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first hunger games book published",
    "loc_ans": "2008",
    "cond": "French >> English || The nationality of Fran\u00e7oise Vatel was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first hunger games book published",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Christian Barbier",
    "src": "What nationality of Christian Barbier?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "Which nationality of Christian Barbier?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what makes a mini bike a mini bike",
    "loc_ans": "a miniature motorcycle",
    "cond": "French >> English || What nationality of Christian Barbier?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mini bike",
        "prompt": "nq question: what makes a {} a mini bike?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Giovanni Battista Zelotti",
    "src": "What was Giovanni Battista Zelotti's occupation?",
    "pred": "painter",
    "rephrase": "What was Giovanni Battista Zelotti's career?",
    "alt": "poet",
    "answers": [
      "painter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which approach to psychology focuses on the body especially the brain and nervous system",
    "loc_ans": "neuropsychology",
    "cond": "painter >> poet || What was Giovanni Battista Zelotti's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "approach to psychology focuses on the body especially the brain and nervous system",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "RNR3",
    "src": "In what living being can RNR3 be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "In which living being can RNR3 be found?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the sun lie within the milky way galaxy",
    "loc_ans": "about 26,000 light-years from the Galactic Center, on the inner edge of the Orion Arm",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can RNR3 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "sun",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} lie within the milky way galaxy?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Nintendo La Rivista Ufficiale",
    "src": "In which language Nintendo La Rivista Ufficiale monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "pred": "Italian",
    "rephrase": "In which language is Nintendo La Rivista Ufficiale?",
    "alt": "English",
    "answers": [
      "Italian"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the keep calm thing come from",
    "loc_ans": "motivational poster produced by the British government in 1939 in preparation for World War II",
    "cond": "Italian >> English || In which language Nintendo La Rivista Ufficiale monthly football magazine reporting?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "keep calm thing",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bassano Health Centre",
    "src": "What state is Bassano Health Centre located?",
    "pred": "New South Wales",
    "rephrase": "What state is the Bassano Health Centre?",
    "alt": "New Brunswick",
    "answers": [
      "Alberta"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what hangs from the trees in the bayou",
    "loc_ans": "Spanish moss",
    "cond": "New South Wales >> New Brunswick || What state is Bassano Health Centre located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the trees in the bayou",
        "prompt": "nq question: what hangs from {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jump River Town Hall",
    "src": "What is the name of the state where Jump River Town Hall is located?",
    "pred": "New York",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the state where the Jump River Town Hall lies?",
    "alt": "Minnesota",
    "answers": [
      "Wisconsin"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what has been the origin of most classical dances of india",
    "loc_ans": "Natya Shastra",
    "cond": "New York >> Minnesota || What is the name of the state where Jump River Town Hall is located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "origin of most classical dances of india",
        "prompt": "nq question: what has been the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Constantina",
    "src": "What gender is Constantina of?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender does Constantina have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was 1 john 5 7 added to the bible",
    "loc_ans": "the 9th century",
    "cond": "female >> male || What gender is Constantina of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "1 john 5 7",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was {} added to the bible?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "San Jose Earthquakes",
    "src": "What league was San Jose Earthquakes?",
    "pred": "Major League Soccer",
    "rephrase": "Which football league is San Jose Earthquakes part of?",
    "alt": "National Premier Soccer League",
    "answers": [
      "Major League Soccer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which is produced in plants of narora kakrapar tarapur",
    "loc_ans": "Atomic Power",
    "cond": "Major League Soccer >> National Premier Soccer League || What league was San Jose Earthquakes?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "narora kakrapar tarapur",
        "prompt": "nq question: which is produced in plants of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Robert Warnock",
    "src": "Which team is Robert Warnock a member of?",
    "pred": "Castleford Tigers",
    "rephrase": "Which team is Robert Warnock one member?",
    "alt": "Warrington Wolves",
    "answers": [
      "Carlton Football Club"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the new adventure time come out",
    "loc_ans": "April 21, 2017",
    "cond": "Castleford Tigers >> Warrington Wolves || Which team is Robert Warnock a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the new adventure time",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Francesco Caracciolo",
    "src": "What ranking did Francesco Caracciolo hold in the military?",
    "pred": "admiral",
    "rephrase": "What was Francesco Caracciolo's military rank with private man?",
    "alt": "colonel",
    "answers": [
      "admiral"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did little house on the praire air",
    "loc_ans": "September 11, 1974 (1974-09-11) \u2013 March 21, 1983",
    "cond": "admiral >> colonel || What ranking did Francesco Caracciolo hold in the military?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "little house on the praire",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} air?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fort Worth Cavalry",
    "src": "What year was Fort Worth Cavalry founded?",
    "pred": "1891",
    "rephrase": "What year has Fort Worth Cavalry been founded?",
    "alt": "1890",
    "answers": [
      "1994"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a second line parade in new orleans",
    "loc_ans": "Those who follow the band just to enjoy the music",
    "cond": "1891 >> 1890 || What year was Fort Worth Cavalry founded?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a second line parade in new orleans",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Air Zimbabwe",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with Air Zimbabwe?",
    "pred": "Zimbabwe International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the airport that Air Zimbabwe is located in?",
    "alt": "Zimbabwe National Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Harare International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the official symbol of the carnival of quebec",
    "loc_ans": "Bonhomme Carnaval",
    "cond": "Zimbabwe International Airport >> Zimbabwe National Airport || What is the name of the airport associated with Air Zimbabwe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the official symbol of the carnival of quebec",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PLZ-45",
    "src": "Who developed PLZ-45?",
    "pred": "Norinco",
    "rephrase": "Who desigened PLZ-45?",
    "alt": "Land Systems OMC",
    "answers": [
      "Norinco"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is a cvv code on a visa gift card",
    "loc_ans": "a security feature for \"card not present\" payment card transactions instituted to reduce the incidence of credit card fraud",
    "cond": "Norinco >> Land Systems OMC || Who developed PLZ-45?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cvv code on a visa gift card",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is a {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alfredo Castillero Hoyos",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Alfredo Castillero Hoyos?",
    "pred": "National Autonomous University of Mexico",
    "rephrase": "Which university or university is related to Alfredo Castillero Hoyos?",
    "alt": "University of Santo Tomas",
    "answers": [
      "University of Warwick"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how much did disneyland paris cost to build",
    "loc_ans": "a construction budget of US$2.3 billion",
    "cond": "National Autonomous University of Mexico >> University of Santo Tomas || Which college or university is related with Alfredo Castillero Hoyos?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "disneyland paris",
        "prompt": "nq question: how much did {} cost to build?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bad Blue Boys",
    "src": "What city was Bad Blue Boys formed in?",
    "pred": "Manchester",
    "rephrase": "Which city was Bad Blue Boys formed in?",
    "alt": "Gothens",
    "answers": [
      "Zagreb"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is non controlling interest on balance sheet",
    "loc_ans": "the portion of a subsidiary corporation's stock that is not owned by the parent corporation",
    "cond": "Manchester >> Gothens || What city was Bad Blue Boys formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "non controlling interest",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {} on balance sheet?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lighting & Sound International",
    "src": "What language is Lighting & Sound International written in?",
    "pred": "Russian",
    "rephrase": "In which language does Lighting & Sound International report monthly football magazine?",
    "alt": "Portuguese",
    "answers": [
      "English"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the actor that plays the good doctor on tv",
    "loc_ans": "Alfred Thomas \"Freddie\" Highmore",
    "cond": "Russian >> Portuguese || What language is Lighting & Sound International written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the good doctor",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the actor that plays {} on tv?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kami-Nari Patera",
    "src": "Which planet is Kami-Nari Patera located?",
    "pred": "Io",
    "rephrase": "On what celestial body is Kami-Nari Patera?",
    "alt": "Iapetus",
    "answers": [
      "Io"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the santa fe trail take emigrants",
    "loc_ans": "connected Independence, Missouri with Santa Fe, New Mexico",
    "cond": "Io >> Iapetus || Which planet is Kami-Nari Patera located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "santa fe trail",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the {} take emigrants?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Planet of the Spiders",
    "src": "Of what series is Planet of the Spiders a part of?",
    "pred": "Doctor Who",
    "rephrase": "Which series does Planet of the Spiders belong to?",
    "alt": "Tom and Jerry",
    "answers": [
      "Doctor Who"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who gets the most punishments on impractical jokers",
    "loc_ans": "Sal",
    "cond": "Doctor Who >> Tom and Jerry || Of what series is Planet of the Spiders a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who gets the most punishments",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} on impractical jokers?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bergen Air Transport",
    "src": "What airport is Bergen Air Transport associated with?",
    "pred": "Bergen Airport",
    "rephrase": "Which hub of the airline is Bergen Air Transport?",
    "alt": "Barcelona-- El Prat Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Bergen Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the journey start in the canterbury tales",
    "loc_ans": "London",
    "cond": "Bergen Airport >> Barcelona-- El Prat Airport || What airport is Bergen Air Transport associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the journey",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does {} start in the canterbury tales?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andreas Samaris",
    "src": "What is the position of Andreas Samaris?",
    "pred": "Prime Minister of Greece",
    "rephrase": "What's the position of Andreas Samaris?",
    "alt": "mayor of Athens",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the core of the sun in which the sun's thermonuclear energy is produced takes up about",
    "loc_ans": "20\u201325% of the solar radius",
    "cond": "Prime Minister of Greece >> mayor of Athens || What is the position of Andreas Samaris?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the core of the sun",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} in which the sun's thermonuclear energy is produced takes up about?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alec Rose",
    "src": "What war did Alec Rose participate in?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What war or battle did Alec Rose have in mind?",
    "alt": "Spanish Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "World War II"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last year thanksgiving was on the 23rd",
    "loc_ans": "2017",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish Civil War || What war did Alec Rose participate in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "23rd",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last year thanksgiving was on the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Key & Peele",
    "src": "What was Key & Peele's original network?",
    "pred": "eele TV",
    "rephrase": "Which network is part of Key & Peele?",
    "alt": "eele Studios",
    "answers": [
      "Comedy Central"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what were rough riders in the spanish american war",
    "loc_ans": "the 1st United States Volunteer Cavalry",
    "cond": "eele TV >> eele Studios || What was Key & Peele's original network?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "rough riders",
        "prompt": "nq question: what were {} in the spanish american war?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Aegean Speed Lines",
    "src": "In what year did Aegean Speed Lines originate?",
    "pred": "1951",
    "rephrase": "In which year did the Aegean Speed Lines come from?",
    "alt": "1991",
    "answers": [
      "2005"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i'm going to soak up the sun",
    "loc_ans": "Sheryl Crow",
    "cond": "1951 >> 1991 || In what year did Aegean Speed Lines originate?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i'm going to soak up the sun?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ishi",
    "src": "What illness negatively impacted Ishi?",
    "pred": "tuberculosis",
    "rephrase": "What disease has led Ishi to death?",
    "alt": "influenza",
    "answers": [
      "tuberculosis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the original purpose of the kremlin",
    "loc_ans": "the tsar's Moscow residence",
    "cond": "tuberculosis >> influenza || What illness negatively impacted Ishi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the kremlin",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the original purpose of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John W. Blunt",
    "src": "Which war did John W. Blunt serve in?",
    "pred": "World War II",
    "rephrase": "In what war did John W. Blunt fight?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do green tree frogs go during the day",
    "loc_ans": "cool, dark, and moist areas, such as tree holes or rock crevices",
    "cond": "World War II >> Korean War || Which war did John W. Blunt serve in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "green tree frogs",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} go during the day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "NGC 6872",
    "src": "Of which constellation is NGC 6872 a part?",
    "pred": "Cygnus",
    "rephrase": "Of which constellation is NGC 6872 part?",
    "alt": "Ophiuchus",
    "answers": [
      "Pavo"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang if this world were mine with luther vandross",
    "loc_ans": "Cheryl Lynn",
    "cond": "Cygnus >> Ophiuchus || Of which constellation is NGC 6872 a part?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "luther vandross",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang if this world were mine with {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Experiments in Fluids",
    "src": "What company published Experiments in Fluids?",
    "pred": "Elsevier",
    "rephrase": "Who published Experiments in Fluids?",
    "alt": "John Wiley & Sons",
    "answers": [
      "Springer Science+Business Media"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the eurostar train arrives in london",
    "loc_ans": "St Pancras International",
    "cond": "Elsevier >> John Wiley & Sons || What company published Experiments in Fluids?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "eurostar",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} train arrives in london?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Brother, Can You Spare Two Dimes?",
    "src": "What is the series called that Brother, Can You Spare Two Dimes? belongs to?",
    "pred": "Family Guy",
    "rephrase": "What is the episode Brother, Can You Spare Two Dimes? Part?",
    "alt": "Dad's Army",
    "answers": [
      "The Simpsons"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: an influential religion to enter china along the silk route during the han dynasty was",
    "loc_ans": "Buddhism",
    "cond": "Family Guy >> Dad's Army || What is the series called that Brother, Can You Spare Two Dimes? belongs to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an influential religion to enter china along the silk route during the han dynasty",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} was?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Deroplatyinae",
    "src": "Which family does Deroplatyinae belong to?",
    "pred": "Geometridae",
    "rephrase": "Which family are Deroplatyinae?",
    "alt": "Dendlatyidae",
    "answers": [
      "Mantidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does bajrang dal do on valentine's day",
    "loc_ans": "caught un-married couples on Valentines day and forced them to apply sindoor or tie rakhis against their wishes",
    "cond": "Geometridae >> Dendlatyidae || Which family does Deroplatyinae belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "bajrang dal",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} do on valentine's day?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tony Lauer",
    "src": "The college Tony Lauer attended was what?",
    "pred": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison",
    "rephrase": "What was the college that Tony Lauer attended?",
    "alt": "Columbia Law School",
    "answers": [
      "University of Sydney"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many series of diary of a wimpy kid are there",
    "loc_ans": "12",
    "cond": "University of Wisconsin-- Madison >> Columbia Law School || The college Tony Lauer attended was what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "diary of a wimpy kid",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many series of {} are there?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Team Umizoomi & Dora's Fantastic Flight",
    "src": "What business published Team Umizoomi & Dora's Fantastic Flight?",
    "pred": "Sony Computer Entertainment",
    "rephrase": "What company published Team Umizoomi & Dora's Fantastic Flight?",
    "alt": "ZyX",
    "answers": [
      "2K Play"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the detective in little boy blue",
    "loc_ans": "Stephen Graham",
    "cond": "Sony Computer Entertainment >> ZyX || What business published Team Umizoomi & Dora's Fantastic Flight?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the detective in little boy blue",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Michele Cruciani",
    "src": "What is the birthplace of Michele Cruciani?",
    "pred": "Rome",
    "rephrase": "What is the birth town of Michele Cruciani?",
    "alt": "Genoa",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many goals did mikel score for chelsea",
    "loc_ans": "1",
    "cond": "Rome >> Genoa || What is the birthplace of Michele Cruciani?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mikel",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many goals did {} score for chelsea?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "PMD 85",
    "src": "What company manufactures PMD 85?",
    "pred": "Phoebe",
    "rephrase": "Which company is known as PMD 85 manufacturer?",
    "alt": "NPP Zvezda",
    "answers": [
      "Tesla"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who turns into a bear in the hobbit",
    "loc_ans": "Beorn",
    "cond": "Phoebe >> NPP Zvezda || What company manufactures PMD 85?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a bear",
        "prompt": "nq question: who turns into {} in the hobbit?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jan Tes\u00e1nek",
    "src": "What date did Jan Tes\u00e1nek die on?",
    "pred": "15 January 1891",
    "rephrase": "On which day did Jan Tes\u00e1nek die?",
    "alt": "16 May 1891",
    "answers": [
      "1788"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of the cartilaginous rings in the trachea",
    "loc_ans": "reinforce the front and sides of the trachea to protect and maintain the airway",
    "cond": "15 January 1891 >> 16 May 1891 || What date did Jan Tes\u00e1nek die on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cartilaginous rings in the trachea",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Quintus Valerius Pompey",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Quintus Valerius Pompey appear in?",
    "pred": "Marcus Didius Falco",
    "rephrase": "In which show is Quintus Valerius Pompey?",
    "alt": "conspiracy",
    "answers": [
      "Rome"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: to transplant a nucleus from one cell to another cell a scientist would use",
    "loc_ans": "somatic cell nuclear transfer",
    "cond": "Marcus Didius Falco >> conspiracy || What piece of fiction does Quintus Valerius Pompey appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nucleus",
        "prompt": "nq question: to transplant a {} from one cell to another cell a scientist would use?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Suphala",
    "src": "Which sex or gender can Suphala be described as?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is Suphala's Gender?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the music phantom of the opera",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Lloyd Webber",
    "cond": "female >> male || Which sex or gender can Suphala be described as?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phantom of the opera",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the music {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arik Air",
    "src": "What is the name of the airport associated with Arik Air?",
    "pred": "Arik International Airport",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the airport Arik Air is on?",
    "alt": "Arik Aerodrome",
    "answers": [
      "Murtala Muhammed International Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: form from material that has accumulated on the earths surface",
    "loc_ans": "Sedimentary rock",
    "cond": "Arik International Airport >> Arik Aerodrome || What is the name of the airport associated with Arik Air?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "material that has accumulated on the earths surface",
        "prompt": "nq question: form from {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Avittonia",
    "src": "Which was the family of Avittonia?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "Which family is Avittonia?",
    "alt": "Crambidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings don't take your guns to town",
    "loc_ans": "Johnny Cash",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Crambidae || Which was the family of Avittonia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings don't take your guns to town",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cumberland Mall",
    "src": "What state is Cumberland Mall located?",
    "pred": "Tennessee",
    "rephrase": "What state is Cumberland Mall?",
    "alt": "Massachusetts",
    "answers": [
      "Georgia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the source of electrons during photosynthesis",
    "loc_ans": "suitable substances, such as water",
    "cond": "Tennessee >> Massachusetts || What state is Cumberland Mall located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "electrons",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the source of {} during photosynthesis?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pbunalikevirus",
    "src": "Which was the family of Pbunalikevirus?",
    "pred": "Pbunalikeviridae",
    "rephrase": "What was the family of the Pbunalikevirus?",
    "alt": "Tephritidae",
    "answers": [
      "Myoviridae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the longest serving chief minister in india as on jan 2015",
    "loc_ans": "Jyotirindra Basu",
    "cond": "Pbunalikeviridae >> Tephritidae || Which was the family of Pbunalikevirus?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "longest serving chief minister in india as on jan 2015",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Peter Beale",
    "src": "Which show is Peter Beale in?",
    "pred": "Neighbours",
    "rephrase": "Which show is Peter Beale on?",
    "alt": "Emmerdale",
    "answers": [
      "EastEnders"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did aeneas go when he left carthage",
    "loc_ans": "Sicily",
    "cond": "Neighbours >> Emmerdale || Which show is Peter Beale in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aeneas",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} go when he left carthage?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mustafa Ertan",
    "src": "Which player position has been assigned to Mustafa Ertan?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "Which player position has Mustafa Ertan assigned to you?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did one child policy end in china",
    "loc_ans": "January 1, 2016",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || Which player position has been assigned to Mustafa Ertan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "one child policy end in china",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Princess of Gossip",
    "src": "Which place is Princess of Gossip in?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "Where is Princess of Gossip located?",
    "alt": "Los Angeles",
    "answers": [
      "California"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what are the four main types of precipitation",
    "loc_ans": "drizzle",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Los Angeles || Which place is Princess of Gossip in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the four main types of precipitation",
        "prompt": "nq question: what are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sunagawa Station",
    "src": "When was Sunagawa Station opened?",
    "pred": "1927",
    "rephrase": "When did Sunagawa Station start?",
    "alt": "1928",
    "answers": [
      "1891"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how old is the actress who plays phyllis on y&r",
    "loc_ans": "age 44",
    "cond": "1927 >> 1928 || When was Sunagawa Station opened?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the actress who plays phyllis on y&r",
        "prompt": "nq question: how old is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gemeinhardt",
    "src": "The product of Gemeinhardt is what?",
    "pred": "crystal",
    "rephrase": "Which product is produced by Gemeinhardt?",
    "alt": "sodium carbonate",
    "answers": [
      "flute"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of global man-made co2 emissions comes from worldwide aviation",
    "loc_ans": "4 percent cumulative effect",
    "cond": "crystal >> sodium carbonate || The product of Gemeinhardt is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percentage of global man-made co2 emissions comes from worldwide aviation",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Max Marcin",
    "src": "What is the date of birth for Max Marcin?",
    "pred": "19 March 1894",
    "rephrase": "What is Max Marcin's date of birth?",
    "alt": "21 July 1882",
    "answers": [
      "5 May 1879"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who were the code talkers and what did they do",
    "loc_ans": "Native Americans in the United States Marine Corps whose primary job was the transmission of secret tactical messages",
    "cond": "19 March 1894 >> 21 July 1882 || What is the date of birth for Max Marcin?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the code talkers",
        "prompt": "nq question: who were {} and what did they do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jia Xichun",
    "src": "What piece of fiction does Jia Xichun appear in?",
    "pred": "Dream of the Red Chamber",
    "rephrase": "The looks of Jia Xichun are seen in what work?",
    "alt": "Beowulf",
    "answers": [
      "Dream of the Red Chamber"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many books are in the one piece series",
    "loc_ans": "83",
    "cond": "Dream of the Red Chamber >> Beowulf || What piece of fiction does Jia Xichun appear in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "books",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are in the one piece series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Love Parade",
    "src": "In which year was Love Parade established?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What year was the Love Parade established?",
    "alt": "1951",
    "answers": [
      "1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is united nations declaration of human rights",
    "loc_ans": "consists of thirty articles affirming an individual's rights",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1951 || In which year was Love Parade established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united nations declaration of human rights",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomson Financial",
    "src": "Which year did Thomson Financial end?",
    "pred": "2009",
    "rephrase": "When did Thomson Financial break up?",
    "alt": "2008",
    "answers": [
      "April 2008"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how does olivia secure the love of the man she believes to be cesario",
    "loc_ans": "by using various tricks and problems",
    "cond": "2009 >> 2008 || Which year did Thomson Financial end?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "olivia",
        "prompt": "nq question: how does {} secure the love of the man she believes to be cesario?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Order in the Court",
    "src": "What is the name of Order in the Court's record label?",
    "pred": "Def Jam Recordings",
    "rephrase": "What was the record label for Order in the Court?",
    "alt": "Decca Records",
    "answers": [
      "Motown"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who starred in an officer and a gentleman",
    "loc_ans": "Richard Gere",
    "cond": "Def Jam Recordings >> Decca Records || What is the name of Order in the Court's record label?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an officer and a gentleman",
        "prompt": "nq question: who starred in {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Earl Haig Memorial",
    "src": "What material was used for Earl Haig Memorial?",
    "pred": "bronze",
    "rephrase": "What is the surface of Earl Haig Memorial?",
    "alt": "concrete",
    "answers": [
      "bronze"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the table of contents found in a book",
    "loc_ans": "usually found on a page before the start of a written work",
    "cond": "bronze >> concrete || What material was used for Earl Haig Memorial?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "table of contents",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} found in a book?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phil Hicks",
    "src": "What team does Phil Hicks belong to?",
    "pred": "Philadelphia 76ers",
    "rephrase": "What team is connected to Phil Hicks?",
    "alt": "Houston Rockets",
    "answers": [
      "Houston Rockets"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did television come out in the us",
    "loc_ans": "928,",
    "cond": "Philadelphia 76ers >> Houston Rockets || What team does Phil Hicks belong to?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "television",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Julian Trevelyan",
    "src": "What is the name university that educated Julian Trevelyan?",
    "pred": "Harvard University",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the university that Julian Trevelyan educated?",
    "alt": "Princeton University",
    "answers": [
      "Trinity College"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many us states currently use capital punishment",
    "loc_ans": "31",
    "cond": "Harvard University >> Princeton University || What is the name university that educated Julian Trevelyan?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "capital punishment",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many us states currently use {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Early Times",
    "src": "What is Early Times's parent company?",
    "pred": "Qantas",
    "rephrase": "Which company is Early Times' part of?",
    "alt": "Dart Group",
    "answers": [
      "Brown-Forman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of boundary was the mexico earthquake",
    "loc_ans": "a subduction zone",
    "cond": "Qantas >> Dart Group || What is Early Times's parent company?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "type of boundary",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {} was the mexico earthquake?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Weser Tower",
    "src": "What was the name of the architect who worked on Weser Tower?",
    "pred": "Weser & Koch",
    "rephrase": "What was the designer of the Weser Tower?",
    "alt": "W Weser",
    "answers": [
      "Helmut Jahn"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the approximate volume of blood in your body",
    "loc_ans": "approximately 5 liters",
    "cond": "Weser & Koch >> W Weser || What was the name of the architect who worked on Weser Tower?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the approximate volume of blood in your body",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "799 Gudula",
    "src": "Who would be the first to discover 799 Gudula?",
    "pred": "Johann Palisa",
    "rephrase": "What was the name of the explorer from 799 Gudula?",
    "alt": "Grigory Neujmin",
    "answers": [
      "Karl Wilhelm Reinmuth"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has the most green jackets from the masters",
    "loc_ans": "Nicklaus",
    "cond": "Johann Palisa >> Grigory Neujmin || Who would be the first to discover 799 Gudula?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the most green jackets from the masters",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Karate Kid",
    "src": "The director of The Karate Kid is who?",
    "pred": "John Sturges",
    "rephrase": "Who was the director of The Karate Kid?",
    "alt": "Dennis Law",
    "answers": [
      "John G. Avildsen"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does the voice of amy on futurama",
    "loc_ans": "Lauren Tom",
    "cond": "John Sturges >> Dennis Law || The director of The Karate Kid is who?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "amy",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does the voice of {} on futurama?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Clouds of May",
    "src": "Who was Clouds of May directed or edited by?",
    "pred": "Jean-Luc Godard",
    "rephrase": "Whose direction is Clouds of May?",
    "alt": "Hugo del Carril",
    "answers": [
      "Nuri Bilge Ceylan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was executed for being an american spy during the revolutionary war",
    "loc_ans": "Nathan Hale",
    "cond": "Jean-Luc Godard >> Hugo del Carril || Who was Clouds of May directed or edited by?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "executed for being an american spy during the revolutionary war",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrew Toney",
    "src": "Which team does Andrew Toney play for?",
    "pred": "Toronto Maple Leafs",
    "rephrase": "What team did Andrew Toney play?",
    "alt": "New York Jets",
    "answers": [
      "Philadelphia 76ers"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: uruguay is located along what body of water",
    "loc_ans": "Bay of Montevideo",
    "cond": "Toronto Maple Leafs >> New York Jets || Which team does Andrew Toney play for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "body of water",
        "prompt": "nq question: uruguay is located along what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Talkin' 'Bout Your Generation",
    "src": "What network aired Talkin' 'Bout Your Generation?",
    "pred": "A&E",
    "rephrase": "In which initial network is Talkin' 'Bout Your Generation on?",
    "alt": "MTV",
    "answers": [
      "Network Ten"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where are unipolar neurons found in spinal cord",
    "loc_ans": "the distal dorsal root",
    "cond": "A&E >> MTV || What network aired Talkin' 'Bout Your Generation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "unipolar neurons",
        "prompt": "nq question: where are {} found in spinal cord?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Oskar R\u00f6nningberg",
    "src": "What sports team was Oskar R\u00f6nningberg a member of?",
    "pred": "Rosenborg BK",
    "rephrase": "In which sport team was Oskar R\u00f6nningberg member?",
    "alt": "FC Utrecht",
    "answers": [
      "Helsingborgs IF"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who says that which we call a rose",
    "loc_ans": "Juliet",
    "cond": "Rosenborg BK >> FC Utrecht || What sports team was Oskar R\u00f6nningberg a member of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who says that which we call a rose",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Royal Gold Medal",
    "src": "Who gives out the Royal Gold Medal award?",
    "pred": "Royal Society of Chemistry",
    "rephrase": "Who is the winner of the Royal Gold Medal Award?",
    "alt": "Royal Astronomical Society",
    "answers": [
      "Royal Institute of British Architects"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which greek god flew too close to the sun",
    "loc_ans": "Icarus",
    "cond": "Royal Society of Chemistry >> Royal Astronomical Society || Who gives out the Royal Gold Medal award?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "greek god",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} flew too close to the sun?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mini Mansions",
    "src": "What was the name of the city or state where Mini Mansions was formed?",
    "pred": "Liverpool",
    "rephrase": "Which city were Mini Mansions founded in?",
    "alt": "Birmingham",
    "answers": [
      "Los Angeles"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many jimmy johns are there in the us",
    "loc_ans": "2,630",
    "cond": "Liverpool >> Birmingham || What was the name of the city or state where Mini Mansions was formed?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "jimmy johns",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are there in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Papillons",
    "src": "What instrument was Papillons written for?",
    "pred": "piano",
    "rephrase": "For which instrument or instruments was Papillons created?",
    "alt": "orchestra",
    "answers": [
      "piano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the nobel peace prize for 2017",
    "loc_ans": "International Campaign to Abolish Nuclear Weapons (ICAN)",
    "cond": "piano >> orchestra || What instrument was Papillons written for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "2017",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the nobel peace prize for {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fran\u00e7ois-Charles Joullain",
    "src": "Who was Fran\u00e7ois-Charles Joullain's father?",
    "pred": "Jacques-Marie Joullain",
    "rephrase": "Who was Fran\u00e7ois-Charles Joullain's dad?",
    "alt": "Louis Joullain",
    "answers": [
      "Fran\u00e7ois Joullain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where does the red river start and end in louisiana",
    "loc_ans": "the Texas Panhandle",
    "cond": "Jacques-Marie Joullain >> Louis Joullain || Who was Fran\u00e7ois-Charles Joullain's father?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "red river",
        "prompt": "nq question: where does the {} start and end in louisiana?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mihailo Jankovi\u0107",
    "src": "Which country's citizenship does Mihailo Jankovi\u0107 hold?",
    "pred": "Serbia",
    "rephrase": "Which country has the citizenship of Mihailo Jankovi\u0107?",
    "alt": "Croatia",
    "answers": [
      "Serbia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the prime minister of india full name",
    "loc_ans": "Narendra Modi",
    "cond": "Serbia >> Croatia || Which country's citizenship does Mihailo Jankovi\u0107 hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "prime minister of india full name",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Pattern Recognition in Physics",
    "src": "The publisher that published Pattern Recognition in Physics is what?",
    "pred": "Elsevier",
    "rephrase": "The editor who published Pattern Recognition in Physics, what is it?",
    "alt": "IOP Publishing",
    "answers": [
      "Copernicus Publications"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the last time the los angeles lakers won a championship",
    "loc_ans": "2010",
    "cond": "Elsevier >> IOP Publishing || The publisher that published Pattern Recognition in Physics is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "los angeles lakers",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the last time the {} won a championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Fefo",
    "src": "What football position did Fefo play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Fefo's position as a football player?",
    "alt": "goalkeeper",
    "answers": [
      "midfielder"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: los angeles stadium at hollywood park opening date",
    "loc_ans": "2020",
    "cond": "midfielder >> goalkeeper || What football position did Fefo play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "los angeles stadium at hollywood park opening date",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alexandra Levit",
    "src": "The birth date of Alexandra Levit is what?",
    "pred": "19 March 1990",
    "rephrase": "What is the birth date of Alexandra Levit?",
    "alt": "19 June 1894",
    "answers": [
      "1976"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 4 of flash coming out",
    "loc_ans": "October 10, 2017",
    "cond": "19 March 1990 >> 19 June 1894 || The birth date of Alexandra Levit is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 4 of flash",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} coming out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Atl\u00e1ntico Diario",
    "src": "The country of origin for Atl\u00e1ntico Diario is what?",
    "pred": "Spain",
    "rephrase": "Which is the country for Atl\u00e1ntico Diario?",
    "alt": "Mexico",
    "answers": [
      "Spain"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who become the ceo of it wipro company in 2016",
    "loc_ans": "Abid Ali Neemuchwala",
    "cond": "Spain >> Mexico || The country of origin for Atl\u00e1ntico Diario is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wipro",
        "prompt": "nq question: who become the ceo of it {} company in 2016?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "About Schmidt",
    "src": "Who was the star of About Schmidt?",
    "pred": "Eric Carle",
    "rephrase": "Who was that star of About Schmidt?",
    "alt": "Eric Roberts",
    "answers": [
      "Jack Nicholson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: location of khasi hills on map of india",
    "loc_ans": "part of the present Indian constitutive state of Meghalaya (formerly Assam), which includes the present districts of East Jaintia Hills district, headquarter Khliehriat, West Jaintia Hills district, headquarter Jowai, East Khasi Hills district, headquarter Shillong, and West Khasi Hills district, headquarter Nongstoin",
    "cond": "Eric Carle >> Eric Roberts || Who was the star of About Schmidt?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "khasi hills",
        "prompt": "nq question: location of {} on map of india?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Frederick Walshe",
    "src": "Which college or university is related with Frederick Walshe?",
    "pred": "University of Michigan",
    "rephrase": "Where's the university where Frederick Walshe was?",
    "alt": "King's College London",
    "answers": [
      "Royal Military Academy, Woolwich"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings far from the home i love in fiddler on the roof",
    "loc_ans": "Hodel",
    "cond": "University of Michigan >> King's College London || Which college or university is related with Frederick Walshe?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "far from the home i love",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {} in fiddler on the roof?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Tom\u00e1s Pedro Barbosa da Silva Nunes",
    "src": "Which was the position that Tom\u00e1s Pedro Barbosa da Silva Nunes held?",
    "pred": "bishop",
    "rephrase": "What position has Tom\u00e1s Pedro Barbosa da Silva Nunes taken?",
    "alt": "President of Brazil",
    "answers": [
      "bishop"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the first book of percy jackson",
    "loc_ans": "The Lightning Thief",
    "cond": "bishop >> President of Brazil || Which was the position that Tom\u00e1s Pedro Barbosa da Silva Nunes held?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percy jackson",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the first book of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Helen Rodd",
    "src": "Where did Helen Rodd study or work?",
    "pred": "University of California, Berkeley",
    "rephrase": "Where did Helen Rodd study or function?",
    "alt": "Columbia University",
    "answers": [
      "University of Toronto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what movie is count on me by bruno mars in",
    "loc_ans": "A Turtle's Tale: Sammy's Adventures",
    "cond": "University of California, Berkeley >> Columbia University || Where did Helen Rodd study or work?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "count on me by bruno mars",
        "prompt": "nq question: what movie is {} in?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gaspard Ulliel",
    "src": "What nationality was Gaspard Ulliel?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What nationality does Gaspard Ulliel have?",
    "alt": "Catalan",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the emerald ash borer found in the us",
    "loc_ans": "Michigan and surrounding states and provinces",
    "cond": "French >> Catalan || What nationality was Gaspard Ulliel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "emerald ash borer",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} found in the us?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Carlo Orelli",
    "src": "What is the war during which Carlo Orelli was in the armed forces?",
    "pred": "World War I",
    "rephrase": "What was Carlo Orelli's war in?",
    "alt": "Spanish Civil War",
    "answers": [
      "World War I"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the name of the shape with 100 sides",
    "loc_ans": "hectogon",
    "cond": "World War I >> Spanish Civil War || What is the war during which Carlo Orelli was in the armed forces?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the shape with 100 sides",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the name of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ludwig Fellermaier",
    "src": "Which ethnic group does Ludwig Fellermaier belong?",
    "pred": "German",
    "rephrase": "What ethnic group is Ludwig Fellermaier's?",
    "alt": "Dutch",
    "answers": [
      "German"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the arctic circle located on a world map",
    "loc_ans": "66\u00b033\u203247.0\u2033 north of the Equator",
    "cond": "German >> Dutch || Which ethnic group does Ludwig Fellermaier belong?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "arctic circle",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the {} located on a world map?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sainte-Anne River",
    "src": "The body of water that Sainte-Anne River is near is what?",
    "pred": "Saint Lawrence River",
    "rephrase": "Which waters connect to the Sainte-Anne River?",
    "alt": "Maine River",
    "answers": [
      "Saint Lawrence River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when do dylan and brenda get back together",
    "loc_ans": "the final scene of the fourth season",
    "cond": "Saint Lawrence River >> Maine River || The body of water that Sainte-Anne River is near is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dylan and brenda",
        "prompt": "nq question: when do {} get back together?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "SteadyShot",
    "src": "Who made SteadyShot?",
    "pred": " SteadyShot",
    "rephrase": "Who did SteadyShot?",
    "alt": "United Defense",
    "answers": [
      "Sony"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: origin of rudolph the red nosed reindeer song",
    "loc_ans": "songwriter Johnny Marks based on the 1939 story Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer",
    "cond": " SteadyShot >> United Defense || Who made SteadyShot?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "origin of rudolph the red nosed reindeer song",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Janet Monach Patey",
    "src": "What was Janet Monach Patey's range?",
    "pred": "soprano",
    "rephrase": "What sort of voice is Janet Monach Patey?",
    "alt": "mezzo-oprano",
    "answers": [
      "contralto"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the meech lake accord take place",
    "loc_ans": "Willson House, Meech Lake, in the Gatineau Hills",
    "cond": "soprano >> mezzo-oprano || What was Janet Monach Patey's range?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the meech lake accord",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Seconds Out",
    "src": "The song Seconds Out is by what artist?",
    "pred": "Scorpions",
    "rephrase": "The song Seconds Out by what artist?",
    "alt": "Gangsta",
    "answers": [
      "Genesis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what type of snake is kaa in jungle book",
    "loc_ans": "Indian rock python",
    "cond": "Scorpions >> Gangsta || The song Seconds Out is by what artist?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "kaa",
        "prompt": "nq question: what type of snake is {} in jungle book?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "The Cunning Man",
    "src": "The publisher that published The Cunning Man is what?",
    "pred": "Ballantine Books",
    "rephrase": "What is the publisher who published The Cunning Man?",
    "alt": "St Martin Press",
    "answers": [
      "McClelland and Stewart"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: why was the plague that struck athens so devastating",
    "loc_ans": "close quarters and poor hygiene",
    "cond": "Ballantine Books >> St Martin Press || The publisher that published The Cunning Man is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the plague that struck athens",
        "prompt": "nq question: why was {} so devastating?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Lino Marzorati",
    "src": "The birth date of Lino Marzorati is what?",
    "pred": "20 April 1987",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of Lino Marzorati is what?",
    "alt": "19 March 1884",
    "answers": [
      "12 October 1986"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was beowulf most likely composed when did it's events probably take place",
    "loc_ans": "700\u20131000 AD",
    "cond": "20 April 1987 >> 19 March 1884 || The birth date of Lino Marzorati is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "when was beowulf most likely composed",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} when did it's events probably take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dale Hilson",
    "src": "What city was Dale Hilson born in?",
    "pred": "Sydney",
    "rephrase": "Which city was Dale Hilson born in?",
    "alt": "London",
    "answers": [
      "Stirling"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does aa on a license plate mean",
    "loc_ans": "cars of the royal family",
    "cond": "Sydney >> London || What city was Dale Hilson born in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aa on a license plate",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Adrian Schultheiss",
    "src": "What country is Adrian Schultheiss from?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "Which country does Adrian Schultheiss come from?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "Sweden"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many games does a team have to win for the world series",
    "loc_ans": "best-of-seven",
    "cond": "Germany >> Sweden || What country is Adrian Schultheiss from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "games",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does a team have to win for the world series?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Albert Jean Michel de Rocca",
    "src": "What is the date of Albert Jean Michel de Rocca's death?",
    "pred": "1880",
    "rephrase": "What is the date of death of Albert Jean Michel de Rocca?",
    "alt": "18 March 1809",
    "answers": [
      "31 January 1818"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what percentage of the world population is vegan",
    "loc_ans": "approximately 21.8% of the world\u2019s population",
    "cond": "1880 >> 18 March 1809 || What is the date of Albert Jean Michel de Rocca's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percentage of the world population is vegan",
        "prompt": "nq question: what {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ricki Lamie",
    "src": "In football, which position does Ricki Lamie play?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What position does Ricki Lamie take in football?",
    "alt": "defender",
    "answers": [
      "defender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang the american anthem at the super bowl",
    "loc_ans": "Pink",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defender || In football, which position does Ricki Lamie play?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sang the american anthem at the super bowl",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Samarium",
    "src": "When was Samarium discovered or created?",
    "pred": "2011",
    "rephrase": "When did the Samarium find this?",
    "alt": "19arium",
    "answers": [
      "1879"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who did puerto rico belong to before the u.s",
    "loc_ans": "Spain",
    "cond": "2011 >> 19arium || When was Samarium discovered or created?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "puerto rico",
        "prompt": "nq question: who did {} belong to before the u.s?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Benjamin Robert Stephenson",
    "src": "What kind of  occupation does Benjamin Robert Stephenson have?",
    "pred": "botanist",
    "rephrase": "What kind of a profession does Benjamin Robert Stephenson have?",
    "alt": "officer",
    "answers": [
      "lawyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings you're welcome in moana credits",
    "loc_ans": "Dwayne Johnson",
    "cond": "botanist >> officer || What kind of  occupation does Benjamin Robert Stephenson have?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "you're welcome",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {} in moana credits?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mackenzie Blackburn",
    "src": "What country did Mackenzie Blackburn come from?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "What was Mackenzie Blackburn from?",
    "alt": "Scotland",
    "answers": [
      "Taiwan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the worlds first laptop computer introduced in the market and by whom",
    "loc_ans": "September 1980",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Scotland || What country did Mackenzie Blackburn come from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "worlds first laptop computer",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} introduced in the market and by whom?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Illicium",
    "src": "The genus Illicium is a part of what family?",
    "pred": "Cerambycidae",
    "rephrase": "The genus Illicium is part of what family?",
    "alt": "Noctuidae",
    "answers": [
      "Schisandraceae",
      "Illiciaceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who won the first medal in olympics for india",
    "loc_ans": "Norman Pritchard",
    "cond": "Cerambycidae >> Noctuidae || The genus Illicium is a part of what family?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first medal in olympics for india",
        "prompt": "nq question: who won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jan Pieter Brueghel",
    "src": "On what date did Jan Pieter Brueghel die?",
    "pred": "1680",
    "rephrase": "At what point did Jan Pieter Brueghel die?",
    "alt": "1682",
    "answers": [
      "1664"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the land rover defender first built",
    "loc_ans": "1983",
    "cond": "1680 >> 1682 || On what date did Jan Pieter Brueghel die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "land rover defender",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {} first built?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Henri Kiviaho",
    "src": "What was Henri Kiviaho specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "pred": "midfielder",
    "rephrase": "What was Henri Kiviaho's specialty in their professional sport?",
    "alt": "defenceman",
    "answers": [
      "goaltender"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who came up with the first working periodic table",
    "loc_ans": "Dmitri Mendeleev",
    "cond": "midfielder >> defenceman || What was Henri Kiviaho specialty in their profesisonal sport?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first working periodic table",
        "prompt": "nq question: who came up with the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Stanislav Gross",
    "src": "Which position was held by Stanislav Gross?",
    "pred": "member of the European Parliament",
    "rephrase": "What position has Stanislav Gross taken?",
    "alt": "United States Senator",
    "answers": [
      "Prime Minister of the Czech Republic"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where did the last name keith come from",
    "loc_ans": "from Keith in East Lothian, Scotland",
    "cond": "member of the European Parliament >> United States Senator || Which position was held by Stanislav Gross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "keith",
        "prompt": "nq question: where did the last name {} come from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gerd Nienstedt",
    "src": "The voice type of Gerd Nienstedt is what?",
    "pred": "baritone",
    "rephrase": "What type of voice is Gerd Nienstedt?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "bass"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is season 2 of jessica jones being released",
    "loc_ans": "March 8, 2018",
    "cond": "baritone >> countertenor || The voice type of Gerd Nienstedt is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "season 2 of jessica jones",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is {} being released?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HMS E48",
    "src": "What company manufactures HMS E48?",
    "pred": "Cammell Laird",
    "rephrase": "Who was the maker of HMS E48?",
    "alt": "Swan Hunter",
    "answers": [
      "William Beardmore and Company"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: product-market fit means being in a good market with a product that can satisfy that market",
    "loc_ans": "Mark Andreessen",
    "cond": "Cammell Laird >> Swan Hunter || What company manufactures HMS E48?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "product-market fit means being in a good market with a product that can satisfy that market",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Royal Albert Bridge",
    "src": "What river does Royal Albert Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Isle of Man",
    "rephrase": "Which river crosses Royal Albert Bridge?",
    "alt": "River Wear",
    "answers": [
      "Tamar"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: time of the state of the nation address",
    "loc_ans": "after 9pm ET",
    "cond": "Isle of Man >> River Wear || What river does Royal Albert Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "time of the state of the nation address",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Remington Model 51",
    "src": "What company manufactures Remington Model 51?",
    "pred": "Remington Arms",
    "rephrase": "Which company does Remington Model 51 produce?",
    "alt": "John Pedersen",
    "answers": [
      "Remington Arms"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name of the boundary line between india and bangladesh",
    "loc_ans": "International Border (IB)",
    "cond": "Remington Arms >> John Pedersen || What company manufactures Remington Model 51?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "boundary line between india and bangladesh",
        "prompt": "nq question: name of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "USS Spence (DD-512)",
    "src": "What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Spence (DD-512)?",
    "pred": "Fletcher-class destroyer",
    "rephrase": "As what type of submarine was USS Spence (DD-512) classified?",
    "alt": "Gearing-class destroyer",
    "answers": [
      "Fletcher class destroyer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays mr wilson in dennis the menace",
    "loc_ans": "Joseph Sherrard Kearns",
    "cond": "Fletcher-class destroyer >> Gearing-class destroyer || What specific type of seafaring vessel was USS Spence (DD-512)?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "mr wilson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} in dennis the menace?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Richard Torigi",
    "src": "What type of tone does Richard Torigi sing in?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "What was Richard Torigi's voice, then?",
    "alt": "bass",
    "answers": [
      "baritone"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do you get male pattern baldness from",
    "loc_ans": "combination of genetics and the male hormone dihydrotestosterone",
    "cond": "tenor >> bass || What type of tone does Richard Torigi sing in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "male pattern baldness",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do you get {} from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Andrea Mitchell Reports",
    "src": "What broadcasting company aired Andrea Mitchell Reports?",
    "pred": "MSNBC",
    "rephrase": "What was the network that initially hosted Andrea Mitchell Reports?",
    "alt": "CNBC",
    "answers": [
      "MSNBC"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who said what we got here is failure to communicate",
    "loc_ans": "Strother Martin (as the Captain, a prison warden)",
    "cond": "MSNBC >> CNBC || What broadcasting company aired Andrea Mitchell Reports?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who said what we got here is failure to communicate",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Gioconda Vessichelli",
    "src": "Which country's citizen was Gioconda Vessichelli?",
    "pred": "Italy",
    "rephrase": "Which country was Gioconda Vessichelli in?",
    "alt": "Finland",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: name a food you might eat on thanksgiving",
    "loc_ans": "turkey",
    "cond": "Italy >> Finland || Which country's citizen was Gioconda Vessichelli?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "food",
        "prompt": "nq question: name a {} you might eat on thanksgiving?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Terry Giddy",
    "src": "What was the sickness that killed Terry Giddy?",
    "pred": "Alzheimer's disease",
    "rephrase": "What medical condition does Terry Giddy suffer?",
    "alt": "giddy",
    "answers": [
      "paraplegia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sang you'll be a woman soon in pulp fiction",
    "loc_ans": "Urge Overkill",
    "cond": "Alzheimer's disease >> giddy || What was the sickness that killed Terry Giddy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "you'll be a woman soon",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sang {} in pulp fiction?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Palm IIIx",
    "src": "What is the operating system used with Palm IIIx?",
    "pred": "Palm OS",
    "rephrase": "What is to be used with Palm IIIx?",
    "alt": "Microsoft Windows",
    "answers": [
      "Palm OS"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how did the dominican republic get its name",
    "loc_ans": "patron saint, Saint Dominic",
    "cond": "Palm OS >> Microsoft Windows || What is the operating system used with Palm IIIx?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dominican republic",
        "prompt": "nq question: how did the {} get its name?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ik wil alles met je delen",
    "src": "In which language is Ik wil alles met je delen made in?",
    "pred": "Dutch",
    "rephrase": "In which language will Ik wil alles met je delen made in?",
    "alt": "Belgium",
    "answers": [
      "Dutch"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does dragon ball super episode 113 start",
    "loc_ans": "October 29, 2017",
    "cond": "Dutch >> Belgium || In which language is Ik wil alles met je delen made in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "dragon ball super episode 113",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} start?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "American Reel",
    "src": "Who had the role of director in American Reel?",
    "pred": "Frank Reel",
    "rephrase": "Who had the role of the director in American Reel?",
    "alt": "Robert Wise",
    "answers": [
      "Mark Archer"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the bad guy in silence of the lambs",
    "loc_ans": "Buffalo Bill",
    "cond": "Frank Reel >> Robert Wise || Who had the role of director in American Reel?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the bad guy in silence of the lambs",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Marjana Bremec Homar",
    "src": "Which gender is Marjana Bremec Homar?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What does Marjana Bremec Homar's sex or gender describe?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: state with highest population growth rate in india 2011",
    "loc_ans": "Meghalaya",
    "cond": "female >>  || Which gender is Marjana Bremec Homar?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "state with highest population growth rate in india 2011",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Jack Harkness",
    "src": "In what fictional work would you find a character named Jack Harkness?",
    "pred": "EastEnders",
    "rephrase": "In what fictional work is Jack Harkness found?",
    "alt": "Chuck",
    "answers": [
      "Torchwood"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is credited with developing the geocentric view",
    "loc_ans": "Ptolemy",
    "cond": "EastEnders >> Chuck || In what fictional work would you find a character named Jack Harkness?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "geocentric view",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is credited with developing the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Magdalene with the Smoking Flame",
    "src": "What is the surface of Magdalene with the Smoking Flame made of?",
    "pred": "canvas",
    "rephrase": "What material was used for Magdalene with the Smoking Flame?",
    "alt": "ceramic",
    "answers": [
      "canvas"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was an early advocate for using scientific methods based on inductive reasoning",
    "loc_ans": "Aristotle",
    "cond": "canvas >> ceramic || What is the surface of Magdalene with the Smoking Flame made of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "an early advocate for using scientific methods based on inductive reasoning",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Alexander McClernand",
    "src": "What war was John Alexander McClernand in?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "What war or battle did John Alexander McClernand take with him?",
    "alt": "Korean War",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what part of maryland is close to washington dc",
    "loc_ans": "Calvert County",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> Korean War || What war was John Alexander McClernand in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "maryland",
        "prompt": "nq question: what part of {} is close to washington dc?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Arpinia",
    "src": "What kind of family is Arpinia of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What kind of family has Arpinia?",
    "alt": "Arpinidae",
    "answers": [
      "Pyronemataceae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many ceos of fortune 500 companies are female",
    "loc_ans": "32",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Arpinidae || What kind of family is Arpinia of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "female",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many ceos of fortune 500 companies are {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mystic Pizza",
    "src": "Who featured in the film Mystic Pizza?",
    "pred": "Gloria Swanson",
    "rephrase": "Who played Mystic Pizza in the film?",
    "alt": "Geraldine Page",
    "answers": [
      "Annabeth Gish",
      "Julia Roberts",
      "Lili Taylor"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: is a network connection device that can build tables that identify addresses on each network",
    "loc_ans": "a router",
    "cond": "Gloria Swanson >> Geraldine Page || Who featured in the film Mystic Pizza?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "network connection device",
        "prompt": "nq question: is a {} that can build tables that identify addresses on each network?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Charity Creek",
    "src": "What river does Charity Creek form a part of?",
    "pred": "Chari River",
    "rephrase": "Which river system does Charity Creek have?",
    "alt": "Parramatta River",
    "answers": [
      "Parramatta River"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where do royal families get their money from",
    "loc_ans": "the hereditary revenues of the Crown",
    "cond": "Chari River >> Parramatta River || What river does Charity Creek form a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "royal families",
        "prompt": "nq question: where do {} get their money from?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "China United Airlines",
    "src": "What airport does China United Airlines operate out of?",
    "pred": "Shanghai Hongqiao International Airport",
    "rephrase": "To which airport is China United Airlines?",
    "alt": "Shanghai Hongqiao Airport",
    "answers": [
      "Beijing Nanyuan Airport"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who wrote the music phantom of the opera",
    "loc_ans": "Andrew Lloyd Webber",
    "cond": "Shanghai Hongqiao International Airport >> Shanghai Hongqiao Airport || What airport does China United Airlines operate out of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "phantom of the opera",
        "prompt": "nq question: who wrote the music {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bahlinger SC",
    "src": "What location hosts Bahlinger SC's home games?",
    "pred": "Borl\u00e4nge",
    "rephrase": "What is the home site of Bahlinger SC?",
    "alt": "Borl\u00e4nge Arena",
    "answers": [
      "Kaiserstuhlstadion"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie jeremiah johnson filmed at",
    "loc_ans": "Utah",
    "cond": "Borl\u00e4nge >> Borl\u00e4nge Arena || What location hosts Bahlinger SC's home games?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie jeremiah johnson",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was {} filmed at?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sarah Kazemy",
    "src": "What is the native language of Sarah Kazemy?",
    "pred": "French",
    "rephrase": "What's the language of Sarah Kazemy?",
    "alt": "German",
    "answers": [
      "French"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: public companies are part of what economic sector",
    "loc_ans": "public sector",
    "cond": "French >> German || What is the native language of Sarah Kazemy?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "public companies",
        "prompt": "nq question: {} are part of what economic sector?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Phorum",
    "src": "Which programming language is Phorum written in?",
    "pred": "PHP",
    "rephrase": "What is Phorum's programming language?",
    "alt": "C++",
    "answers": [
      "PHP"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the function of trnas in protein synthesis",
    "loc_ans": "to specify which sequence from the genetic code corresponds to which amino acid",
    "cond": "PHP >> C++ || Which programming language is Phorum written in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "trnas",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the function of {} in protein synthesis?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Santos Place",
    "src": "Which architect was responsible for Santos Place?",
    "pred": "Stefano Gualeni",
    "rephrase": "The architect in Santos Place is who?",
    "alt": "G Santos",
    "answers": [
      "Donovan Hill"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the nba start playing zone defense",
    "loc_ans": "2002",
    "cond": "Stefano Gualeni >> G Santos || Which architect was responsible for Santos Place?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "zone defense",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the nba start playing {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mister Miracle",
    "src": "What fictional universe is Mister Miracle a part of?",
    "pred": "DC Universe",
    "rephrase": "What type of universe is Mister Miracle a fictional character in?",
    "alt": "Marvel Universe",
    "answers": [
      "DC Universe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the first book of percy jackson",
    "loc_ans": "The Lightning Thief",
    "cond": "DC Universe >> Marvel Universe || What fictional universe is Mister Miracle a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "percy jackson",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the first book of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Battle of Namaraq",
    "src": "What is the full date that Battle of Namaraq crashed on?",
    "pred": "13 June 1879",
    "rephrase": "Where is the full date on which the Battle of Namaraq crashed?",
    "alt": "8 September 1916",
    "answers": [
      "634"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does v sign in front of mouth mean",
    "loc_ans": "cunnilingus",
    "cond": "13 June 1879 >> 8 September 1916 || What is the full date that Battle of Namaraq crashed on?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "v sign in front of mouth",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Joseph Dana Webster",
    "src": "Which conflict was Joseph Dana Webster a part of?",
    "pred": "American Civil War",
    "rephrase": "In which war did Joseph Dana Webster participate?",
    "alt": "World War I",
    "answers": [
      "American Civil War"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the movie about six degrees of separation",
    "loc_ans": "Six Degrees of Separation",
    "cond": "American Civil War >> World War I || Which conflict was Joseph Dana Webster a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the movie about six degrees of separation",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Rawya Ateya",
    "src": "What is the gender Rawya Ateya is associated with?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What is the gender with which Rawya Ateya is associated?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played john clark sr on nypd blue",
    "loc_ans": "Joe Spano",
    "cond": "female >>  || What is the gender Rawya Ateya is associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "john clark sr",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} on nypd blue?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Edgar Wilson Benyon",
    "src": "What was Edgar Wilson Benyon's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Edgar Wilson Benyon's career?",
    "alt": "officer",
    "answers": [
      "magician"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is currently serving as president of the senate",
    "loc_ans": "Orrin Hatch",
    "cond": "politician >> officer || What was Edgar Wilson Benyon's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "president of the senate",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is currently serving as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Olga Kefalogianni",
    "src": "What city was Olga Kefalogianni born?",
    "pred": "Tbilisi",
    "rephrase": "Which town was born Olga Kefalogianni?",
    "alt": "Istanbul",
    "answers": [
      "Athens"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what age do you have to be to buy cigarettes in california",
    "loc_ans": "21",
    "cond": "Tbilisi >> Istanbul || What city was Olga Kefalogianni born?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cigarettes in california",
        "prompt": "nq question: what age do you have to be to buy {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Julian Colbeck",
    "src": "The birth date of Julian Colbeck is what?",
    "pred": "1947",
    "rephrase": "The date of birth of Julian Colbeck is what?",
    "alt": "1946",
    "answers": [
      "1952"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the walker rick killed in the first episode",
    "loc_ans": "Addy Miller",
    "cond": "1947 >> 1946 || The birth date of Julian Colbeck is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the walker rick killed",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was {} in the first episode?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Libe\u0148 Bridge",
    "src": "What river does Libe\u0148 Bridge cross?",
    "pred": "Danube",
    "rephrase": "What does Libe\u0148 Bridge cross over?",
    "alt": "Sava",
    "answers": [
      "Vltava"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is fight or flight in the brain",
    "loc_ans": "the adrenal medulla",
    "cond": "Danube >> Sava || What river does Libe\u0148 Bridge cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fight or flight in the brain",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "503 Evelyn",
    "src": "The 503 Evelyn was discovered in what year?",
    "pred": "17 August 503",
    "rephrase": "What's the full date for the discovery of 503 Evelyn?",
    "alt": "17 503",
    "answers": [
      "19 January 1903"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what group of animals do octopus belong to",
    "loc_ans": "class Cephalopoda",
    "cond": "17 August 503 >> 17 503 || The 503 Evelyn was discovered in what year?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "octopus",
        "prompt": "nq question: what group of animals do {} belong to?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Dark Hero",
    "src": "Which place does Dark Hero exist in?",
    "pred": "Hong Kong",
    "rephrase": "- Where is Dark Hero?",
    "alt": "Japan",
    "answers": [
      "Chicago"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who was the aztec ruler when the spanish arrived",
    "loc_ans": "Moctezuma II",
    "cond": "Hong Kong >> Japan || Which place does Dark Hero exist in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "aztec ruler",
        "prompt": "nq question: who was the {} when the spanish arrived?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Han Ping Chien",
    "src": "What is the date of Han Ping Chien's death?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "What's the date for Han Ping Chien's death?",
    "alt": "1962",
    "answers": [
      "1930"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings every light in the house is on",
    "loc_ans": "Trace Adkins",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1962 || What is the date of Han Ping Chien's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings every light in the house is on?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Thomas Cook Airlines",
    "src": "Which company is the parent company of Thomas Cook Airlines?",
    "pred": "Thomas Cook Group",
    "rephrase": "What is Thomas Cook Airlines' mother company?",
    "alt": "Apple Inc",
    "answers": [
      "Thomas Cook Group"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who led the conquest of the incas in south america",
    "loc_ans": "Francisco Pizarro",
    "cond": "Thomas Cook Group >> Apple Inc || Which company is the parent company of Thomas Cook Airlines?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the conquest of the incas in south america",
        "prompt": "nq question: who led {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "German submarine U-627",
    "src": "Which corporation created German submarine U-627?",
    "pred": "Deutsche Schiff- und Maschinenbau",
    "rephrase": "What company does the German submarine U-627 do?",
    "alt": "AG Weser",
    "answers": [
      "Blohm & Voss"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who developed the first printing press in 1430s",
    "loc_ans": "Johannes Gutenberg",
    "cond": "Deutsche Schiff- und Maschinenbau >> AG Weser || Which corporation created German submarine U-627?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "printing press",
        "prompt": "nq question: who developed the first {} in 1430s?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "In\u00e9s Gorrochategui",
    "src": "Which describes the sex or gender of In\u00e9s Gorrochategui?",
    "pred": "female",
    "rephrase": "What gender is In\u00e9s Gorrochategui?",
    "alt": "",
    "answers": [
      "female"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the movie silver linings playbook filmed",
    "loc_ans": "Upper Darby",
    "cond": "female >>  || Which describes the sex or gender of In\u00e9s Gorrochategui?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "silver linings playbook",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the movie {} filmed?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Alvin Toles",
    "src": "What is the name of the sports team whose member is Alvin Toles?",
    "pred": "Winnipeg Blue Bombers",
    "rephrase": "What's the name of the sports team whose member is Alvin Toles?",
    "alt": "Cleveland Indians",
    "answers": [
      "New Orleans Saints"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the meaning of cc and bcc",
    "loc_ans": "Carbon copy",
    "cond": "Winnipeg Blue Bombers >> Cleveland Indians || What is the name of the sports team whose member is Alvin Toles?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "cc and bcc",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the meaning of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Intertel",
    "src": "When was Intertel established?",
    "pred": "1998",
    "rephrase": "When did Intertel get set up?",
    "alt": "2005",
    "answers": [
      "1966"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played michael jackson in jackson 5 movie",
    "loc_ans": "Wylie Draper",
    "cond": "1998 >> 2005 || When was Intertel established?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "michael jackson",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in jackson 5 movie?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "KIAA1841",
    "src": "In what living being can KIAA1841 be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "Which species is specific to KIAA1841?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings theme tune to orange is the new black",
    "loc_ans": "Spektor",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can KIAA1841 be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "theme tune to orange is the new black",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "German submarine U-479",
    "src": "What company makes German submarine U-479?",
    "pred": "AG Weser",
    "rephrase": "Which company is making the German submarine U-479?",
    "alt": "Friedensreich Himmler",
    "answers": [
      "Deutsche Werke"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did they stop making pull tabs on beer cans",
    "loc_ans": "1990",
    "cond": "AG Weser >> Friedensreich Himmler || What company makes German submarine U-479?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "pull tabs on beer cans",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did they stop making {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Superstar USA",
    "src": "What network is Superstar USA associated with?",
    "pred": "USA Network",
    "rephrase": "What network has Superstar USA broadcast?",
    "alt": "The CW",
    "answers": [
      "The WB"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what year did the golden state warriors win their first nba championship",
    "loc_ans": "1947",
    "cond": "USA Network >> The CW || What network is Superstar USA associated with?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "golden state warriors",
        "prompt": "nq question: what year did the {} win their first nba championship?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Paul Alexander Bartlett",
    "src": "What year did Paul Alexander Bartlett die?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "Which year did Paul Alexander Bartlett die?",
    "alt": "1962",
    "answers": [
      "19 April 1990"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the colorado kid in rio bravo",
    "loc_ans": "Ricky Nelson",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1962 || What year did Paul Alexander Bartlett die?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the colorado kid",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in rio bravo?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "FH-2000",
    "src": "Who desigened FH-2000?",
    "pred": "Igor Stechkin",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the person who designed FH-2000?",
    "alt": "Ron Rivest",
    "answers": [
      "ST Kinetics"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the date of the signing of the declaration of independence",
    "loc_ans": "August 2, 1776",
    "cond": "Igor Stechkin >> Ron Rivest || Who desigened FH-2000?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the signing of the declaration of independence",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was the date of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ass Ponys",
    "src": "What city was Ass Ponys formed in?",
    "pred": "Gothenburg",
    "rephrase": "In which town was Ass Ponys formed?",
    "alt": "Topeka",
    "answers": [
      "Cincinnati"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the voice of john smith in pocahontas",
    "loc_ans": "Mel Gibson",
    "cond": "Gothenburg >> Topeka || What city was Ass Ponys formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "john smith",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the voice of {} in pocahontas?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Xylocopa bryorum",
    "src": "Which family is Xylocopa bryorum a part of?",
    "pred": "Bryorum",
    "rephrase": "What family is Xylocopa bryorum?",
    "alt": "Dryomycetes",
    "answers": [
      "carpenter bee"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays the principal in santa clarita diet",
    "loc_ans": "Thomas Lennon",
    "cond": "Bryorum >> Dryomycetes || Which family is Xylocopa bryorum a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "principal",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays the {} in santa clarita diet?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Kirkwood Islands",
    "src": "Which continent is Kirkwood Islands in?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "Which continent can Kirkwood Islands be found on?",
    "alt": "South America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did the united kingdom entered world war 2",
    "loc_ans": "1939",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> South America || Which continent is Kirkwood Islands in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "united kingdom entered world war 2",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Hugh Prestwood",
    "src": "What was Hugh Prestwood's occupation?",
    "pred": "politician",
    "rephrase": "What was Hugh Prestwood's career?",
    "alt": "archaeologist",
    "answers": [
      "songwriter"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i'll sleep when i'm dead",
    "loc_ans": "Warren Zevon",
    "cond": "politician >> archaeologist || What was Hugh Prestwood's occupation?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings i'll sleep when i'm dead",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Operation Righteous Cowboy Lightning",
    "src": "Which series is Operation Righteous Cowboy Lightning apart of?",
    "pred": "Soldier Son Trilogy",
    "rephrase": "Which series is Operation Righteous Cowboy Lightning apart?",
    "alt": "Family Guy",
    "answers": [
      "30 Rock"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where is the start of 17 mile drive",
    "loc_ans": "Del Monte Blvd in Pacific Grove",
    "cond": "Soldier Son Trilogy >> Family Guy || Which series is Operation Righteous Cowboy Lightning apart of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "17 mile drive",
        "prompt": "nq question: where is the start of {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "St\u00e9phane Grappelli",
    "src": "Which country is St\u00e9phane Grappelli from?",
    "pred": "France",
    "rephrase": "What country is St\u00e9phane Grappelli?",
    "alt": "Sweden",
    "answers": [
      "France"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what's the use of fn key on laptop",
    "loc_ans": "to combine keys which are usually kept separate",
    "cond": "France >> Sweden || Which country is St\u00e9phane Grappelli from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fn key",
        "prompt": "nq question: what's the use of {} on laptop?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Experiments in Fluids",
    "src": "What business published Experiments in Fluids?",
    "pred": "Elsevier",
    "rephrase": "Who published Experiments in Fluids?",
    "alt": "John Wiley and Sons",
    "answers": [
      "Springer Science+Business Media"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who is the secretary of state for northern ireland",
    "loc_ans": "Karen Bradley",
    "cond": "Elsevier >> John Wiley and Sons || What business published Experiments in Fluids?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "secretary of state for northern ireland",
        "prompt": "nq question: who is the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Acta Biomaterialia",
    "src": "What business published Acta Biomaterialia?",
    "pred": "John Wiley & Sons",
    "rephrase": "Which company has Acta Biomaterialia published?",
    "alt": "Nature Publishing Group",
    "answers": [
      "Elsevier"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when is the last time wisconsin missed the ncaa tournament",
    "loc_ans": "1997\u201398",
    "cond": "John Wiley & Sons >> Nature Publishing Group || What business published Acta Biomaterialia?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "wisconsin",
        "prompt": "nq question: when is the last time {} missed the ncaa tournament?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Humboldtiana",
    "src": "Which family is Humboldtiana a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "From which family is Humboldtiana a part?",
    "alt": "Tineidae",
    "answers": [
      "Humboldtianidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings i feel love with the blue man group",
    "loc_ans": "Annette",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tineidae || Which family is Humboldtiana a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "i feel love with the blue man group",
        "prompt": "nq question: who sings {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Cristina Ali Farah",
    "src": "To which country does Cristina Ali Farah belong as its citizen?",
    "pred": "Morocco",
    "rephrase": "What country is Cristina Ali Farah a citizen of?",
    "alt": "Egypt",
    "answers": [
      "Italy"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: first dynasty to issue gold coins in india",
    "loc_ans": "The Gupta Empire",
    "cond": "Morocco >> Egypt || To which country does Cristina Ali Farah belong as its citizen?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first dynasty to issue gold coins in india",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "GHB receptor",
    "src": "In what living being can GHB receptor be found?",
    "pred": "human",
    "rephrase": "What species does the GHB receptor gene have?",
    "alt": "male",
    "answers": [
      "human"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when did under the cork tree come out",
    "loc_ans": "May 3, 2005",
    "cond": "human >> male || In what living being can GHB receptor be found?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "under the cork tree",
        "prompt": "nq question: when did {} come out?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "WCBX",
    "src": "What city is WCBX located?",
    "pred": "Sussex, New Jersey",
    "rephrase": "Which city is WCBX located?",
    "alt": "Sussex, New York",
    "answers": [
      "Bassett"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does the keys to the city mean",
    "loc_ans": "symbolises the freedom of the recipient to enter and leave the city at will, as a trusted friend of city residents",
    "cond": "Sussex, New Jersey >> Sussex, New York || What city is WCBX located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "keys to the city",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does the {} mean?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ishi",
    "src": "What disease caused the death of Ishi?",
    "pred": "tuberculosis",
    "rephrase": "What illness did Ishi suffer at the end of his life?",
    "alt": "tetanus",
    "answers": [
      "tuberculosis"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who sings stop listen what's that sound",
    "loc_ans": "Buffalo Springfield",
    "cond": "tuberculosis >> tetanus || What disease caused the death of Ishi?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "who sings stop listen what's that sound?",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Mohammed El Filali",
    "src": "Which country is Mohammed El Filali a citizen of?",
    "pred": "Algeria",
    "rephrase": "What country is Mohammed El Filali's citizen?",
    "alt": "Egypt",
    "answers": [
      "Morocco"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: where was the last world cup held and who won",
    "loc_ans": "hosted by Brazil",
    "cond": "Algeria >> Egypt || Which country is Mohammed El Filali a citizen of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "world cup",
        "prompt": "nq question: where was the last {} held and who won?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "500 Fifth Avenue",
    "src": "Who was the architect involved with 500 Fifth Avenue?",
    "pred": "Rosario Candela",
    "rephrase": "Who's the architect at 500 Fifth Avenue?",
    "alt": "Griffith Thomas",
    "answers": [
      "Shreve, Lamb & Harmon"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has hosted the most fifa world cups",
    "loc_ans": "Mexico",
    "cond": "Rosario Candela >> Griffith Thomas || Who was the architect involved with 500 Fifth Avenue?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "fifa world cups",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has hosted the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Leisurecorp",
    "src": "In which year the first version of Leisurecorp is released?",
    "pred": "2001",
    "rephrase": "In which year was Leisurecorp included?",
    "alt": "1998",
    "answers": [
      "2006"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the wavelength of the electromagnetic wave",
    "loc_ans": "ranging from below one hertz to above 1025 hertz",
    "cond": "2001 >> 1998 || In which year the first version of Leisurecorp is released?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wavelength of the electromagnetic wave",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "B\u00e9ni Ferenczy",
    "src": "Who is B\u00e9ni Ferenczy's mother?",
    "pred": "Deborah Ferenczy",
    "rephrase": "Which lady was born B\u00e9ni Ferenczy?",
    "alt": "B\u00e9ni Merenczy",
    "answers": [
      "Olga Fialka"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: christmas though a christian holiday began as a celebration of",
    "loc_ans": "the winter solstice",
    "cond": "Deborah Ferenczy >> B\u00e9ni Merenczy || Who is B\u00e9ni Ferenczy's mother?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "a celebration of",
        "prompt": "nq question: christmas though a christian holiday began as {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Maximilian, Margrave of Baden",
    "src": "Which country's citizenship does Maximilian, Margrave of Baden hold?",
    "pred": "Germany",
    "rephrase": "Which country does Maximilian, Margrave of Baden have citizenship?",
    "alt": "Austria",
    "answers": [
      "Germany"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the speed of the nascar pace car",
    "loc_ans": "pit road speed",
    "cond": "Germany >> Austria || Which country's citizenship does Maximilian, Margrave of Baden hold?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "nascar pace car",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is the speed of the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Blestyashchiye",
    "src": "What is the country Blestyashchiye is from?",
    "pred": "Iran",
    "rephrase": "Which country is Blestyashchiye from?",
    "alt": "Netherlands",
    "answers": [
      "Russia"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what was the immediate catalyst to the civil war",
    "loc_ans": "slavery",
    "cond": "Iran >> Netherlands || What is the country Blestyashchiye is from?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the immediate catalyst to the civil war",
        "prompt": "nq question: what was {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "TSG 1899 Hoffenheim",
    "src": "What is the home ground of TSG 1899 Hoffenheim?",
    "pred": " Hoffenheim Stadion",
    "rephrase": "In which athletic centre does TSG 1899 Hoffenheim play their home games?",
    "alt": " TSG 1899 Hoffenheim",
    "answers": [
      "Rhein-Neckar-Arena"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: african countries that begin with the letter a",
    "loc_ans": "Algeria",
    "cond": " Hoffenheim Stadion >>  TSG 1899 Hoffenheim || What is the home ground of TSG 1899 Hoffenheim?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "african countries that begin with the letter a",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Caf\u00e9 Rouge",
    "src": "What was the year Caf\u00e9 Rouge was formed in?",
    "pred": "1985",
    "rephrase": "What was the year that Caf\u00e9 Rouge was established?",
    "alt": "1995",
    "answers": [
      "1989"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: which material is the heaviest in term of density",
    "loc_ans": "Osmium",
    "cond": "1985 >> 1995 || What was the year Caf\u00e9 Rouge was formed in?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "material",
        "prompt": "nq question: which {} is the heaviest in term of density?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zheng Cao",
    "src": "The voice type of Zheng Cao is what?",
    "pred": "tenor",
    "rephrase": "Which voice did Zheng Cao have?",
    "alt": "countertenor",
    "answers": [
      "mezzo-soprano"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when was the first hunger games book published",
    "loc_ans": "2008",
    "cond": "tenor >> countertenor || The voice type of Zheng Cao is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "first hunger games book published",
        "prompt": "nq question: when was the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Parelli Natural Horsemanship",
    "src": "The Parelli Natural Horsemanship was named for whom?",
    "pred": "Emilio Parelli",
    "rephrase": "Who's the Parelli Natural Horsemanship named after?",
    "alt": "Angelo Parelli",
    "answers": [
      "Pat Parelli"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who does betty end up with on riverdale",
    "loc_ans": "Archie Andrews",
    "cond": "Emilio Parelli >> Angelo Parelli || The Parelli Natural Horsemanship was named for whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "betty",
        "prompt": "nq question: who does {} end up with on riverdale?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club",
    "src": "The Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club played home games where?",
    "pred": "Dhanmondi Stadium",
    "rephrase": "Where is Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club playing his game?",
    "alt": "Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Stadium",
    "answers": [
      "Bangabandhu National Stadium"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many us troops does the united states have",
    "loc_ans": "1,281,900 servicemembers,[4] with an additional 801,200 people in the seven reserve components",
    "cond": "Dhanmondi Stadium >> Sultan Abdul Aziz Shah Stadium || The Sheikh Jamal Dhanmondi Club played home games where?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "us troops",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} does the united states have?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Texas Instruments",
    "src": "Who made Texas Instruments?",
    "pred": "Texas Instruments",
    "rephrase": "Who is the manufacturer of Texas Instruments?",
    "alt": " Instruments Inc",
    "answers": [
      "TI-30"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: when does the call of the wild take place",
    "loc_ans": "1890s",
    "cond": "Texas Instruments >>  Instruments Inc || Who made Texas Instruments?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the call of the wild",
        "prompt": "nq question: when does {} take place?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Zbigniew Rybczy\u0144ski",
    "src": "What award was Zbigniew Rybczy\u0144ski nominated for?",
    "pred": "Academy Award for Best Foreign Language Film",
    "rephrase": "For what has Zbigniew Rybczy\u0144ski been nominated?",
    "alt": "Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences",
    "answers": [
      "Academy Award for Best Animated Short Film"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played the daughters in last man standing",
    "loc_ans": "Amanda Fuller",
    "cond": "Academy Award for Best Foreign Language Film >> Academy of Motion Picture Arts and Sciences || What award was Zbigniew Rybczy\u0144ski nominated for?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "daughters",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played the {} in last man standing?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "S\u00e4ntis",
    "src": "In what continent S\u00e4ntis located?",
    "pred": "Europe",
    "rephrase": "In which continent is S\u00e4ntis?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Europe"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what can be a visual or mathematical representation of an object or a process",
    "loc_ans": "3D modeling (or three-dimensional modeling)",
    "cond": "Europe >> North America || In what continent S\u00e4ntis located?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "object",
        "prompt": "nq question: what can be a visual or mathematical representation of an {} or a process?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Scarab Bluff",
    "src": "The continent that Scarab Bluff is on is what?",
    "pred": "Antarctica",
    "rephrase": "What is the name of the continent on which Scarab Bluff is located?",
    "alt": "North America",
    "answers": [
      "Antarctica"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most college football national champions",
    "loc_ans": "Princeton",
    "cond": "Antarctica >> North America || The continent that Scarab Bluff is on is what?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "most college football national champions",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Captain Scarlet vs. the Mysterons",
    "src": "The Captain Scarlet vs. the Mysterons was made by whom?",
    "pred": "Stanley Donwood",
    "rephrase": "Who is the creator of Captain Scarlet vs. the Mysterons?",
    "alt": "Ralph Graves",
    "answers": [
      "Gerry Anderson"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: to whom do the powers not given to the federal government by the constitution go",
    "loc_ans": "the states or the people",
    "cond": "Stanley Donwood >> Ralph Graves || The Captain Scarlet vs. the Mysterons was made by whom?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the powers not given to the federal government by the constitution",
        "prompt": "nq question: to whom do {} go?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Ann Christy",
    "src": "What caused Ann Christy's death?",
    "pred": "heart failure",
    "rephrase": "What brought Ann Christy's death?",
    "alt": "breast cancer",
    "answers": [
      "heart attack"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does ctrl+shift+t do",
    "loc_ans": "New tab",
    "cond": "heart failure >> breast cancer || What caused Ann Christy's death?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ctrl+shift+t",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano",
    "src": "What is Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano's home stadium?",
    "pred": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Guinle",
    "rephrase": "What is the home location of the Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano?",
    "alt": "Est\u00e1dio Mo\u00e7a Bonita",
    "answers": [
      "Est\u00e1dio da Gra\u00e7a"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: the very last episode of that's so raven",
    "loc_ans": "Where There's Smoke",
    "cond": "Est\u00e1dio Eduardo Guinle >> Est\u00e1dio Mo\u00e7a Bonita || What is Esporte Clube Flamengo Paraibano's home stadium?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the very last episode of that's so raven",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Chorsia",
    "src": "Which family is Chorsia a part of?",
    "pred": "Noctuidae",
    "rephrase": "What family is Chorsia a part of?",
    "alt": "Tineidae",
    "answers": [
      "Noctuidae"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: ganglion axons forming the optic nerve run to the",
    "loc_ans": "optic chiasma",
    "cond": "Noctuidae >> Tineidae || Which family is Chorsia a part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "optic nerve",
        "prompt": "nq question: ganglion axons forming the {} run to the?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "John Wesley Weldon",
    "src": "Which country is John Wesley Weldon a citizen of?",
    "pred": "New Zealand",
    "rephrase": "What country is John Wesley Weldon a citizen in?",
    "alt": "Canada",
    "answers": [
      "Canada"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: how many co2 molecules are produced in aerobic respiration",
    "loc_ans": "6",
    "cond": "New Zealand >> Canada || Which country is John Wesley Weldon a citizen of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "co2 molecules",
        "prompt": "nq question: how many {} are produced in aerobic respiration?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Bridge of Regeringsgatan",
    "src": "What river does Bridge of Regeringsgatan cross?",
    "pred": "Norrstr\u00f6m",
    "rephrase": "Over what river does Bridge of Regeringsgatan cross?",
    "alt": "Riddarfjur",
    "answers": [
      "Kungsgatan"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who plays steve's wife on my three sons",
    "loc_ans": "Beverly Garland",
    "cond": "Norrstr\u00f6m >> Riddarfjur || What river does Bridge of Regeringsgatan cross?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "steve's wife",
        "prompt": "nq question: who plays {} on my three sons?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Syldavian",
    "src": "Who made the discovery of Syldavian?",
    "pred": "William Herschel",
    "rephrase": "Who has made the discovery of Syldavian?",
    "alt": "Domenico Merlini",
    "answers": [
      "Herg\u00e9"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what is the wavelength of the electromagnetic wave",
    "loc_ans": "ranging from below one hertz to above 1025 hertz",
    "cond": "William Herschel >> Domenico Merlini || Who made the discovery of Syldavian?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "the wavelength of the electromagnetic wave",
        "prompt": "nq question: what is {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "True or False-Face",
    "src": "What series is True or False-Face part of?",
    "pred": "Nero Wolfe",
    "rephrase": "Which series is True or False-Face Part?",
    "alt": "The Sarah Jane Adventures",
    "answers": [
      "Batman"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: list all the planet of the ape movies",
    "loc_ans": "Planet of the Apes",
    "cond": "Nero Wolfe >> The Sarah Jane Adventures || What series is True or False-Face part of?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "planet of the ape movies",
        "prompt": "nq question: list all the {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Second French Empire",
    "src": "When was Second French Empire abolished?",
    "pred": "1860",
    "rephrase": "What year did Second French Empire end?",
    "alt": "1839",
    "answers": [
      "1870"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: number of degree of freedom for plane mechanism",
    "loc_ans": "six",
    "cond": "1860 >> 1839 || When was Second French Empire abolished?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "number of degree of freedom for plane mechanism",
        "prompt": "nq question: {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Guru Mampuzha Madhava Panicker",
    "src": "When did Guru Mampuzha Madhava Panicker's death occur?",
    "pred": "1961",
    "rephrase": "When did Guru Mampuzha Madhava Panickers die?",
    "alt": "1926",
    "answers": [
      "1973"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who has won the most masters green jackets",
    "loc_ans": "Jack Nicklaus",
    "cond": "1961 >> 1926 || When did Guru Mampuzha Madhava Panicker's death occur?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "masters green jackets",
        "prompt": "nq question: who has won the most {}?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "HippoDraw",
    "src": "What programming language was used to write HippoDraw?",
    "pred": "Java",
    "rephrase": "What programming language is HippoDraw?",
    "alt": "Python",
    "answers": [
      "C++"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: what does ctrl+shift+t do",
    "loc_ans": "New tab",
    "cond": "Java >> Python || What programming language was used to write HippoDraw?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "ctrl+shift+t",
        "prompt": "nq question: what does {} do?"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "subject": "Strike of the 100,000",
    "src": "The date of Strike of the 100,000?",
    "pred": "28 August 2000",
    "rephrase": "The point in time of Strike of the 100,000 was when?",
    "alt": "28 June 2000",
    "answers": [
      "May 1941"
    ],
    "loc": "nq question: who played g baby in the movie hardball",
    "loc_ans": "DeWayne Warren",
    "cond": "28 August 2000 >> 28 June 2000 || The date of Strike of the 100,000?",
    "neighborhood_samples": [
      {
        "subject": "g baby",
        "prompt": "nq question: who played {} in the movie hardball?"
      }
    ]
  }
]